<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Disclaimer: http://www.sbr.gov.au/content/taxonomy_introduction_3_0.htm#Disclaimer -->
<link:linkbase xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase http://www.xbrl.org/2003/xbrl-linkbase-2003-12-31.xsd" xmlns:link="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xbrli="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance">
  <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#sbrReportLabel"/>
  <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#Label"/>
  <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#reportGuidance"/>
  <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/rprt/ato/rds/rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00/labRole" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#rds.0001.lodge.req.02.00.lodge.requestlabLinkInfoCls"/>
  <link:labelLink xlink:type="extended" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/rprt/ato/rds/rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00/labRole">
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/py/pyde/pyde.02.00.data.xsd#DE64" xlink:label="loc_DE64"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE64" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Group member organisation name type code - Australian</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE64" xlink:to="lbl_DE64" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE64" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Group member organisation name type code</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE64" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Group member organisation name type code - foreign</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE64" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Reporting Party organisation name type code - Australian</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE64" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Company name type code - reporting party</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE64" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Reporting party organisation name type code</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE64" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Reporting party organisation name type code - foreign</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/py/pyde/pyde.02.00.data.xsd#DE55" xlink:label="loc_DE55"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R and D incremental tax concession - Company Name</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE55" xlink:to="lbl_DE55" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R and D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Name</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R and D incremental tax concession - Entity Name</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R and D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Name</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Company name - reporting party</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">R and D Tax Offset Entity Name</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Research and Development Tax Offset Group Entity Name</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Company Name - Inform the relevant field with the name and Tax File Number (TFN) of the company and all group members (if any) that have incurred incremental expenditure in a group membership period in any of the four years. If the company has any group relationships, inform with any relevant group membership periods by using the grouping rules  for the year of income and the previous three years of income.  The head company of a consolidated group should also inform about any Research and Development (R&amp;D) grouping provisions, for example, if it is grouped with other entities with less than 100% control or ownership.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Name - Inform the relevant field with the name and Tax File Number of the group that has incurred incremental expenditure in any of the four years.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Company Name - Inform the relevant field with the name of the company and all group members that have incurred expenditure on foreign owned Research and Development (R&amp;D) in the group membership period in the Y0 year of income in the relevant field in the Research and Development tax concession schedule. 
NOTE: Ensure that only the name of the head company (and not the subsidiary companies) informs for a consolidated group.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Name - Inform the relevant field with the name of the group that has incurred incremental expenditure in any of the four years.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">R &amp; D Tax Offset Company Name - Inform the relevant field with the company name of all entities that are required to be grouped for the Research and Development (R &amp; D)  tax offset.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">R &amp; D Tax Offset Group Entity Name - Inform the relevant field with the entity name of the group that has incurred incremental expenditure in any of the four years.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/py/pyid/pyid.02.00.data.xsd#DE26" xlink:label="loc_DE26"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE26" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian Business Number - reporting party</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE26" xlink:to="lbl_DE26" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/py/pyin/pyin.02.00.data.xsd#DE706" xlink:label="loc_DE706"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE706" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Original or Amended Claim Indicator</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE706" xlink:to="lbl_DE706" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE706" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Original or Amended Claim Indicator - If the company has already lodged a Research &amp; Development (R&amp;D) schedule for the relevant income year, inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol of the Amended claim. If the company has not lodged a R&amp;D schedule for the relevant income year, inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol of the Original claim.
Enumeration Values: O - indicates that this is the first schedule that has been lodged with the Tax Office, A - indicates that the schedule has previously been lodged on paper or electronically.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/py/pyid/pyid.02.00.data.xsd#DE1901" xlink:label="loc_DE1901"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1901" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">AusIndustry or Innovation Australia number</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE1901" xlink:to="lbl_DE1901" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1901" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">AusIndustry/Innovation Australia Number - Inform the relevant field with the AusIndustry/Industry and  Research Development Board registration number issued to the company for the current income year for registered activities.  If the company is the head entity of a consolidated group and it is not registered with AusIndustry for the current year, inform the relevant field with the registration number of any one company in the consolidated group that has been registered.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.00.data.xsd#DE1914" xlink:label="loc_DE1914"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1914" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">R and D Tax Offset Aggregate Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE1914" xlink:to="lbl_DE1914" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1914" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">R &amp; D Tax Offset Company Aggregate R&amp;D Amount - Inform the relevant field with  the amount of each entity's aggregate Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure, and the R&amp;D group turnover respectively against the entity's tax file number. If  certain expenditure on R&amp;D activities cannot be deducted under the R&amp;D tax concession (for example, capital works deductions for buildings used for the purpose of carrying out R&amp;D activities) that expenditure will still form a part of the aggregate R&amp;D amount. If the relevant amounts are used  from part A to determine the aggregate R&amp;D amount of the company,  the above will need to be taken into account and any necessary adjustments made. Such adjustments relating to the aggregate R&amp;D amount should inform the relevant field with the amount that informs the field of the R&amp;D schedule. These adjustments must also be incorporated in the calculation of the aggregate R&amp;D amount of the company and R&amp;D group members in  the R&amp;D schedule. Adjustments to the R&amp;D group turnover should also be taken into account to calculate the R&amp;D group turnover recorded at that item.  If the group aggregate amount is $1,000,000 or less and the group turnover amount is less than $5,000,000, the company may choose to claim the R&amp;D tax offset.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1914" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">R &amp; D Tax Offset Group Entity Aggregate R&amp;D Amount - Inform the relevant field with the amount eligible for the Research and Development Tax offset where the decision has been taken to choose the R&amp;D tax offset instead of the tax deduction..</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.00.data.xsd#DE1916" xlink:label="loc_DE1916"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1916" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">R &amp; D Tax Offset - Group Totals - Aggregate R&amp;D Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE1916" xlink:to="lbl_DE1916" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1916" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">R &amp; D Tax Offset - Group Totals - Aggregate R&amp;D Amount - inform the relevant field with the Total  Aggregate R&amp;D Amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.00.data.xsd#DE1917" xlink:label="loc_DE1917"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1917" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">R &amp; D Tax Offset - Group Totals - Entity Turnover Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE1917" xlink:to="lbl_DE1917" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1917" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">R &amp; D Tax Offset - Group Totals - Entity Turnover Amount - Inform the relevant field with the Total of R&amp;D tax Offset Entity Turnover Amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.00.data.xsd#DE1918" xlink:label="loc_DE1918"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1918" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Amount eligible for the R and D Offset</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE1918" xlink:to="lbl_DE1918" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1918" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Amount eligible for the R &amp; D Offset - If the company chooses to take the R&amp;D tax offset, it means that the company has chosen to forgo a Research and Development (R&amp;D) tax concession deduction . The company cannot claim both.  NOTE  The company can choose to take the R&amp;D tax offset only on its company tax return (which includes the R&amp;D schedule).  The company must be registered with the IRDB before it makes its choice.  Transfer the amount from the calculation statement to R&amp;D tax offset of the Research and development tax concession schedule , and  tax offset in the Calculation section of the Company tax return.  An eligible company can choose a tax offset instead of a deduction  for a year of income if it is eligible to make that choice. The choice must be made in the company's return of income for the tax offset year.  The eligible company's tax offset for the tax offset year is calculated for each dollar that the company could, deduct for that year. An eligible company cannot deduct any amount  for the tax offset year if it chooses the tax offset for that year. Note: The tax offset is subject to the refundable tax offset rules.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.00.data.xsd#DE1919" xlink:label="loc_DE1919"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1919" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Calculated R and D Tax Offset</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE1919" xlink:to="lbl_DE1919" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1919" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Calculated R&amp;D Tax Offset - The amount at Research and development claim subject to the research and development tax offset is the company's entitlement to the R&amp;D tax offset. This amount is transferred to the Company tax return. Transfer the amount (30% (company tax rate) of Research and development claim subject to the research and development tax offset) to the Calculation Statement on  the Company tax return.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3341" xlink:label="loc_DE3341"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3341" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Add-Back of R and D Accounting Expenditure</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3341" xlink:to="lbl_DE3341" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3341" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Add-Back of R and D Accounting Expenditure - On the Research and Development (R&amp;D) Schedule at Preliminary Calculation inform the write-back of R&amp;D accounting expenditure for the amounts included at the appropriate expenditure labels at Information statement- Calculation of total profit or loss on the Company tax return field.  The amount shown at Preliminary Calculation on the R&amp;D Schedule must be the same as the amount shown at Information statement- Reconciliation to taxable income or loss- Accounting expenditure in item 6 subject to R&amp;D tax concession on the company tax return.  If expense amounts for R&amp;D deductions at Information statement- Calculation of total profit or loss on the company tax return have not been included (for example, those amounts are capitalised) write zero 0 at Preliminary Calculation on the R&amp;D tax concession schedule and Information statement- Reconciliation to taxable income or loss- Accounting expenditure in item 6 subject to R&amp;D tax concession on the company tax return. For consolidated groups -  If aggregated expenditure has been used for accounting R&amp;D expenditure under Information statement- Calculation of total profit or loss on the company tax return, add back the full amount of this aggregated expenditure at the fields Information statement- Reconciliation to taxable income or loss- Accounting expenditure in item 6 subject to R&amp;D tax concession on the company tax return.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3342" xlink:label="loc_DE3342"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3342" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Contracted Expenditure RRA - Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3342" xlink:to="lbl_DE3342" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3342" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Contracted Expenditure RRA - Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3342" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Contracted Expenditure - RRA Claimable at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3342" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Contracted expenditure RRA - Foreign owned R and D Exp</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3342" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Contracted Expenditure RRA - Base Amount - Inform the relevant field with the total amount of contracted expenditure that is Register Research Agency incurred.  The base amount must equal the sum of the other amounts claimed at the fields Claimable at 100%, Claimable at 125% and Foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3342" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Contracted Expenditure RRA - Claimable at 100% - Inform the relevant field with the portion of expenditure claimable at 100%.
Contracted Expenditure Registered Research Agency Claimable at 100%.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3342" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Contracted Expenditure - RRA Claimable at 125% - Inform the relevant field with the portion of expenditure claimable at 125%.
Contracted Expenditure Registered Research Agency Claimable at 125%.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3342" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Contracted expenditure RRA - Foreign owned R&amp;D Exp - Inform the relevant field with the portion of expenditure claimable at claimable at Foreign owned R&amp;D Exp.

Contracted Expenditure Registered Research Agency. Amount claimable under Subsection 73B(14C)</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/lr/lrla/lrla.02.05.data.xsd#DE3343" xlink:label="loc_DE3343"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3343" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Salary Expenditure Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3343" xlink:to="lbl_DE3343" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3343" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Salary Expenditure Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3343" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Salary Expenditure Claimable at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3343" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Salary expenditure - Foreign owned R and D Exp</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3343" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Salary Expenditure Base Amount - Inform the relevant field with the amount of salary expenditure for employees who are actually carrying out an eligible Research and Development (R&amp;D) activity  including: salaries, wages, allowances, bonuses, overtime payments, penalty rate payments, annual leave, sick leave and long service leave, and on-costs such as contributions to a superannuation fund, premiums for workers' compensation insurance and payroll tax. The expenditure may need to be apportioned between R&amp;D and non-R&amp;D activities. This item does not include: salary expenditure incurred in the construction of R&amp;D plant, depreciating assets, structural improvements or buildings; salary expenditure of R&amp;D support staff not directly connected with the research activity - include those at the fields Other R&amp;D expenditure; salary expenditure claimed that is to be adjusted in accordance with the prepayment provisions. The total of the amounts at the fields Claimable at 100%-  Claimable at 125% and Foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the base amount.

Eligibility Salary Expenditure. Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3343" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Salary Expenditure Claimable at 100% - Inform the relevant field with any amount of the Research and Development (R&amp;D) salary expenditure claimable at 100%, including: salaries, wages, allowances, bonuses, overtime payments, penalty rate payments, annual leave, sick leave and long service leave, and on-costs such as contributions to a superannuation fund, premiums for workers' compensation insurance and payroll tax. The expenditure may need to  be apportioned between R&amp;D and non-R&amp;D activities. This item does not include: salary expenditure incurred in the construction of R&amp;D plant, depreciating assets, structural improvements or buildings; salary expenditure of R&amp;D support staff not directly connected with the research activity - include those at Other R&amp;D expenditure that is to be adjusted in accordance with the prepayment provisions. The total of the amounts at the fields Claimable at 100%, Claimable at 125% and Foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3343" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Salary Expenditure Claimable at 125% - Inform the relevant field with any amount of the Research and Development (R&amp;D) salary expenditure claimable at 125%, including: salaries, wages, allowances, bonuses, overtime payments, penalty rate payments, annual leave, sick leave and long service leave, and on-costs such as contributions to a superannuation fund, premiums for workers' compensation insurance and payroll tax.  The expenditure may need to  be apportioned between R&amp;D and non-R&amp;D activities. This item does not include: salary expenditure incurred in the construction of R&amp;D plant, depreciating assets, structural improvements or buildings; salary expenditure of R&amp;D support staff not directly connected with the research activity - include those at Other R&amp;D expenditure that is to be adjusted in accordance with the prepayment provisions. The total of the amounts at the fields Claimable at 100%-  Claimable at 125% and Foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3343" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Salary expenditure - Foreign owned R&amp;D Exp - Inform the relevant field with any amount of the Research and Development (R&amp;D) salary expenditure claimable at Foreign owned R&amp;D Exp, including: salaries, wages, allowances, bonuses, overtime payments, penalty rate payments, annual leave, sick leave and long service leave, and on-costs such as contributions to a superannuation fund, premiums for workers' compensation insurance and payroll tax. The expenditure may need to  be apportioned between R&amp;D and non-R&amp;D activities. This item does not include: salary expenditure incurred in the construction of R&amp;D plant, depreciating assets, structural improvements or buildings; salary expenditure of R&amp;D support staff not directly connected with the research activity - include those at Other R&amp;D expenditure that is to be adjusted in accordance with the prepayment provisions. The total of the amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100%-  Claimable at 125% and Foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3344" xlink:label="loc_DE3344"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3344" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Other R and D Expenditure Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3344" xlink:to="lbl_DE3344" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3344" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Other R and D Expenditure Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3344" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Other R and D Expenditure Claimable at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3344" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Other R and D Expenditure - Foreign owned R and D Exp</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3344" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Other R&amp;D Expenditure Base Amount - Inform the relevant field with other Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure incurred directly in respect of R&amp;D activities carried on by or on behalf of the company. Do not include amounts to be shown at Contract other or  Plant leasing. Taxation Ruling states that overhead and administrative expenditure is directly in respect of R&amp;D where the eligible R&amp;D activities contributed to all or an identifiable part of the expenditure being incurred, or the conduct of eligible R&amp;D activities by the company would be materially impaired if the expenditure was not incurred. Adjust the amount of other R&amp;D expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions 'Other R&amp;D expenditure' does NOT include:  core technology expenditure;  interest expenditure;  feedstock expenditure (show eligible feedstock expenditure and residual feedstock expenditure at separate items);   expenditure incurred acquiring or constructing plant, pilot plant or a building, or extending, altering or making improvements to a building expenditure incurred acquiring or constructing a depreciating asset. The amounts claimed at the fields -Claimable at 100%- - Claimable at 125%- and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3344" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Other R&amp;D Expenditure Claimable at 100% - Inform the relevant field with any amount of 'other Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure' claimable at 100%.  Inform the relevant field with expenditure incurred directly in respect of R&amp;D activities carried on by or on behalf of the company. Do not include amounts to be shown at Contract other or  Plant leasing. Taxation Ruling states that overhead and administrative expenditure is directly in respect of R&amp;D where the eligible R&amp;D activities contributed to all or an identifiable part of the expenditure being incurred, or the conduct of eligible R&amp;D activities by the company would be materially impaired if the expenditure was not incurred. Adjust the amount of other R&amp;D expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions 'Other R&amp;D expenditure' does NOT include:  core technology expenditure;  interest expenditure;  feedstock expenditure (show eligible feedstock expenditure and residual feedstock expenditure at separate items);  expenditure incurred acquiring or constructing plant, pilot plant or a building, or extending, altering or making improvements to a building expenditure incurred acquiring or constructing a depreciating asset. The amounts claimed at the fields - Claimable at 100%- Claimable at 125%- and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3344" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Other R&amp;D Expenditure Claimable at 125% - Inform the relevant field with any amount of 'other Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure' claimable at 125%.  Inform the relevant field with expenditure incurred directly in respect of R&amp;D activities carried on by or on behalf of the company. Do not include amounts to be shown at Contract other or  Plant leasing. Taxation Ruling states that overhead and administrative expenditure is directly in respect of R&amp;D where: the eligible R&amp;D activities contributed to all or an identifiable part of the expenditure being incurred, or the conduct of eligible R&amp;D activities by the company would be materially impaired if the expenditure was not incurred. Adjust the amount of other R&amp;D expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions 'Other R&amp;D expenditure' does NOT include:  core technology expenditure;  interest expenditure;  feedstock expenditure (show eligible feedstock expenditure and residual feedstock expenditure at separate items); expenditure incurred acquiring or constructing plant, pilot plant or a building, or extending, altering or making improvements to a building expenditure incurred acquiring or constructing a depreciating asset. The amounts claimed at the fields -Claimable at 100% - Claimable at 125%- and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3344" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Other R&amp;D expenditure - Foreign owned R&amp;D Exp - Inform the relevant field with any amount of 'other Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure' claimable at Foreign owned R&amp;D Exp%. Inform the field with the expenditure incurred directly in respect of R&amp;D activities carried on by or on behalf of the company. Do not include amounts to be shown at Contract other or  Plant leasing. Taxation Ruling states that overhead and administrative expenditure is directly in respect of R&amp;D where: the eligible R&amp;D activities contributed to all or an identifiable part of the expenditure being incurred, or the conduct of eligible R&amp;D activities by the company would be materially impaired if the expenditure was not incurred. Adjust the amount of other R&amp;D expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions 'Other R&amp;D expenditure' does NOT include core technology expenditure;  interest expenditure; feedstock expenditure (show eligible feedstock expenditure and residual feedstock expenditure at separate items); expenditure incurred acquiring or constructing plant, pilot plant or a building, or extending, altering or making improvements to a building expenditure incurred acquiring or constructing a depreciating asset. The amounts claimed at the fields -Claimable at 100%-Claimable at 125%- and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3345" xlink:label="loc_DE3345"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3345" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Contract - Other Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3345" xlink:to="lbl_DE3345" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3345" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Contract - Other Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3345" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Contract - Other Claimable at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3345" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Contract other - Foreign owned R and D Exp</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3345" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Contract - Other Base Amount - Inform the relevant field with any expenditure incurred under a contract to another party, other than a Registered Research Agency (RRA), that is directly for Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities carried on by or on behalf of the company. This item excludes contracted expenditure carried out by an RRA and  expenditure under a contract that is, in substance, for the acquisition of plant. The amounts claimed at the fields -Claimable at 100%-  Claimable at 125%- and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3345" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Contract - Other Claimable at 100% - Inform the relevant field with the amount of expenditure incurred - Claimable at 100%. Inform the relevant field with any expenditure incurred under a contract to another party, other than an Registered Research Agency (RRA) that is directly for Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities carried on by or on behalf of the company. This item excludes contracted expenditure carried out by an RRA and expenditure under a contract that is, in substance, for the acquisition of plant. The amounts claimed at the fields Claimable at 100%, Claimable at 125%, and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3345" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Contract - Other Claimable at 125% - Inform the relevant field with the amount of expenditure incurred - Claimable at 125%. Inform any expenditure incurred under a contract to another party, other than an Registered Research Agency (RRA) that is directly for Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities carried on by or on behalf of the company.  This item excludes contracted expenditure carried out by a RRA and  expenditure under a contract that is, in substance, for the acquisition of plant. The amounts claimed at the fields -Claimable at 100%-  Claimable at 125%- and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3345" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Contract other - Foreign owned R&amp;D Exp - Inform the relevant field with the amount of expenditure incurred - Foreign owned R&amp;D Exp.  Inform any expenditure incurred under a contract to another party, other than a Registered Research Agency (RRA), that is directly for Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities carried on by or on behalf of the company.  This item excludes contracted expenditure carried out by an RRA and  expenditure under a contract that is, in substance, for the acquisition of plant. The amounts claimed at the fields -Claimable at 100%-  Claimable at 125%- and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3346" xlink:label="loc_DE3346"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3346" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Plant Leasing Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3346" xlink:to="lbl_DE3346" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3346" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Plant Leasing - Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3346" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Plant Leasing - Claimable at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3346" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Plant Leasing Base Amount - Inform the relevant field with any expenditure incurred in the hire or leasing of an item of plant that is directly in respect of Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities carried on by or on behalf of the company. Adjust the amount of plant leasing expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions. The amounts at the fields  - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3346" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Plant Leasing - Claimable at 100% - Inform the relevant field with any expenditure incurred in the hire or leasing of an item of plant that is directly in respect of Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities carried on by or on behalf of the company and claimable at 100%. Adjust the amount of plant leasing expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3346" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Plant Leasing - Claimable at 125% - Inform the relevant field with any expenditure incurred in the hire or leasing of an item of plant that is directly in respect of Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities carried on by or on behalf of the company and claimable at 125%. Adjust the amount of plant leasing expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3347" xlink:label="loc_DE3347"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3347" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Eligible Feedstock Expenditure - Base amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3347" xlink:to="lbl_DE3347" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3347" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Eligible Feedstock Expenditure - Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3347" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Eligible Feedstock Expenditure - Claimable at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3347" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Eligible feedstock expenditure - Foreign owned R and D Exp</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3347" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Eligible Feedstock Expenditure - Base amount - Inform the relevant field with the amount of eligible feedstock expenditure.  It is the excess of the feedstock input over the feedstock output for the related activities, in the year of income. The eligible feedstock expenditure will attract the additional 25% concession component.  If the company has eligible feedstock expenditure, include this amount.  Inform the remainder of feedstock input at Residual feedstock expenditure as residual feedstock expenditure. Adjust the amount of eligible feedstock expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions.  The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% ,  Claimable at 125% and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3347" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Eligible Feedstock Expenditure - Claimable at 100% - Inform the relevant field with the amount of eligible feedstock expenditure claimable at 100%.  It is the excess of the feedstock input over the feedstock output for the related activities, in the year of income. The eligible feedstock expenditure will attract the additional 25% concession component.  If the company has eligible feedstock expenditure, include this amount.  Inform the remainder of feedstock input at Residual feedstock expenditure as residual feedstock expenditure. Adjust the amount of eligible feedstock expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions.  The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% ,  Claimable at 125% and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3347" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Eligible Feedstock Expenditure - Claimable at 125% - Inform the relevant field with the amount of eligible feedstock expenditure claimable at 125%.  It is the excess of the feedstock input over the feedstock output for the related activities, in the year of income. The eligible feedstock expenditure will attract the additional 25% concession component.  If the company has eligible feedstock expenditure, include this amount.  Inform the remainder of feedstock input at Residual feedstock expenditure as residual feedstock expenditure. Adjust the amount of eligible feedstock expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions.  The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% ,  Claimable at 125% and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3347" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Eligible feedstock expenditure - Foreign owned R&amp;D Exp - Inform the relevant field with the amount of eligible feedstock expenditure claimable at Foreign owned R&amp;D exp.  It is the excess of the feedstock input over the feedstock output for the related activities, in the year of income. The eligible feedstock expenditure will attract the additional 25% concession component.  If the company has eligible feedstock expenditure, include this amount.  Inform the remainder of feedstock input at Residual feedstock expenditure as residual feedstock expenditure. Adjust the amount of eligible feedstock expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions.  The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% ,  Claimable at 125% and Foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3348" xlink:label="loc_DE3348"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3348" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Plant/Pilot Deductions Pre-29 Jan 2001 (include. Loss on Disposal) Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3348" xlink:to="lbl_DE3348" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3348" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Plant and pilot plant deductions pre 29 Jan 2001 (including disposal losses) Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3348" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Plant and pilot plant deductions pre 29 Jan 2001 (including disposal losses) Claimable at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3348" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Plant/Pilot Deductions Pre-29 Jan 2001 (include. Loss on Disposal) Base Amount - Inform the relevant field with any deduction that is claimed  for expenditure in acquiring or constructing such an item of pilot plant only if the unit of pilot plant is used exclusively for carrying on R&amp;D activities during the year of income. The base amount at this item is the annual deduction percentage of the qualifying pilot plant expenditure for such items. Balancing adjustments may be needed if items of plant and pilot plant for which expenditure has been deducted  are disposed of, lost or destroyed after being used exclusively for carrying on R&amp;D activities, provided no deduction is allowable to the company for depreciation.  Such balancing adjustments are covered under the  ITAA 1936. The consideration received for the plant at the time of disposal may vary from the written-down value. If this balancing adjustment is a loss, record it at this item. If the consideration receivable for the disposal, loss or destruction of the unit of R&amp;D plant is less than the written-down value, the amount of this difference can be claimed if a deduction for that expenditure is allowable under the  ITAA 1936. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% (Claimable at 150% pre 8/96) must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3348" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Plant and pilot plant deductions pre 29 Jan 2001 (including disposal losses) Claimable at 100% - Inform the relevant field with the amount of Plant/Pilot Deductions Pre-29 Jan 2001 (incl. Loss on Disposal) claimable at 100%. A deduction can be claimed  for expenditure in acquiring or constructing such an item of pilot plant only if the unit of pilot plant is used exclusively for carrying on Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities during the year of income. The base amount at this item is the annual deduction percentage of the qualifying pilot plant expenditure for such items. Balancing adjustments may be needed if items of plant and pilot plant for which expenditure has been deducted  are disposed of, lost or destroyed after being used exclusively for carrying on R&amp;D activities, provided no deduction is allowable to the company for depreciation.  Such balancing adjustments are covered under the  ITAA 1936. The consideration received for the plant at the time of disposal may vary from the written-down value. If this balancing adjustment is a loss, record it at this item. If the consideration receivable for the disposal, loss or destruction of the unit of R&amp;D plant is less than the written-down value, the amount of this difference can be claimed if a deduction for that expenditure is allowable under the  ITAA 1936. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% (Claimable at 150% pre 8/96) must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3348" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Plant and pilot plant deductions pre 29 Jan 2001 (including disposal losses) Claimable at 125% - Inform the relevant field with the amount of Plant/Pilot Deductions Pre-29 Jan 2001 (incl. Loss on Disposal) claimable at 125%. A deduction can be claimed  for expenditure in acquiring or constructing such an item of pilot plant only if the unit of pilot plant is used exclusively for carrying on R&amp;D activities during the year of income. The base amount at this item is the annual deduction percentage of the qualifying pilot plant expenditure for such items. Balancing adjustments may be needed if items of plant and pilot plant for which expenditure has been deducted  are disposed of, lost or destroyed after being used exclusively for carrying on R&amp;D activities, provided no deduction is allowable to the company for depreciation.  Such balancing adjustments are covered under the  ITAA 1936. The consideration received for the plant at the time of disposal may vary from the written-down value. If this balancing adjustment is a loss, record it at this item. If the consideration receivable for the disposal, loss or destruction of the unit of R&amp;D plant is less than the written-down value, the amount of this difference can be claimed if a deduction for that expenditure is allowable under the  ITAA 1936. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% (Claimable at 150% pre 8/96) must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3349" xlink:label="loc_DE3349"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3349" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Pre 29 Jan 2001 disposal profits Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3349" xlink:to="lbl_DE3349" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3349" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Pre 29 Jan 2001 disposal profits Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3349" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Pre 29 Jan 2001 disposal profits Base Amount - Inform the relevant field with the amount of Pre 29 Jan 2001 disposal profits. Include the amount by which the consideration exceeds the written-down value, up to the limit of the difference between the cost of the plant and its written-down value.   NOTE: If the company chooses to take the Research and Development (R&amp;D) tax offset,  use this amount in calculating the size of the offset. Include the amount of any balancing adjustment (assessable income). Balancing adjustments sale of pilot plant (profits). If the consideration receivable is greater than the written-down value of the unit of pilot plant, include the amount by which the consideration exceeds the written-down value, up to a limit of the difference between the cost of the plant and its written-down value. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3349" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Pre 29 Jan 2001 disposal profits Claimable at 100% - Inform the relevant field with the amount of Pre 29 Jan 2001 disposal profits claimable at 100%. Include the amount by which the consideration exceeds the written-down value, up to the limit of the difference between the cost of the plant and its written-down value NOTE: If the company chooses to take the Research and Development (R&amp;D) tax offset,  use this amount in calculating the size of the offset. Include the amount of any balancing adjustment (assessable income). Balancing adjustments sale of pilot plant (profits). If the consideration receivable is greater than the written-down value of the unit of pilot plant, include the amount by which the consideration exceeds the written-down value, up to a limit of the difference between the cost of the plant and its written-down value The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3350" xlink:label="loc_DE3350"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3350" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Plant and depreciating assets - post 29 Jan 2001 (decline in value) Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3350" xlink:to="lbl_DE3350" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3350" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Plant and depreciating assets - post 29 Jan 2001 (decline in value) Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3350" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Plant and depreciating assets - post 29 Jan 2001 (decline in value) Claimable at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3350" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Plant and depreciating assets - post 29 Jan 2001 (decline in value) Base Amount - Inform the relevant field with the notional amount as determined under at the base amount. Deductions for depreciating assets including certain capital works, used in carrying on Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities must have begun to be constructed, or have been acquired under contracts entered into, after midday Australian Eastern Standard Time on 29 January 2001. The amount allowable is determined through a notional application of the provisions of the  ITAA 1997, subject to certain assumptions. Calculation of research and development deduction asset applied to non-R&amp;D purposes as well as R&amp;D use in a year,  the R&amp;D portion  of the decline in value can be claimed.  If an STS taxpayer, or a taxpayer who could otherwise allocate an asset to a low-value pool, uses that asset for R&amp;D activities as its first use, the taxpayer must claim deductions for it under these provisions, not the STS  or low-value pool provisions. If the asset is used for non-R&amp;D purposes for part of the year or in a subsequent year, deductions for that part of the year or the subsequent year will be considered.  If an asset was not used for R&amp;D in an earlier income year and the company was entitled to a deduction for the asset(s) under a low-value pool or a Simplified Tax Systems (STS) pool in that year, continue to calculate deductions under the relevant pooling provisions, even if the asset is subsequently used for R&amp;D. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3350" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Plant and depreciating assets - post 29 Jan 2001 (decline in value) Claimable at 100% - Inform the relevant field with the notional amount as determined under claimable at 100%, including where the aggregate Research and Development (R&amp;D) amount is less than $20,000.   Deductions for depreciating assets including certain capital works, used in carrying on R&amp;D activities must have begun to be constructed, or have been acquired under contracts entered into, after midday Australian Eastern Standard Time on 29 January 2001. The amount allowable is determined through a notional application of the provisions of the  ITAA 1997, subject to certain assumptions. Calculation of research and development deduction asset applied to non-R&amp;D purposes as well as R&amp;D use in a year,  the R&amp;D portion  of the decline in value can be claimed.  If an Simplified Tax System (STS) taxpayer, or a taxpayer who could otherwise allocate an asset to a low-value pool, uses that asset for R&amp;D activities as its first use, the taxpayer must claim deductions for it under these provisions, not the STS  or low-value pool provisions. If the asset is used for non-R&amp;D purposes for part of the year or in a subsequent year, deductions for that part of the year or the subsequent year will be considered.  If an asset was not used for R&amp;D in an earlier income year and the company was entitled to a deduction for the asset(s) under a low-value pool or an STS pool in that year, continue to calculate deductions under the relevant pooling provisions, even if the asset is subsequently used for R&amp;D. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3350" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Plant and depreciating assets - post 29 Jan 2001 (decline in value) Claimable at 125%. - Inform the relevant field with the notional amount as determined under claimable at 125%. Deductions for depreciating assets including certain capital works, used in carrying on Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities must have begun to be constructed, or have been acquired under contracts entered into, after midday Australian Eastern Standard Time on 29 January 2001. The amount allowable is determined through a notional application of the provisions of the  ITAA 1997, subject to certain assumptions. Calculation of research and development deduction asset applied to non-R&amp;D purposes as well as R&amp;D use in a year,  the R&amp;D portion  of the decline in value can be claimed.  If an Simplified Tax System (STS) taxpayer, or a taxpayer who could otherwise allocate an asset to a low-value pool, uses that asset for R&amp;D activities as its first use, the taxpayer must claim deductions for it under these provisions, not the STS  or low-value pool provisions. If the asset is used for non-R&amp;D purposes for part of the year or in a subsequent year, deductions for that part of the year or the subsequent year will be considered.  If an asset was not used for R&amp;D in an earlier income year and the company was entitled to a deduction for the asset(s) under a low-value pool or an STS pool in that year, continue to calculate deductions under the relevant pooling provisions, even if the asset is subsequently used for R&amp;D.  The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3351" xlink:label="loc_DE3351"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3351" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Post 29 Jan 2001 Balancing Losses Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3351" xlink:to="lbl_DE3351" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3351" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Post 29 Jan 2001 Balancing Losses Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3351" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Post 29 Jan 2001 Balancing Losses Claimable at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3351" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Post 29 Jan 2001 Balancing Losses Base Amount - If the company is entitled to deduct an amount following a balancing adjustment event (such as disposal), inform the relevant field with the amount of any part of the balancing adjustment that the company is entitled to increase by 25%, in the calculation of the base amount.   The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3351" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Post 29 Jan 2001 Balancing Losses Claimable at 100% - If the company is entitled to deduct an amount following a balancing adjustment event (such as disposal), inform the relevant field with any balancing adjustment (deduction) claimable at 100%.  The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3351" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Post 29 Jan 2001 Balancing Losses Claimable at 125% - If the company is entitled to deduct an amount following a balancing adjustment event (such as disposal), inform the relevant field with any balancing adjustment (deduction) claimable at 125%.  The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3352" xlink:label="loc_DE3352"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3352" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Post 29 Jan 2001 Balancing Profits Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3352" xlink:to="lbl_DE3352" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3352" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Post 29 Jan 2001 Balancing Profits Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3352" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Post 29 Jan 2001 Balancing Profits Claimable at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3352" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Post 29 Jan 2001 Balancing Profits Base Amount - If the company is entitled to deduct an amount following a balancing adjustment event (such as disposal), inform the relevant field with the amount of any part of the balancing adjustment that the company is entitled to increase by 25%, in the calculation of the base amount.   The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3352" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Post 29 Jan 2001 Balancing Profits Claimable at 100% - If the company is entitled to deduct an amount following a balancing adjustment event (such as disposal), inform the relevant field with any balancing adjustment (deduction) claimable at 100%.  The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3352" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Post 29 Jan 2001 Balancing Profits Claimable at 125% - If the company is entitled to deduct an amount following a balancing adjustment event (such as disposal), inform the relevant field with any balancing adjustment (deduction) claimable at 125%.  The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3353" xlink:label="loc_DE3353"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3353" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Core Technology - deductible Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3353" xlink:to="lbl_DE3353" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3353" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Core Technology - Deductible Amount Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3353" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Core Technology - deductible Base Amount - Inform the relevant field with the deductible amount of Core technology expenditure.  Include deductions for core technology expenditure. Core technology expenditure includes expenditure incurred in acquiring, or in acquiring the right to use, core technology for Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities that are carried on by the company or on its behalf. A maximum of one-third of R&amp;D expenditure incurred during the year on R&amp;D activities related to the core technology can be deducted. Any undeducted core technology expenditure amounts can be carried forward to future years when the company undertakes R&amp;D activities related to the core technology. Adjust the amount of core technology expenditure claimed in accordance with prepayment provisions.  An adjustment may need to be made if core technology is disposed of.  If core technology expenditure is deductible, as a result  of the company joining a consolidated group, the tax cost of the core technology asset is 'set'. An adjustment may need to be made to any deductions allowable for the decline in value of that asset. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3353" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Core Technology - Deductible Amount Claimable at 100% - Inform the relevant field with the deductible amount of Core technology expenditure claimable at 100%. Include deductions for core technology expenditure. Core technology expenditure includes expenditure incurred in acquiring, or in acquiring the right to use, core technology for Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities that are carried on by the company or on its behalf. A maximum of one-third of R&amp;D expenditure incurred during the year on R&amp;D activities related to the core technology can be deducted. Any undeducted core technology expenditure amounts can be carried forward to future years when the company undertakes R&amp;D activities related to the core technology. Adjust the amount of core technology expenditure claimed in accordance with prepayment provisions.  An adjustment may need to be made if core technology is disposed of.  If core technology expenditure is deductible, as a result  of the company joining a consolidated group, the tax cost of the core technology asset is 'set'. An adjustment may need to be made to any deductions  allowable for the decline in value of that asset. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3354" xlink:label="loc_DE3354"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3354" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Interest or Amounts in the Nature of Interest Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3354" xlink:to="lbl_DE3354" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3354" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Interest or amounts in the nature of interest Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3354" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Interest or Amounts in the Nature of Interest Base Amount - Inform the relevant field with the amount of interest expenditure.
This item includes interest, or an amount in the nature of interest, incurred during the year of income in the financing of Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities. NOTE: You may need to adjust the amount of interest expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3354" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Interest or amounts in the nature of interest Claimable at 100% - Inform the relevant field with the amount of interest expenditure claimable at 100%.  This item includes interest, or an amount in the nature of interest, incurred during the year of income in the financing of Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities. NOTE: You may need to adjust the amount of interest expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3355" xlink:label="loc_DE3355"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3355" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Residual Feedstock Expenditure Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3355" xlink:to="lbl_DE3355" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3355" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Residual Feedstock Expenditure Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3355" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Residual Feedstock Expenditure Base Amount - Inform the relevant field with the amount of residual feedstock expenditure. Residual feedstock expenditure is the lesser amount of the company's feedstock input and feedstock output for Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities in the year of income. If feedstock inputs are greater than feedstock outputs, inform the relevant field with  the outputs amount; if it is less than feedstock outputs, inform the relevant field with the inputs amount  Residual feedstock expenditure. This is the residual feedstock expenditure.  The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3355" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Residual Feedstock Expenditure Claimable at 100% - Inform the relevant field with the amount of residual feedstock expenditure. Residual feedstock expenditure is the lesser amount of the company's feedstock input and feedstock output for Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities in the year of income. If feedstock inputs are greater than feedstock outputs, inform the relevant field with the outputs amount; if it is less than feedstock outputs, inform the relevant field with the inputs amount Residual feedstock expenditure. This is the residual feedstock expenditure. The amounts at - Claimable at 100% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3356" xlink:label="loc_DE3356"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3356" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Total of Allocated Base Amounts - Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3356" xlink:to="lbl_DE3356" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3356" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Total of Allocated Base Amounts Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3356" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Total of Allocated Base Amounts Claimable at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3356" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Total of Allocated Base Amounts - Foreign owned R and D Exp</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3356" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Total of Allocated Base Amounts - Base Amount - Inform the relevant field with the total of Allocated Base Amounts.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3356" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Total of Allocated Base Amounts Claimable at 100% - Inform the relevant field with the total of Allocated Base Amounts claimable at 100%.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3356" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Total of Allocated Base Amounts Claimable at 125% - Inform the relevant field with the Total of Allocated Base Amounts claimable at 125%.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3356" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Total of Allocated Base Amounts - Foreign owned R&amp;D Exp - Inform the relevant field with the Total of Allocated Base Amounts - Foreign owned Research and Development expenditure.
 It should be noted that some of the amounts listed under base amount could be negative.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3357" xlink:label="loc_DE3357"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3357" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Claims including Concession Claimable at 100 percent</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3357" xlink:to="lbl_DE3357" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3357" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Claims including Concession Claimable at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3357" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Claims including concession - Foreign owned R and D Exp</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3357" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Claims including Concession Claimable at 100% -  Inform the relevant field with the total of allocated base amounts by 100%.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3357" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Claims including Concession Claimable at 125% - Inform the relevant field with the total of allocated base amounts by 125%.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3357" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Claims including concession - Foreign owned R&amp;D Exp - Inform the relevant field with the total of allocated base amounts of the calculation of the claim amount at foreign owned Research and Development (R&amp;D) Exp.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3358" xlink:label="loc_DE3358"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3358" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">R and D tax concession - excluding extra incremental 50 percent deduction</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3358" xlink:to="lbl_DE3358" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3358" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">R and D tax concession - excluding extra incremental 75 percent deduction</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3358" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">R&amp;D tax concession - excluding extra incremental 50% deduction - Inform the relevant field with the amount that is to be transferred to Australian owned Research and Development (R&amp;D) tax concession - not including the relevant field of the Company tax return.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3358" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">R&amp;D tax concession - excluding extra incremental 75% deduction - Inform the relevant field with the amount to be transferred to foreign owned Research and Development (R&amp;D) tax concession - not including the relevant field of the Company tax return.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/baf/bafpr/bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3359" xlink:label="loc_DE3359"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3359" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Adjustments to aggregate R and D amount of company</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3359" xlink:to="lbl_DE3359" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3359" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Adjustments to aggregate R&amp;D amount of company - Inform the relevant field with the amount of expenditure on the following items- Building expenditure and other adjustments required to the company's aggregate Research and Development (R&amp;D) amount, other amounts that are not included in the fields informing the Calculation of R&amp;D in the Research and Development Tax Concession Schedule that are needed to calculate the company's aggregate R&amp;D amount. These amounts form part of the aggregate research and development amount even though they are not deductible.  These include the total amount of any capital expenditure on buildings used for the purpose of carrying on R&amp;D activities, for companies that are lodging a return regarding income and deductions for a period before or after they joined a consolidated group, the additional aggregate research and development amount.   NOTE The items referred to above are not eligible for deduction under the R&amp;D tax concession but are part of the aggregate R&amp;D amount.  (Only complete this item if the company chooses to take the R&amp;D tax offset. Include also at Amount of expenditure on the following items- Building expenditure and other adjustments required to the company's aggregate R&amp;D amount any positive or negative adjustments that may need to be made where a company has a transitional substituted account period in the year of income, and where the amounts reported in the fields informing the Calculation of R&amp;D in the Research and Development Tax Concession Schedule that relate to a period that is less or greater than 12 months. The aggregate R&amp;D amount is calculated using the 12 month period that is the tax offset year.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagg/gfagg.02.01.data.xsd#DE3360" xlink:label="loc_DE3360"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3360" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Entitlement to government grants and recoupments for the financial year that relate to activities and projects claimed</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3360" xlink:to="lbl_DE3360" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3360" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Entitlement to government grants and recoupments for the financial year that relate to activities and projects claimed - Inform the relevant field with the total amount of government recoupments of, or grants received in respect of, Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure for which the company is claiming the R&amp;D tax concession in the year of income. Exclude amounts received under Co-operative Research Centre (CRC) programs.  NOTE: The clawback provisions may operate on these amounts.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagg/gfagg.02.01.data.xsd#DE3361" xlink:label="loc_DE3361"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3361" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Grants and recoupments attributable to incremental expenditure on Australian owned R and D</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3361" xlink:to="lbl_DE3361" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3361" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Grants and recoupments attributable to incremental expenditure on Australian owned R&amp;D - Inform the relevant field with the amount of government grants and recoupments to incremental expenditure on Australian owned Research and Development (R&amp;D).</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagg/gfagg.02.01.data.xsd#DE3362" xlink:label="loc_DE3362"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3362" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Grants and recoupments attributable to expenditure on foreign owned R and D</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3362" xlink:to="lbl_DE3362" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3362" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Grants and recoupments attributable to expenditure on foreign owned R&amp;D - Inform the relevant field with the amount of government grants and recoupments to expenditure on Foreign owned Research and Development (R&amp;D).</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3363" xlink:label="loc_DE3363"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3363" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Eligibility and claim indicator for the Australian owned R and D incremental tax concession</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3363" xlink:to="lbl_DE3363" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3363" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Are you eligible for the Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession and do you wish to claim it? - Inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol if the company wants to claim the Australian owned Research and Development (R&amp;D) incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3364" xlink:label="loc_DE3364"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3364" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R and D incremental tax concession - Adjustment to Y0 reduced expenditure on Australian ownedR and D of the claiming company - not deductible at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3364" xlink:to="lbl_DE3364" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3364" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R and D incremental tax concession - Adjustment to Y0 reduced expenditure on Australian ownedR and D of the claiming company - deductible at 125 percent</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3364" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Adjustment to Y0 reduced expenditure on Australian owned R&amp;D of the claiming company - not deductible at 125% - Inform the relevant field with any adjustments which may be required if any of the following circumstances apply;  the company has incurred some R&amp;D expenditure which is not deductible (for example, in relation to unregistered activities).  An intra-group mark-up should be included in any adjustments. The amount of intra-group mark-up is shown Adjustment to Y0. Note: If no other amounts are included at  Adjustment to Y0, inform this field with a negative value.  
If a company has left or joined a consolidated group an adjustment (positive or negative) may be required at Adjustment to Y0.  It is also used to adjust incremental expenditure claimable at 100% and incremental expenditure that is not deductible.  Total of additional schedule where applicable is used to adjust the incremental expenditure claimable at 125%. A negative value may be inserted in these rows if necessary.  The types of adjustments that may be required to inform the field of the Y0 amount may also likely affect the amount reported in respect of Y-1, Y-2 and Y-3 for the company and other group members.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3364" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Adjustment to Y0 reduced expenditure on Australian owned R&amp;D of the claiming company - deductible at 125% - Inform the relevant field with any adjustments of the incremental expenditure which may be required if any of the following circumstances apply; where deduction amounts claimed in part A relate to a period that is greater or less than 12 months an adjustment must be made to reflect the incremental expenditure incurred in the 12 month period. 
If a company has left or joined a consolidated group an adjustment (positive or negative) may be required to inform the relevant field at Adjustment to Y0.  A negative value may inform in these fields if necessary.  The types of adjustments that may be required to inform the field of the Y0 amount may also likely affect the amount reported in respect of Y-1, Y-2 and Y-3 for the company and other group members.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3365" xlink:label="loc_DE3365"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3365" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Indicator of whether the company, or any of its group members, was eligible, or deemed to be eligible, to claim an incremental tax concession in the year prior to the current year.</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3365" xlink:to="lbl_DE3365" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3365" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Indicator of whether the company, or any of its group members, was eligible, or deemed to be eligible, to claim an incremental tax concession in the year two years prior to the current year</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3365" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Please indicate whether the company, or any of its group members, was eligible, or deemed to be eligible, to claim an incremental tax concession in the year prior to the current year. - Inform the relevant field with a Y for Yes or N for No to the question of whether the company, or any of its group members, was eligible, or deemed to be eligible, to claim an incremental tax concession in 2007.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3365" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Please indicate whether the company, or any of its group members, was eligible, or deemed to be eligible, to claim an incremental tax concession in the year two years prior to the current year - Inform the relevant field with a Y for Yes or N for No to the question of  whether the company, or any of its group members, was eligible, or deemed to be eligible, to claim an incremental tax concession in 2006.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3366" xlink:label="loc_DE3366"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3366" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R and D - extra incremental 50 percent deduction</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3366" xlink:to="lbl_DE3366" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3366" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R and D - extra incremental 75 percent deduction</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3366" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D - extra incremental 50% deduction - Inform the relevant field with the amount of the company's deduction under the Research and Development (R&amp;D) incremental concession on the Schedule and Incremental R&amp;D (additional 50%) deduction in the relevant field on the Company tax return.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3366" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D - extra incremental 75% deduction - Inform the relevant field with the amount transferred from the calculation made in relation to an eligible company claim regarding the deduction of an extra 75% deduction on foreign owned Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3367" xlink:label="loc_DE3367"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3367" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Eligible for the foreign owned R and D incremental tax concession and wish to claim it?</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3367" xlink:to="lbl_DE3367" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3367" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Are you eligible for the foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession and do you wish to claim it? - Inform the appropriate symbol in the relevant field if the company wants to claim the Foreign owned Research and Development (R&amp;D) incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3368" xlink:label="loc_DE3368"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R and D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y0 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3368" xlink:to="lbl_DE3368" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R and D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y-1 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R and D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y-2 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R and D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y-3 reduced expenditureAustralian ownedR and D incremental tax concession - Company Year-3 Reduced Expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R and D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y0 Reduced Expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R and D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y-1 Reduced Expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R and D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y-2 Reduced Expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R and D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y-3 Reduced Expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R and D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y0 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R and D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y-1 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R and D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y-2 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R and D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y-3 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R and D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y0 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R and D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y-1 Reduced Expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R and D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y-2 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R and D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y-3 Reduced Expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y0 reduced expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y-1 reduced expenditure - The company should inform the relevant field by calculating the amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y-2 reduced expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y-3 reduced expenditureAustralian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Company Year-3 Reduced Expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y0 Reduced Expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession -Group Entity Year Y-1 Reduced Expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y-2 Reduced Expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3 .  Total each column to determine the Research and Development (R&amp;D) spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y-3 Reduced Expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y0 reduced expenditure - Calculate and inform the relevant field  with the reduced expenditure on foreign owned R&amp;D for the company for its group membership period in the current year of income (Y0) using the calculation table.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y-1 reduced expenditure - Calculate and inform the relevant field with the amount of reduced expenditure and reduced notional expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform the amounts of reduced expenditure for each company in the relevant fields.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y-2 reduced expenditure - Calculate and inform the relevant field with the amount of reduced expenditure and reduced notional expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform the amounts of reduced expenditure for each company in the relevant fields.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Company Year Y-3 reduced expenditure - Calculate and inform the relevant field with the amount of reduced expenditure and reduced notional expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform the amounts of reduced expenditure for each company in the relevant fields.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y0 reduced expenditure - Calculate and inform the relevant field the amount of reduced expenditure and reduced notional expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform the amounts of reduced expenditure for each company in the relevant fields.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y-1 Reduced Expenditure - Calculate and inform the relevant field the amount of reduced expenditure and reduced notional expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform the amounts of reduced expenditure for each company in the relevant fields.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y-2 reduced expenditure - Calculate and inform the relevant field the amount of reduced expenditure and reduced notional expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform the amounts of reduced expenditure for each company in the relevant fields.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Entity Year Y-3 Reduced Expenditure - Calculate and inform the relevant field the amount of reduced expenditure and reduced notional expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform the amounts of reduced expenditure for each company in the relevant fields.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3369" xlink:label="loc_DE3369"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3369" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R and D incremental tax concession - Adjustment to Y0 reduced expenditure on Foreign owned R and D of the claiming company</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3369" xlink:to="lbl_DE3369" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3369" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Adjustment to Y0 reduced expenditure on Foreign owned R&amp;D of the claiming company - Inform the relevant field with the amount of Foreign owned research and Development incremental tax concession adjustment to Y0 reduced expenditure on foreign owned R&amp;D for the claiming company.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3370" xlink:label="loc_DE3370"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3370" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Wish to claim the R and D tax offset?</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3370" xlink:to="lbl_DE3370" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3370" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Do you wish to claim the R&amp;D tax offset? - If the company chooses to take the offset, inform the Yes field with the appropriate symbol. If the company is ineligible to claim the offset, inform the No field with the appropriate symbol.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3371" xlink:label="loc_DE3371"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3371" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">R and D Tax Offset Company Turnover</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3371" xlink:to="lbl_DE3371" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3371" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">R and D Tax Offset Group Entity Turnover</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3371" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">R &amp; D Tax Offset Company Turnover - Inform the relevant field with the amount of each entity's aggregate Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure, and the R&amp;D group turnover respectively against the entity's tax file number. If certain expenditure on R&amp;D activities  cannot be deducted under the R&amp;D tax concession (for example, capital works deductions for buildings used for the purpose of carrying out R&amp;D activities) that expenditure will still form a part of the aggregate R&amp;D amount. If the relevant amounts are used  informing earlier fields are used to determine the aggregate R&amp;D amount of the company,  the above will need to be taken into account and any necessary adjustments made. Such adjustments relating to the aggregate R&amp;D amount should be included at amount in the relevant field of the R&amp;D schedule. These adjustments must also be incorporated in the calculation of the aggregate R&amp;D amount of the company and R&amp;D group members  in  the R&amp;D schedule. Adjustments to the R&amp;D group turnover should also be taken into account to calculate the R&amp;D group turnover recorded at that item.  If the group aggregate amount is $1,000,000 or less and the group turnover amount is less than $5,000,000, the company may choose to claim the R&amp;D tax offset.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3371" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">R &amp; D Tax Offset Group Entity Turnover - Inform the relevant field with the amount of each entity's aggregate Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure, and the R&amp;D group turnover respectively against the entity's tax file number. If  certain expenditure on R&amp;D activities  cannot be deducted under the R&amp;D tax concession (for example, capital works deductions for buildings used for the purpose of carrying out R&amp;D activities) that expenditure will still form a part of the aggregate R&amp;D amount. If the relevant amounts are used  from part A to determine the aggregate R&amp;D amount of the company,  the above will need to be taken into account and any necessary adjustments made. Such adjustments relating to the aggregate R&amp;D amount should be included at amount in part B of the R&amp;D schedule. These adjustments must also be incorporated in the calculation of the aggregate R&amp;D amount of the company and R&amp;D group members  in the R&amp;D schedule. Adjustments to the R&amp;D group turnover should also be taken into account to calculate the R&amp;D group turnover recorded at that item.  If the group aggregate amount is $1,000,000 or less and the group turnover amount is less than $5,000,000, the company may choose to claim the R&amp;D tax offset.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/gfa/gfagc/gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3568" xlink:label="loc_DE3568"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y0 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3568" xlink:to="lbl_DE3568" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y-1 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y-2 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y-3 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y0 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y-1 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y-2 reduced expenditure</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y-3</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y0 reduced expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the total amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y-1 reduced expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the total amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y-2 reduced expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the total amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y-3 reduced expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the total amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y0 reduced expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the total amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y-1 reduced expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the total amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y-2 reduced expenditure - The company should inform the field by calculating the total amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year Y-3 - The company should inform the field by calculating the total amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y-1, Y-2, and Y-3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1332" xlink:label="loc_RA1332"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1332" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">GroupMemberCTAUS [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1332" xlink:to="lbl_RA1332" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1333" xlink:label="loc_RA1333"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1333" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">GroupMemberCTAUSY0 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1333" xlink:to="lbl_RA1333" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1335" xlink:label="loc_RA1335"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1335" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">GroupMemberCTAUSY0-1 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1335" xlink:to="lbl_RA1335" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1337" xlink:label="loc_RA1337"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1337" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">GroupMemberCTAUSY0-2 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1337" xlink:to="lbl_RA1337" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1339" xlink:label="loc_RA1339"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1339" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">GroupMemberCTAUSY0-3 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1339" xlink:to="lbl_RA1339" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1429" xlink:label="loc_RA1429"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1429" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">GroupMemberCTFGN [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1429" xlink:to="lbl_RA1429" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1334" xlink:label="loc_RA1334"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1334" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">GroupMemberCTFGNY0 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1334" xlink:to="lbl_RA1334" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1336" xlink:label="loc_RA1336"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1336" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">GroupMemberCTFGNY0-1 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1336" xlink:to="lbl_RA1336" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1338" xlink:label="loc_RA1338"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1338" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">GroupMemberCTFGNY0-2 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1338" xlink:to="lbl_RA1338" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1340" xlink:label="loc_RA1340"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1340" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">GroupMemberCTFGNY0-3 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1340" xlink:to="lbl_RA1340" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1313" xlink:label="loc_RA1313"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1313" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">RDS Lodge Request [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1313" xlink:to="lbl_RA1313" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1405" xlink:label="loc_RA1405"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1405" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1405" xlink:to="lbl_RA1405" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1317" xlink:label="loc_RA1317"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1317" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyCTAUS [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1317" xlink:to="lbl_RA1317" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1320" xlink:label="loc_RA1320"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1320" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyCTAUSC [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1320" xlink:to="lbl_RA1320" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1321" xlink:label="loc_RA1321"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1321" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyCTAUSS [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1321" xlink:to="lbl_RA1321" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1324" xlink:label="loc_RA1324"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1324" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyCTAUSY0 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1324" xlink:to="lbl_RA1324" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1326" xlink:label="loc_RA1326"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1326" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyCTAUSY0-1 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1326" xlink:to="lbl_RA1326" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1328" xlink:label="loc_RA1328"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1328" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyCTAUSY0-2 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1328" xlink:to="lbl_RA1328" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1330" xlink:label="loc_RA1330"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1330" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyCTAUSY0-3 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1330" xlink:to="lbl_RA1330" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1319" xlink:label="loc_RA1319"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1319" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyCTBSE [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1319" xlink:to="lbl_RA1319" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1318" xlink:label="loc_RA1318"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1318" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyCTFGN [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1318" xlink:to="lbl_RA1318" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1325" xlink:label="loc_RA1325"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1325" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyCTFGNY0 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1325" xlink:to="lbl_RA1325" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1327" xlink:label="loc_RA1327"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1327" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyCTFGNY0-1 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1327" xlink:to="lbl_RA1327" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1329" xlink:label="loc_RA1329"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyCTFGNY0-2 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1329" xlink:to="lbl_RA1329" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1331" xlink:label="loc_RA1331"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1331" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyCTFGNY0-3 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1331" xlink:to="lbl_RA1331" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1322" xlink:label="loc_RA1322"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1322" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyY0-1 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1322" xlink:to="lbl_RA1322" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rds.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1323" xlink:label="loc_RA1323"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1323" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingPartyY0-2 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1323" xlink:to="lbl_RA1323" order="1.0"/>
  </link:labelLink>
</link:linkbase>
