<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Disclaimer: http://www.sbr.gov.au/content/taxonomy_introduction_3_0.htm#Disclaimer -->
<!--Build # 284 - Publish generation of sbr_au_taxonomy. Generated Tuesday, 14 June 2011-->
<link:linkbase xmlns:link="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xbrli="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance">
    <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#businessDefinition"/>
    <link:labelLink xlink:type="extended" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/link">
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="RetailClass.02.00.data.xsd#DM374" xlink:label="loc_DM374"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DM374" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Retail Class</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DM374" xlink:to="lbl_DM374"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DM374" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This dimension categorises information reported under the internal ratings based approach to credit risk, based on the prescribed retail exposure classes, as determined in accordance with relevant prudential standards.

An exposure is categorised as a retail exposure if it is extended to an individual (that is, a natural person) or individuals and is part of a large pool of exposures that are managed by the ADI on a pooled basis and is not margin lending.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="RetailClass.02.00.data.xsd#DV4082" xlink:label="loc_DV4082"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DV4082" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Other Retail</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DV4082" xlink:to="lbl_DV4082"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DV4082" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The information reported is in relation to other retail exposures, as determined under the internal ratings-based (IRB) approach to credit risk in accordance with relevant prudential standards.

Other retails exposures represent those retail exposures which are not classified as any of the following:
- Qualifying revolving retail exposures;
- Retail exposures secured by housing (housing retail exposures); or
- Retail exposures with small- and medium-sized enterprises (SME exposures).

An exposure is categorised as a retail exposure if it is extended to an individual (that is, a natural person) or individuals and is part of a large pool of exposures that are managed by the ADI on a pooled basis and is not margin lending.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="RetailClass.02.00.data.xsd#DV4269" xlink:label="loc_DV4269"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DV4269" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Qualifying Revolving Retail</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DV4269" xlink:to="lbl_DV4269"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DV4269" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The information reported is in relation to qualifying revolving retail (QRR) exposures, as determined under the internal ratings-based (IRB) approach to credit risk in accordance with relevant prudential standards.

The following criteria must be satisfied for a sub-portfolio to be included in the QRR sub-asset class:
(i) the exposures are revolving, unsecured and unconditionally cancellable (both contractually and in practice) by the ADI. In this context, revolving exposures are defined as those where customers' outstanding balances are permitted to fluctuate based on their decisions to borrow and repay, up to a limit established by the ADI;
(ii) the exposures are to individuals and not explicitly for business purposes;
(iii) the maximum exposure of an individual account in the sub-portfoliois $100,000;
(iv) the ADI must demonstrate that the use of the QRR risk-weight function is limited to exposures that have exhibited, in comparison with other types of lending products, low loss rate volatility relative to the average level of loss rates (especially within low PD bands).
APRA will review the relative volatility of loss rates across relevant QRR sub-portfolios, as well as the aggregate of the QRR sub-asset class. Data on loss rates for the relevant QRR sub-portfolios and the QRR sub-asset class must be retained by the ADI in order to allow analysis of the volatility of loss rates; and
(v) the ADI is able to demonstrate to APRA that treatment of an exposure as a QRR exposure is consistent with the underlying risk characteristics of the sub-asset class.

An exposure is categorised as a retail exposure if it is extended to an individual (that is, a natural person) or individuals and is part of a large pool of exposures that are managed by the ADI on a pooled basis and is not margin lending.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="RetailClass.02.00.data.xsd#DV4084" xlink:label="loc_DV4084"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DV4084" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Residential Mortgages</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DV4084" xlink:to="lbl_DV4084"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DV4084" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The information reported is in relation to residential mortgage retail exposures, as determined under the internal ratings-based (IRB) approach to credit risk in accordance with relevant prudential standards.

Housing retail exposures represent retail exposures which are partly or fully secured by residential properties.

An exposure is categorised as a retail exposure if it is extended to an individual (that is, a natural person) or individuals and is part of a large pool of exposures that are managed by the ADI on a pooled basis and is not margin lending.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="RetailClass.02.00.data.xsd#DV4083" xlink:label="loc_DV4083"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DV4083" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">SME Retail</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DV4083" xlink:to="lbl_DV4083"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DV4083" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The information reported is in relation to retail exposures with small- and medium-sized enterprises (SME), as determined under the internal ratings-based (IRB) approach to credit risk in accordance with relevant prudential standards.

An exposure is categorised as a retail exposure if it is extended to an individual (that is, a natural person) or individuals and is part of a large pool of exposures that are managed by the ADI on a pooled basis and is not margin lending.

Small-business exposures (SME exposures), whether or not extended to an individual, may be treated as retail exposures if the ADI treats such exposures in its internal risk management systems in the same manner as other retail exposures consistently over time. This requires that such exposures are originated in a similar manner o other retail exposures. Furthermore, the exposure must not be managed individually in a way that is comparable to an exposure in the corporate IRB asset class but rather as part of a portfolio segment or pool of exposures with similar risk characteristics for purposes of risk assessment and quantification. This does not preclude these exposures from being managed individually at some stages of the risk management process. To be regarded as a retail exposure, the total business-related exposure of the consolidated banking group to a small-business obligor or group of connected small-business obligors must be less than $1 million. An ADI must have policies detailing the criteria that connect small-business obligors for this purpose. Small-business loans extended through, or guaranteed by, an individual are subject to the same exposure threshold.</link:label>
    </link:labelLink>
</link:linkbase>
