<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Disclaimer: http://www.sbr.gov.au/content/taxonomy_introduction_3_0.htm#Disclaimer -->
<link:linkbase xmlns:link="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xbrli="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance">
    <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#businessDefinition"/>
    <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#dataElementGuidance"/>
    <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.03.tech/dataElementStatus" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.03.xsd#dataElementStatus"/>
    <link:labelLink xlink:type="extended" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/link">
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.04.data.xsd#DE1679" xlink:label="loc_DE1679"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1679" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.03.tech/dataElementStatus" xml:lang="en">This element has been retired and should no longer be used.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE1679" xlink:to="lbl_DE1679"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1679" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The amount of the average total debt of the entity for the income year.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1679" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Average Balance Of Debt Total Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.04.data.xsd#DE2830" xlink:label="loc_DE2830"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2830" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.03.tech/dataElementStatus" xml:lang="en">This element has been retired and should no longer be used.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2830" xlink:to="lbl_DE2830"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2830" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">For interpretation/definition of this item refer to the Australian Accounting Standards, as an example, see provided reference</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2830" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Current Tax Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#bafpo1.02.05_bafpo1Abstract" xlink:label="loc_bafpo1.02.05_bafpo1Abstract"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_bafpo1Abstract" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Financial Position 1</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_bafpo1.02.05_bafpo1Abstract" xlink:to="lbl_bafpo1Abstract"/>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5765" xlink:label="loc_DE5765"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5765" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the increase in, or where applicable, the acquisition cost of, cash and liquid assets, during the relevant period.

For the purposes of this item, only report those amounts acquired, or initially recognised, during the relevant period. Where an asset is an amount held in a bank account, the value reported is the net of all movements in the account over the relevant period, but only where this net movement represents a net increase in the account's balance.

Assets are to be determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.

The acquisition cost, or historical cost, of an asset is the original cost paid to acquire the asset, at the date the asset was initially acquired. Where the asset was acquired in stages, sum the initial acquisition cost of each stage, but only to the extent the acquisitions occurred during the relevant period.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5765" xlink:to="lbl_DE5765"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5765" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Cash And Liquid Acquired Historical Cost Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5768" xlink:label="loc_DE5768"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5768" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the disposal proceeds arising from the decrease in cash and liquid assets during the relevant period.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5768" xlink:to="lbl_DE5768"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5768" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Cash And Liquid Disposal Proceeds Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5073" xlink:label="loc_DE5073"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5073" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value, as at the relevant date, of the assets of the relevant counterparty.

Assets are to be determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5073" xlink:to="lbl_DE5073"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5073" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Counterparty Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5058" xlink:label="loc_DE5058"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5058" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value or fair value of counterparty exposures to cash, after adjusting for derivatives.

An exposure to a counterparty or a group of related counterparties is the aggregate of all claims, commitments and contingent liabilities arising from on- and off-balance sheet transactions with the counterparty or group of related counterparties.

Off-balance sheet exposures refer to items that are not recognised in the statement of financial position of the reporting party, such as contingent assets and liabilities.

Where credit risk is unequivocally transferred to a third party by an irrevocable letter of credit or a direct guarantee, the exposure is to the third party.

Net market value or fair value, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5058" xlink:to="lbl_DE5058"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5058" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Exposures Cash Adjusted For Derivatives Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5550" xlink:label="loc_DE5550"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5550" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value or fair value of counterparty exposures to equity investment securities, after adjusting for derivatives. 

Equity investment securities are, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, contracts that evidence a residual interest in the assets of an entity after deducting all its liabilities, acquired with the intent to derive a gain either through an income stream or disposal.

An exposure to a counterparty or a group of related counterparties is the aggregate of all claims, commitments and contingent liabilities arising from on- and off-balance sheet transactions with the counterparty or group of related counterparties. An exposure includes an investment in an individual listed corporation or an individual property. It does not include an exposure to an asset class such as domestic equities, property, or an industry sector.

Exposures include claims and commitments of the entity recorded both on and off the balance sheet that are of the following nature:
(a) Credit exposures (i.e. such as a money market placement with a Bank or holding of a corporation's debt securities);
(b) Asset exposures that are not in the nature of a credit exposure (e.g. a direct property investment); and
(c) Exposures in the nature of a liability or obligation to a single party or group of related parties.

Off-balance sheet exposures refer to items that are not recognised in the statement of financial position of the reporting party, such as contingent assets and liabilities.

Where credit risk is unequivocally transferred to a third party by an irrevocable letter of credit or a direct guarantee, the exposure is to the third party.

Net market value or fair value, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5550" xlink:to="lbl_DE5550"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5550" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Exposures Equity Securities Adjusted For Derivatives Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4884" xlink:label="loc_DE4884"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4884" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the acquisition cost, or historical cost, of asset exposures, excluding those arising from contribution revenue. For the purposes of this item, only report those amounts acquired during the relevant period. Where an asset exposure is an amount held in a bank account, the value reported is the net of all movements in the account over the relevant period, but only where this net movement represents a net increase in the account's balance.

An asset exposure represents those assets or rights of an entity, recorded both on and off the balance sheet. 

An on-balance sheet exposure relates to those assets or rights recognised on the face of the balance sheet, or statement of financial position. An off-balance sheet exposure relates to those assets or rights that are not recognised on the face of the balance sheet, or statement of financial position, such as contingent assets, performance-related rights and guarantees.

Assets are to be determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.

The acquisition cost, or historical cost, of an asset is the original cost paid to acquire the asset, at the date the asset was initially acquired. Where the asset was acquired in stages, sum the initial acquisition cost of each stage, but only to the extent the acquisitions occurred during the relevant period.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4884" xlink:to="lbl_DE4884"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4884" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Exposures Excluding Contribution Revenue Acquisition Costs Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5252" xlink:label="loc_DE5252"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5252" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the proceeds received, or receivable, on the disposal of asset exposures, excluding those arising from contribution revenue. For the purposes of this item, only report those amounts received from disposals during the relevant period. Where an asset exposure is an amount held in a bank account, the value reported is the net of all movements in the account over the relevant period, but only where this net movement represents a net decrease in the account's balance.

An asset exposure represents those assets or rights of an entity, recorded both on and off the balance sheet. 

An on-balance sheet exposure relates to those assets or rights recognised on the face of the balance sheet, or statement of financial position. An off-balance sheet exposure relates to those assets or rights that are not recognised on the face of the balance sheet, or statement of financial position, such as contingent assets, performance-related rights and guarantees.

Assets are to be determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.

The disposal of an asset exposure represents a change in ownership of that asset, whether because of some act or event, or by operation of law. Proceeds are calculated as the total consideration received, or receivable, by the reporting party arising from the change in ownership of that asset, but only to the extent the change occured during the relevant period.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5252" xlink:to="lbl_DE5252"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5252" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Exposures Excluding Contribution Revenue Disposal Proceeds Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5448" xlink:label="loc_DE5448"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5448" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net of acquisition costs incurred and disposal proceeds received, or receivable, on the acquisition and disposal of asset exposures during the relevant period. For the purposes of this item, exclude exposures arising from contribution revenue. Where an asset exposure is an amount held in a bank account, the value reported is the net of all movements in the account over the relevant period.

An asset exposure represents those assets or rights of an entity, recorded both on and off the balance sheet. 

An on-balance sheet exposure relates to those assets or rights recognised on the face of the balance sheet, or statement of financial position. An off-balance sheet exposure relates to those assets or rights that are not recognised on the face of the balance sheet, or statement of financial position, such as contingent assets, performance-related rights and guarantees.

Assets are to be determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.

The acquisition cost, or historical cost, of an asset is the original cost paid to acquire the asset, at the date the asset was initially acquired. Where the asset was acquired in stages, sum the initial acquisition cost of each stage, but only to the extent the acquisitions occurred during the relevant period.

The disposal of an asset represents a change in ownership of that asset, whether because of some act or event, or by operation of law. Proceeds are calculated as the total consideration received, or receivable, by the reporting party arising from the change in ownership of that asset, but only to the extent the change occured during the relevant period.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5448" xlink:to="lbl_DE5448"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5448" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Exposures Excluding Contribution Revenue Net Acquisition Disposal Transactions Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4534" xlink:label="loc_DE4534"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4534" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value, or fair value, of asset exposures, excluding contribution revenue received or receivable.

An asset exposure represents those assets or rights of an entity, recorded both on and off the balance sheet. 

An on-balance sheet exposure relates to those assets or rights recognised on the face of the balance sheet, or statement of financial position. An off-balance sheet exposure relates to those assets or rights that are not recognised on the face of the balance sheet, or statement of financial position, such as contingent assets, performance-related rights and guarantees.

Assets, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, are resources:
(a) controlled by an entity as a result of past events; and
(b) from which future economic benefits are expected to flow to the entity.

Net market value or fair value is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4534" xlink:to="lbl_DE4534"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4534" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Exposures Excluding Contribution Revenue Net Market Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4892" xlink:label="loc_DE4892"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4892" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value or fair value of counterparty exposures to indexed interest bearing securities, after adjusting for derivatives. 

Indexed securities pay an income stream that is dependent upon an external factor.

Interest bearing securities are debt securities paying an income stream based upon an interest rate consistent with the classification and measurement basis used for investment securities in accordance with the accounting standards.

An exposure to a counterparty or a group of related counterparties is the aggregate of all claims, commitments and contingent liabilities arising from on-
and off-balance sheet transactions with the counterparty or group of related counterparties. An exposure includes an investment in an individual listed corporation or an individual property. It does not include an exposure to an asset class such as domestic equities, property, or an industry sector.

Exposures include claims and commitments of the entity recorded both on and off the balance sheet that are of the following nature:
(a) Credit exposures (i.e. such as a money market placement with a Bank or holding of a corporation's debt securities);
(b) Asset exposures that are not in the nature of a credit exposure (e.g. a direct property investment); and
(c) Exposures in the nature of a liability or obligation to a single party or group of related parties.

Off-balance sheet exposures refer to items that are not recognised in the statement of financial position of the reporting party, such as contingent assets and liabilities.

Where credit risk is unequivocally transferred to a third party by an irrevocable letter of credit or a direct guarantee, the exposure is to the third party.

Net market value or fair value, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4892" xlink:to="lbl_DE4892"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4892" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Exposures Indexed Interest Bearing Securities Adjusted For Derivatives Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5592" xlink:label="loc_DE5592"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5592" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value or fair value of counterparty exposures to other investment assets, after adjusting for derivatives. 

Other investment assets represent those which are required to be reported on APRA form LRF_220_0.

An exposure to a counterparty or a group of related counterparties is the aggregate of all claims, commitments and contingent liabilities arising from on- and off-balance sheet transactions with the counterparty or group of related counterparties. An exposure includes an investment in an individual listed corporation or an individual property. It does not include an exposure to an asset class such as domestic equities, property, or an industry sector.

Exposures include claims and commitments of the entity recorded both on and off the balance sheet that are of the following nature:
(a) Credit exposures (i.e. such as a money market placement with a Bank or holding of a corporation's debt securities);
(b) Asset exposures that are not in the nature of a credit exposure (e.g. a direct property investment); and
(c) Exposures in the nature of a liability or obligation to a single party or group of related parties.

Off-balance sheet exposures refer to items that are not recognised in the statement of financial position of the reporting party, such as contingent assets and liabilities.

Where credit risk is unequivocally transferred to a third party by an irrevocable letter of credit or a direct guarantee, the exposure is to the third party.

Net market value or fair value, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5592" xlink:to="lbl_DE5592"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5592" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Exposures Investment Assets Other LRF 220 0 Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5294" xlink:label="loc_DE5294"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5294" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value or fair value of counterparty exposures to investment property, after adjusting for derivatives.

Property investments are holdings of property acquired with the intent to derive a gain either through an income stream or disposal. This  includes investments in property by way of units in property trusts or other indirect investment methods as well as investments in real property (land and buildings).

An exposure to a counterparty or a group of related counterparties is the aggregate of all claims, commitments and contingent liabilities arising from on- and off-balance sheet transactions with the counterparty or group of related counterparties. An exposure includes an investment in an individual listed corporation or an individual property. It does not include an exposure to an asset class such as domestic equities, property, or an industry sector.

Exposures include claims and commitments of the entity recorded both on and off the balance sheet that are of the following nature:
(a) Asset exposures that are not in the nature of a credit exposure (e.g. a direct property investment); and
(b) Exposures in the nature of a liability or obligation to a single party or group of related parties.

Off-balance sheet exposures refer to items that are not recognised in the statement of financial position of the reporting party, such as contingent assets and liabilities.

Where credit risk is unequivocally transferred to a third party by an irrevocable letter of credit or a direct guarantee, the exposure is to the third party.

Net market value or fair value, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5294" xlink:to="lbl_DE5294"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5294" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Exposures Investment Property Adjusted For Derivatives Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5002" xlink:label="loc_DE5002"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5002" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value or fair value of counterparty exposures to loans, after adjusting for derivatives. 

An exposure to a counterparty or a group of related counterparties is the aggregate of all claims, commitments and contingent liabilities arising from on- and off-balance sheet transactions with the counterparty or group of related counterparties. An exposure includes an investment in an individual listed corporation or an individual property. It does not include an exposure to an asset class such as domestic equities, property, or an industry sector.

Exposures include claims and commitments of the entity recorded both on and off the balance sheet that are of the following nature:
(a) Credit exposures (i.e. such as a money market placement with a Bank or holding of a corporation's debt securities); and
(b) Exposures in the nature of a liability or obligation to a single party or group of related parties.

Off-balance sheet exposures refer to items that are not recognised in the statement of financial position of the reporting party, such as contingent assets and liabilities.

Where credit risk is unequivocally transferred to a third party by an irrevocable letter of credit or a direct guarantee, the exposure is to the third party.

Net market value or fair value, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5002" xlink:to="lbl_DE5002"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5002" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Exposures Loans Adjusted For Derivatives Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5203" xlink:label="loc_DE5203"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5203" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value or fair value of counterparty exposures to non indexed interest bearing securities, after adjusting for derivatives. 

Non-indexed securities pay an income stream that is not dependent upon any external factor.

Interest bearing securities are debt securities paying an income stream based upon an interest rate consistent with the classification and measurement basis used for investment securities in accordance with the accounting standards.

An exposure to a counterparty or a group of related counterparties is the aggregate of all claims, commitments and contingent liabilities arising from on- and off-balance sheet transactions with the counterparty or group of related counterparties. An exposure includes an investment in an individual listed corporation or an individual property. It does not include an exposure to an asset class such as domestic equities, property, or an industry sector.

Exposures include claims and commitments of the entity recorded both on and off the balance sheet that are of the following nature:
(a) Credit exposures (i.e. such as a money market placement with a Bank or holding of a corporation's debt securities);
(b) Asset exposures that are not in the nature of a credit exposure (e.g. a direct property investment); and
(c) Exposures in the nature of a liability or obligation to a single party or group of related parties.

Off-balance sheet exposures refer to items that are not recognised in the statement of financial position of the reporting party, such as contingent assets and liabilities.

Where credit risk is unequivocally transferred to a third party by an irrevocable letter of credit or a direct guarantee, the exposure is to the third party.

Net market value or fair value, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5203" xlink:to="lbl_DE5203"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5203" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Exposures Non Indexed Interest Bearing Securities Adjusted For Derivatives Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5251" xlink:label="loc_DE5251"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5251" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value or fair value of counterparty exposures to other non investment assets, after adjusting for derivatives. 

Other non investment assets are those which are required to be reported on APRA form LRF_220_0.

An exposure to a counterparty or a group of related counterparties is the aggregate of all claims, commitments and contingent liabilities arising from on-
and off-balance sheet transactions with the counterparty or group of related counterparties. An exposure includes an investment in an individual listed corporation or an individual property. It does not include an exposure to an asset class such as domestic equities, property, or an industry sector.

Exposures include claims and commitments of the entity recorded both on and off the balance sheet that are of the following nature:
(a) Credit exposures (i.e. such as a money market placement with a Bank or holding of a corporation's debt securities);
(b) Asset exposures that are not in the nature of a credit exposure (e.g. a direct property investment); and
(c) Exposures in the nature of a liability or obligation to a single party or group of related parties.

Off-balance sheet exposures refer to items that are not recognised in the statement of financial position of the reporting party, such as contingent assets and liabilities.

Where credit risk is unequivocally transferred to a third party by an irrevocable letter of credit or a direct guarantee, the exposure is to the third party.

Net market value or fair value, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5251" xlink:to="lbl_DE5251"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5251" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Exposures Non Investment Assets Other LRF 220 0 Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4902" xlink:label="loc_DE4902"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4902" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value or fair value of counterparty exposures to receivables, after adjusting for derivatives. 

An exposure to a counterparty or a group of related counterparties is the aggregate of all claims, commitments and contingent liabilities arising from on- and off-balance sheet transactions with the counterparty or group of related counterparties. An exposure includes an investment in an individual listed corporation or an individual property. It does not include an exposure to an asset class such as domestic equities, property, or an industry sector.

Exposures include claims and commitments of the entity recorded both on and off the balance sheet that are of the following nature:
(a) Credit exposures (i.e. such as a money market placement with a Bank or holding of a corporation's debt securities); and
(b) Exposures in the nature of a liability or obligation to a single party or group of related parties.

Off-balance sheet exposures refer to items that are not recognised in the statement of financial position of the reporting party, such as contingent assets and liabilities.

Where credit risk is unequivocally transferred to a third party by an irrevocable letter of credit or a direct guarantee, the exposure is to the third party.

Net market value or fair value, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4902" xlink:to="lbl_DE4902"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4902" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Exposures Receivables Adjusted For Derivatives Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4505" xlink:label="loc_DE4505"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4505" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value, or fair value, of in-house assets, as determined in accordance with relevant superannuation legislation.
     
In-house assets held on 11 August 1999, which have been grandfathered, may be excluded from this item.
     
In-house assets are generally limited to 5% of the market value of an entity's assets. The following should not be reported at this item:
- In-house assets, for which the entity has an exemption; and
- An investment in, or loan to, a related party or trust which falls under one of the exclusion categories listed under the relevant superannuation legislation.

Net market value, or fair value, is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4505" xlink:to="lbl_DE4505"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4505" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets In House Assets Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4071" xlink:label="loc_DE4071"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4071" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is a balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

Report, the net market value, or fair value, plus the value of accrued income, of any asset that has been classified as an investment asset, other than:
- Cash;
- Property;
- Equities;
- Interest bearing securities; or
- Loans

Net market value, or fair value, is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4071" xlink:to="lbl_DE4071"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4071" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Investment Including Accrued Income Other Net Market Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5494" xlink:label="loc_DE5494"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5494" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is a balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

Report the net market value, or fair value, of any other non investment asset which cannot be classified elsewhere within the list of assets backing policy liabilities on LRF_420_0.

Net market value, or fair value, is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5494" xlink:to="lbl_DE5494"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5494" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Non Investment Other LRF420 Net Market Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4572" xlink:label="loc_DE4572"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4572" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is a balancing item.

Report the net market value, or fair value, of any asset that has not been classified as an investment asset, other than 
- receivables
- deferred tax
- property; or
- gross policy liabilities ceded under reinsurance

Net market value, or fair value, is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4572" xlink:to="lbl_DE4572"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4572" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Non Investment Other Other Net Market Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4516" xlink:label="loc_DE4516"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4516" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is a balancing item.

Report the net market value, or fair value, of any asset that has not been classified as an investment asset, other than receivables

Net market value, or fair value, is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4516" xlink:to="lbl_DE4516"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4516" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Non Investment Other Than Receivables1 Net Market Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4390" xlink:label="loc_DE4390"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4390" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value of gross policy liabilities ceded under outwards reinsurance.

This amount includes insurance liabilities, financial instrument liabilities and management services element liabilities ceded under reinsurance.

Reinsurance contracts as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, are insurance contracts issued by one insurer (the reinsurer) to compensate another insurer (the cedent) for losses on one or more contracts issued by the cedent.

Outwards Reinsurance that meets the definition of an insurance contract consists of both a Reinsured Best Estimate Liability and the Value of Reinsured Profit Margins.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4390" xlink:to="lbl_DE4390"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4390" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Policy Liabilities Ceded Under Reinsurance Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5233" xlink:label="loc_DE5233"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5233" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value of property plant and equipment held by the reporting party as at the relevant date in accordance  with the classification and measurement basis defined by the accounting standards. This item excludes all Information technology costs, both tangible and intangible.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5233" xlink:to="lbl_DE5233"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5233" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Property Plant And Equipment Excluding IT Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5397" xlink:label="loc_DE5397"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5397" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The value to be reported is the net market value, or fair value, of holdings of real estate property, plus income accrued but not received in relation to this asset. This method of disclosure differs from the Australian Accounting Standards.

Net market value, or fair value, is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5397" xlink:to="lbl_DE5397"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5397" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Real Estate Property Plus Accrued Income Net Market Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4391" xlink:label="loc_DE4391"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4391" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

The value to be reported is the net market value, or fair value, of receivables other than:
- outstanding insurance premiums
- receivables in relation to investment assets
- income accrued
- deferred acquisition costs 

Acquisition costs, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, are the fixed and variable costs of acquiring new business including commissions and similar distribution costs, and costs of accepting, issuing and initially recording policies. (Acquisition costs relate to the costs incurred in acquiring specific life insurance contracts during the relevant period. They do not include the general growth and development costs incurred by a life insurer.)

Net market value, or fair value, is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4391" xlink:to="lbl_DE4391"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4391" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Receivables Other Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4294" xlink:label="loc_DE4294"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4294" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value of assets held in respect of standard employer sponsored business.

The value of the assets held in respect of standard employer-sponsored business' is the aggregate balance of the accounts of those members in the fund who joined the fund wholly or partly through an arrangement between the trustee of the regulated superannuation fund (including public offer funds) and each of the standard employer-sponsors which contribute to that fund.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4294" xlink:to="lbl_DE4294"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4294" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Standard Employer Sponsored Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5306" xlink:label="loc_DE5306"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5306" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value, or fair value, of the reporting party's assets, excluding deferred acquisition costs arising in respect of policies. This method of disclosure differs from the Australian Accounting Standards.

An asset is, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, a resource: (a) controlled by an entity as a result of past events; and (b) from which future economic benefits are expected to flow to the entity.

Acquisition costs, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, are the fixed and variable costs of acquiring new business including commissions and similar distribution costs, and costs of accepting, issuing and initially recording policies. (Acquisition costs relate to the costs incurred in acquiring specific life insurance contracts during the relevant period. They do not include the general growth and development costs incurred by a life insurer.)

Net market value, or fair value, is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5306" xlink:to="lbl_DE5306"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5306" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Total Excluding Deferred Acquisition Costs Net Market Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4989" xlink:label="loc_DE4989"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4989" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net value of all acquisition and disposal transactions, during the relevant period, of trade and other receivables. These transactions involve the exchange of valuable consideration between counterparties. Where this results in a net decrease in the net market value of assets, then report a negative figure.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4989" xlink:to="lbl_DE4989"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4989" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Trade And Other Receivables Net Acquisition Disposal Transactions Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5528" xlink:label="loc_DE5528"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5528" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the decrease in the value of trade and other receivables arising from the receipt of monies or consideration from the entity's debtors during the relevant period.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5528" xlink:to="lbl_DE5528"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5528" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Trade And Other Receivables Receipts Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4448" xlink:label="loc_DE4448"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4448" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the historical value of trade and other receivables arising from the sale or exchange of goods and services to the entity's debtors, or from other non-investment activities.

For the purposes of this item, only report those amounts acquired, or initially recognised, during the relevant period.

This item is to be determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4448" xlink:to="lbl_DE4448"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4448" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Trade And Other Receivables Recognised Historical Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE2408" xlink:label="loc_DE2408"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2408" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value, as at the reporting date, of Goods and Services Tax (GST) that is receivable on purchases, as determined in accordance with the Goods and Services Tax Act 1999.

GST is a tax on the supply of most goods and services and other taxable supplies (for example, real property and rights) in Australia, including things that are imported. In most cases it does not apply to exports of goods or services, and other things consumed outside Australia. It is similar to 'value-added taxes' applying in other countries. The GST is a multi-stage tax, that is, GST is paid at each stage of the supply chain. Liability for this tax rests on the supplier.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2408" xlink:to="lbl_DE2408"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2408" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Trade and Receivables Goods And Services Tax Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5578" xlink:label="loc_DE5578"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5578" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value, as at the relevant date, of the total equity components that make up net assets as calculated by the Life Insurance Act 1995. This amount is not necessarily equal to net assets per the entity's general purpose accounts.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5578" xlink:to="lbl_DE5578"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5578" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Equity Calculated Life Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE2061" xlink:label="loc_DE2061"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2061" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">This item relates to defined benefit superannuation entities. The excess/deficiency of assets available for use for a defined benefit superannuation entity will be determined by an actuary when a formal valuation is conducted. Accordingly for a defined benefit superannuation entity, only complete this item where this is applicable and is determined by an actuarial review.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2061" xlink:to="lbl_DE2061"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2061" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Equity Excess Or Deficiency Of Assets Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE2060" xlink:label="loc_DE2060"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2060" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Report value of members' accrued benefits as at the reporting date. This is to be determined in accordance with the requirements of current Australian Accounting Standards. Accumulation/defined contribution superannuation entities The liability for accrued benefits for a defined contribution superannuation entity is the superannuation entity's present obligation to pay benefits to members and beneficiaries in the future and is calculated as the difference between the carrying amounts of the assets and the carrying amounts of the liabilities and reserves as at the reporting date. Defined benefit superannuation entities Accrued benefits of a defined benefit superannuation entity shall be measured, using actuarial assumptions and valuations where appropriate, as the present value of expected future payments to members arising from membership of the superannuation entity up to the measurement date. In absence of formal actuarial review, the amount is calculated as the difference between the carrying amounts of the assets and the carrying amounts of the liabilities as at the reporting date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2060" xlink:to="lbl_DE2060"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2060" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Equity Liability For Allocated Accrued Benefits Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4697" xlink:label="loc_DE4697"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4697" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value of the difference between retained profits as determined in accordance with the Life Insurance Act and retained profits determined in accordance with accounting standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4697" xlink:to="lbl_DE4697"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4697" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Equity Life Act Reconciling Adjustments Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5343" xlink:label="loc_DE5343"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5343" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value, as at the relevant date, of the net assets of the relevant counterparty, measured at fair value. This fair value of net assets may not necessarily equal the amount of assets less the amount of liabilities. For example, if the party was a listed entity, then the fair value of net assets may be based on the market value of the entity's shares.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5343" xlink:to="lbl_DE5343"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5343" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Equity Net Assets Fair Value Counterparty Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4915" xlink:label="loc_DE4915"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4915" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value, as at the relevant date, of net assets as calculated by the Life Insurance Act 1995. This amount is not necessarily equal to net assets per the entity's general purpose accounts.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4915" xlink:to="lbl_DE4915"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4915" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Equity Net Assets Life Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4674" xlink:label="loc_DE4674"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4674" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the total reconcilliation adjustment between net assets as per general purpose accounts and the net as per the Life Act.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4674" xlink:to="lbl_DE4674"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4674" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Equity Reconciliation Adjustment Other Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4539" xlink:label="loc_DE4539"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4539" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value of Shareholder retained profits as calculated in accordance with the requirements of this form.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4539" xlink:to="lbl_DE4539"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4539" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Equity Retained Profits As Calculated Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5225" xlink:label="loc_DE5225"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5225" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is a subtotal item within the list in which it is being used. It relates to the total of all transfers into or out of retained profits other than those related to operating profit of the reporting party or Provisions for Bonuses to Participating Policy Owners as determined in accordance with the instructions for APRA form LRF340.1.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5225" xlink:to="lbl_DE5225"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5225" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Equity Transfers Other Total LRF340 Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5235" xlink:label="loc_DE5235"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5235" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the face value, or principle value, of liabilities incurred during the relevant period that are classified as administration fees.

Adminitstration Fees are typically amounts payable to an entity for performing required administration activities.

The face value or principle value of a liability represents the amount that an issuer agrees to pay at the maturity date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5235" xlink:to="lbl_DE5235"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5235" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Administration Fees Incurred Face Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5501" xlink:label="loc_DE5501"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5501" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the net of all incurrance and settlement transactions, during the relevant period, of administration fees payable .

Adminitstration Fees are typically amounts payable to an entity for performing required administration activities.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5501" xlink:to="lbl_DE5501"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5501" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Administration Fees Net Incurrence Settlement Transactions Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4759" xlink:label="loc_DE4759"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4759" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the net market value, or fair value, of Adminitstration Fees payable.

Adminitstration Fees are typically amounts payable to an entity for performing required administration activities.

Net market value or fair value is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of a liability in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4759" xlink:to="lbl_DE4759"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4759" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Administration Fees Payable Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5244" xlink:label="loc_DE5244"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5244" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the amount paid during the relevant period to settle liabilities classified as administration fees.

Adminitstration Fees are typically amounts payable to an entity for performing required administration activities.

The settlement of a liability takes place when all legal or constructive obligations are eliminated.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5244" xlink:to="lbl_DE5244"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5244" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Administration Fees Settlement Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4760" xlink:label="loc_DE4760"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4760" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the net market value, or fair value, of audit and tax agent fees payable.

Audit and tax agent fees are typically amounts payable to an entity for performing agreed assurance and taxation services.

Net market value or fair value is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of a liability in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4760" xlink:to="lbl_DE4760"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4760" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Audit Taxation Fees Payable Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5192" xlink:label="loc_DE5192"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5192" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the face value, or principle value, of liabilities incurred during the relevant period that are classified as audit and tax agent fees.

Audit and tax agent fees are typically amounts payable to an entity for performing agreed assurance and taxation services.

The face value or principle value of a liability represents the amount that an issuer agrees to pay at the maturity date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5192" xlink:to="lbl_DE5192"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5192" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Audit Tax Fees Incurred Face Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5726" xlink:label="loc_DE5726"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5726" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the net of all incurrance and settlement transactions, during the relevant period, of audit and tax agent fees payable.

Audit and tax agent fees are typically amounts payable to an entity for performing agreed assurance and taxation services.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5726" xlink:to="lbl_DE5726"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5726" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Audit Tax Fees Net Incurrence Settlement Transactions Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5210" xlink:label="loc_DE5210"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5210" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the amount paid during the relevant period to settle liabilities classified as audit and tax agent fees.

Audit and tax agent fees are typically amounts payable to an entity for performing agreed assurance and taxation services.

The settlement of a liability takes place when all legal or constructive obligations are eliminated.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5210" xlink:to="lbl_DE5210"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5210" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Audit Tax Fees Settlement Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5374" xlink:label="loc_DE5374"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5374" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value, as at the relevant date, of bill acceptance and discount facilities provided to the reporting party. For the purposes of this item, report the total approved balance of the facility.

Bill acceptance and discount facilities are a form of liquidity, or funding, provided to entity through a facility that discounts bills (e.g. bank accepted bills). Principal and interest (discount) owing on the bill is repaid or 'rolled over' by the reporting party on maturity of the bill.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5374" xlink:to="lbl_DE5374"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5374" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Bill Acceptance Discount Facilities Available Approved Limit Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4233" xlink:label="loc_DE4233"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4233" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value, or fair value, of borrowings, including overdrafts. This method of disclosure differs from the Australian Accounting Standards.

Borrowings are amounts of money on loan from financial institutions or other creditors with the promise or understanding that it will be repaid.

Net market value, or fair value, is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4233" xlink:to="lbl_DE4233"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4233" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Borrowings Including Overdrafts Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4678" xlink:label="loc_DE4678"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4678" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the hedging adjustment required to translate the aggregate borrowings balance to the effective post-derivatives position. 

A hedging adjustment represents the adjustment required to translate the effective exposure associated with hedging investments. The purpose of a hedging investment is to offset the risk of changes in the fair value or investment cash flows of another contract.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4678" xlink:to="lbl_DE4678"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4678" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Borrowings Including Overdrafts Adjustment Hedging Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4702" xlink:label="loc_DE4702"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4702" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the look-through adjustment for borrowings held indirectly via listed unit trusts, unlisted unit trusts or controlled unit trusts.

A look through adjustment item represents the adjustment required to convert effective holdings in investments via trusts from aggregated amounts classified as other investment assets or unit trusts to the appropriate categories on a look-through basis.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4702" xlink:to="lbl_DE4702"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4702" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Borrowings Including Overdrafts Adjustment Look Through Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4232" xlink:label="loc_DE4232"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4232" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The value to be reported is the net market value, or fair value, of borrowings, plus overdrafts less any borrowings classified as seed capital. This method of disclosure differs from the Australian Accounting Standards.

Borrowings are amounts of money on loan from financial institutions or other creditors with the promise or understanding that it will be repaid.

Seed capital is the preliminary contribution of funding toward the financing of a new business. Commonly this is in the form of a loan, usually provided by a related entity.

Net market value, or fair value, is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4232" xlink:to="lbl_DE4232"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4232" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Borrowings Including Overdrafts Excluding Seed Capital Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5014" xlink:label="loc_DE5014"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5014" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the face value, or principle value, of borrowings incurred during the relevant period.. 

Borrowings are generally amounts of money on loan from financial institutions or other creditors with the promise or understanding that it will be repaid.

The face value or principle value of a liability represents the amount that an issuer agrees to pay at the maturity date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5014" xlink:to="lbl_DE5014"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5014" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Borrowings Incurred Face Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5031" xlink:label="loc_DE5031"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5031" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the net of all incurrance and settlement transactions, during the relevant period, relating to borrowings payable.

Borrowings are generally amounts of money on loan from financial institutions or other creditors with the promise or understanding that it will be repaid.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5031" xlink:to="lbl_DE5031"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5031" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Borrowings Net Incurrence Settlement Transactions Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4831" xlink:label="loc_DE4831"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4831" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The value to be reported is the net market value, or fair value, of borrowings classified as seed capital. 

Seed capital is the preliminary contribution of funding toward the financing of a new business. Commonly this is in the form of a loan, usually provided by a related entity.

Borrowings are amounts of money on loan from financial institutions or other creditors with the promise or understanding that it will be repaid.

Net market value, or fair value, is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4831" xlink:to="lbl_DE4831"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4831" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Borrowings Seed Capital Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4982" xlink:label="loc_DE4982"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4982" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the amount paid during the relevant period to settle liabilities, claims and obligations classified as borrowings.

Borrowings are generally amounts of money on loan from financial institutions or other creditors with the promise or understanding that it will be repaid.

The settlement of a liability, claim or obligation takes place when all legal or constructive obligations are eliminated.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4982" xlink:to="lbl_DE4982"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4982" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Borrowings Settlement Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE2762" xlink:label="loc_DE2762"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2762" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Endorsement of a bill of exchange creates a contingent liability by the endorser to pay out the funds conditional on the bearer/holder demanding payment.
Bills of exchange that have been endorsed and sold and are not in an Registered Financial Corporation's asset portfolio are included in this Memo item.
Bills of exchange that have been endorsed and held in an Registered Financial Corporation's asset portfolio are included in the Statement of Financial Position under either Trading Securities or Investment Securities.
Only endorsed bills where this entity is the first endorser of a non-Australian Deposit-taking Institutions or Registered Financial Corporations accepted bill should be included.
Include only these counterparties:
- private trading corporations;
- government non-financial corporations;
- insurance corporations;
- financial auxiliaries and other financial intermediaries; and
- individuals, private unincorporated businesses, and Community Service Organisations.
Exclude:
- bills of exchange accepted and then sold by the institution (these appear in acceptances); and
- bills of exchange neither accepted nor endorsed.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2762" xlink:to="lbl_DE2762"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2762" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Contingent Liabilities Arising From Bill Endorsements Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4900" xlink:label="loc_DE4900"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4900" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value, as at the relevant date, of the liabilities of the relevant counterparty.

Liabilities are to be determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4900" xlink:to="lbl_DE4900"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4900" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Counterparty Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5679" xlink:label="loc_DE5679"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5679" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the face value, or principle value, of liabilities incurred during the relevant period

Liabilities, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, are present obligations of the entity arising from past events, the settlement of which is expected to result in an outflow from the entity of resources embodying economic benefits.

The face value or principle value of a liability represents the amount that an issuer agrees to pay at the maturity date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5679" xlink:to="lbl_DE5679"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5679" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Face Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5402" xlink:label="loc_DE5402"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5402" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the face value, or principle value, of liabilities incurred during the relevant period that are classified as investment fees.

Investment fees are typically amounts payable to an entity that arise as a result of investing activities undertaken.

The face value or principle value of a liability represents the amount that an issuer agrees to pay at the maturity date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5402" xlink:to="lbl_DE5402"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5402" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Investment Fees Incurred Face Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5477" xlink:label="loc_DE5477"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5477" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the net of all incurrance and settlement transactions, during the relevant period, of investment fees payable.

Investment fees are typically amounts payable to an entity that arise as a result of investing activities undertaken.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5477" xlink:to="lbl_DE5477"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5477" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Investment Fees Net Incurrence Settlement Transactions Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4789" xlink:label="loc_DE4789"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4789" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the net market value, or fair value, of investment fees payable.

Investment fees are typically amounts payable to an entity that arise as a result of investing activities undertaken.

Net market value or fair value is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of a liability in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4789" xlink:to="lbl_DE4789"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4789" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Investment Fees Payable Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5310" xlink:label="loc_DE5310"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5310" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the amount paid during the relevant period to settle liabilities classified as investment fees.

Investment fees are typically amounts payable to an entity that arise as a result of investing activities undertaken.

The settlement of a liability takes place when all legal or constructive obligations are eliminated.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5310" xlink:to="lbl_DE5310"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5310" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Investment Fees Settlement Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4974" xlink:label="loc_DE4974"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4974" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value, as at the relevant date, of letter of credit facilities committed to by the reporting party. For the purposes of this item, report the total approved balance of the facility.

A letter of credit facility is an irrevocable and unconditional undertaking to repay the principal and interest of a loan in the event of default.

The approved balance of a facility is the maximum approved amount that can be drawn down in relation to that facility.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4974" xlink:to="lbl_DE4974"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4974" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Letter Of Credit Facilities Available Approved Limit Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5516" xlink:label="loc_DE5516"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5516" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the face value, or principle value, of liabilities incurred during the relevant period that are classified as management fees.

Management Fees are typically amounts payable to an entity for performing agreed management activities.

The face value or principle value of a liability represents the amount that an issuer agrees to pay at the maturity date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5516" xlink:to="lbl_DE5516"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5516" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Management Fees Incurred Face Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5692" xlink:label="loc_DE5692"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5692" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the net of all incurrance and settlement transactions, during the relevant period, of management fees payable .

Management Fees are typically amounts payable to an entity for performing agreed management activities.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5692" xlink:to="lbl_DE5692"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5692" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Management Fees Net Incurrence Settlement Transactions Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4655" xlink:label="loc_DE4655"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4655" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the net market value, or fair value, of the Management Fees payable.

Management Fees are typically amounts payable to an entity for performing agreed management activities.

Net market value or fair value is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of a liability in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4655" xlink:to="lbl_DE4655"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4655" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Management Fees Payable Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5786" xlink:label="loc_DE5786"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5786" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the amount paid during the relevant period to settle liabilities, claims and obligations classified as Management Fees.

Management Fees are typically amounts payable to an entity for performing agreed management activities.

The settlement of a liability, claim or obligation takes place when all legal or constructive obligations are eliminated.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5786" xlink:to="lbl_DE5786"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5786" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Management Fees Settlement Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5632" xlink:label="loc_DE5632"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5632" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the face value, or principle value, of liabilities incurred during the relevant period that are classified as member benefits.

This is to be determined in accordance with the requirements of current Australian Accounting Standards. 

Accumulation/defined contributions: 
The liability for accrued benefits for a defined contribution plan is the entity's present obligation to pay benefits to members and beneficiaries in the future and is calculated as the difference between the carrying amounts of the assets and the carrying amounts of the liabilities as at the relevant date. 

Defined benefits:
Accrued benefits of a defined benefit plan shall be measured, using actuarial assumptions and valuations where appropriate, as the present value of expected future payments to members arising from membership of the entity up to the measurement date. In absence of formal actuarial review, the amount is calculated as the difference between the carrying amounts of the assets and the carrying amounts of the liabilities as at the relevant date.

The face value or principle value of a liability represents the amount that an issuer agrees to pay at the maturity date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5632" xlink:to="lbl_DE5632"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5632" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Member Benefits Incurred Face Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4990" xlink:label="loc_DE4990"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4990" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the net of all incurrance and settlement transactions, during the relevant period, relating to member benefits payable.

This is to be determined in accordance with the requirements of current Australian Accounting Standards. 

Accumulation/defined contributions: 
The liability for accrued benefits for a defined contribution plan is the entity's present obligation to pay benefits to members and beneficiaries in the future and is calculated as the difference between the carrying amounts of the assets and the carrying amounts of the liabilities as at the relevant date. 

Defined benefits:
Accrued benefits of a defined benefit plan shall be measured, using actuarial assumptions and valuations where appropriate, as the present value of expected future payments to members arising from membership of the entity up to the measurement date. In absence of formal actuarial review, the amount is calculated as the difference between the carrying amounts of the assets and the carrying amounts of the liabilities as at the relevant date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4990" xlink:to="lbl_DE4990"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4990" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Member Benefits Payable Net Incurrence Settlement Transactions Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5024" xlink:label="loc_DE5024"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5024" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the amount paid during the relevant period to settle liabilities, claims and obligations classified as member benefits.

This is to be determined in accordance with the requirements of current Australian Accounting Standards. 

Accumulation/defined contributions: 
The liability for accrued benefits for a defined contribution plan is the entity's present obligation to pay benefits to members and beneficiaries in the future and is calculated as the difference between the carrying amounts of the assets and the carrying amounts of the liabilities as at the relevant date. 

Defined benefits:
Accrued benefits of a defined benefit plan shall be measured, using actuarial assumptions and valuations where appropriate, as the present value of expected future payments to members arising from membership of the entity up to the measurement date. In absence of formal actuarial review, the amount is calculated as the difference between the carrying amounts of the assets and the carrying amounts of the liabilities as at the relevant date.

The settlement of a liability, claim or obligation takes place when all legal or constructive obligations are eliminated.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5024" xlink:to="lbl_DE5024"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5024" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Member Benefits Settlement Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5053" xlink:label="loc_DE5053"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5053" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net of all liabilities, obligations &amp; claims incurred and settled during the relevant period. These transactions involve the exchange of valuable consideration between counterparties. Where this results in a net decrease in the value of liabilities, then report a negative figure.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5053" xlink:to="lbl_DE5053"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5053" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Net Incurrence Settlement Transactions Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4810" xlink:label="loc_DE4810"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4810" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the net market value or fair value of the entity's liabilities.

Liabilities, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, are present obligations of the entity arising from past events, the settlement of which is expected to result in an outflow from the entity of resources embodying economic benefits.

Net market value or fair value is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of a liability in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4810" xlink:to="lbl_DE4810"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4810" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Net Market Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4896" xlink:label="loc_DE4896"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4896" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value, as at the relevant date, of bill acceptance and discount facilities provided to the reporting party. For the purposes of this item, report only the balance of the facility that has not been used or drawn down by the reporting party at the relevant date.

Bill acceptance and discount facilities are a form of liquidity, or funding, provided to entity through a facility that discounts bills (e.g. bank accepted bills). Principal and interest (discount) owing on the bill is repaid or 'rolled over' by the reporting party on maturity of the bill.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4896" xlink:to="lbl_DE4896"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4896" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Off Balance Sheet Bill Acceptance Discount Facilities Available Undrawn Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5019" xlink:label="loc_DE5019"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5019" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value, as at the relevant date, of letter of credit facilities committed to by the reporting party. For the purposes of this item, report only the balance of the facility that has not been used or drawn down by the reporting party at the relevant date.

A letter of credit facility is an irrevocable and unconditional undertaking to repay the principal and interest of a loan in the event of default.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5019" xlink:to="lbl_DE5019"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5019" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Off Balance Sheet Letter Of Credit Facilities Undrawn Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5621" xlink:label="loc_DE5621"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5621" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value, as at the relevant date, of overdraft facilities available to the reporting party. For the purposes of this item, report only the balance of the facility that has not been used or drawn down by the reporting party at the relevant date.

Overdraft facilities are accounts which may be overdrawn up to a limit agreed by the parties involved.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5621" xlink:to="lbl_DE5621"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5621" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Off Balance Sheet Overdraft Available Undrawn Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4325" xlink:label="loc_DE4325"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4325" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the hedging adjustment required to translate the aggregate other liabilities balance to the effective post-derivatives position. This will contain liabilities other than:
- Borrowings
- Trade and other payables
- Provisions
- Gross policy liabilities
- Policy owner retained profits
- Unearned premium income
- Approved subordinated debt

A hedging adjustment represents the adjustment required to translate the effective exposure associated with hedging investments. The purpose of a hedging investment is to offset the risk of changes in the fair value or investment cash flows of another contract.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4325" xlink:to="lbl_DE4325"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4325" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Other Adjustment Hedging Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5259" xlink:label="loc_DE5259"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5259" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is a balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

Report the net market value, or fair value, of any amounts payable other than those categorised as one of the following: 
- Administration Fees
- Management Fees
- Investment Fees
- Trustee Fees
- Audit and Tax Fees
- Members benefits payable
- Borrowings.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5259" xlink:to="lbl_DE5259"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5259" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Other BS Fees Payable Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5234" xlink:label="loc_DE5234"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5234" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the net market value, or fair value, of liabilities other than:
- Borrowings
- Trade and other payables
- Provisions
- Gross policy liabilities
- Policy owner retained profits
- Unearned premium income
- Approved subordinated debt

Liabilities, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, are present obligations of an entity arising from past events, the settlement of which is expected to result in an outflow from the entity of resources embodying economic benefits.

Net market value, or fair value, is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of an asset in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5234" xlink:to="lbl_DE5234"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5234" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Other BS Item Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5191" xlink:label="loc_DE5191"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5191" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is a balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

Report the face value, or principle value, of liabilities incurred during the relevant period other than those categorised as one of the following: 

- Administration Fees
- Management Fees
- Investment Fees
- Trustee Fees
- Audit and Tax Fees
- Members benefits payable
- Borrowings.

The face value or principle value of a liability represents the amount that an issuer agrees to pay at the maturity date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5191" xlink:to="lbl_DE5191"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5191" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Other BS Item Incurred Face Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5366" xlink:label="loc_DE5366"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5366" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is a balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

Report the net of all incurrance and settlement transactions, during the relevant period, of any amounts related to liabilities other than those categorised as one of the following: 
- Administration Fees
- Management Fees
- Investment Fees
- Trustee Fees
- Audit and Tax Fees
- Members benefits payable
- Borrowings.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5366" xlink:to="lbl_DE5366"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5366" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Other BS Item Net Incurrence Settlement Transactions Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5022" xlink:label="loc_DE5022"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5022" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is a balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

Report the amount paid during the relevant period to settle liabilities other than those categorised as one of the following: 

- Administration Fees
- Management Fees
- Investment Fees
- Trustee Fees
- Audit and Tax Fees
- Members benefits payable
- Borrowings.

The settlement of a liability takes place when all legal or constructive obligations are eliminated.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5022" xlink:to="lbl_DE5022"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5022" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Other BS Item Settlement Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5754" xlink:label="loc_DE5754"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5754" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value, as at the relevant date, of overdraft facilities available to the reporting party. For the purposes of this item, report the total approved balance of the facility.

Overdraft facilities are accounts which may be overdrawn up to a limit agreed by the parties involved.

The approved balance of a facility is the maximum approved amount that can be drawn down in relation to that facility.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5754" xlink:to="lbl_DE5754"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5754" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Overdraft Available Approved Limit Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5431" xlink:label="loc_DE5431"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5431" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the amount paid during the relevant period to settle the entity's liabilities, claims, or obligations.

Liabilities, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, are present obligations of the entity arising from past events, the settlement of which is expected to result in an outflow from the entity of resources embodying economic benefits.

The settlement of a liability, claim or obligation takes place when all legal or constructive obligations are eliminated.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5431" xlink:to="lbl_DE5431"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5431" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Settlement Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4736" xlink:label="loc_DE4736"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4736" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value of approved subordinated debt, as determined in accordance with the approval letter received from the relevant regulatory authority.

Subordinated debt is that debt which is ranked lower in priority than other senior debt. In the event of bankruptcy, subordinated debtholders receive payment only after senior debt claims are paid in full.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4736" xlink:to="lbl_DE4736"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4736" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Subordinated Debt Approved Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4134" xlink:label="loc_DE4134"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4134" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value of eligible approved subordinated debt, as determined in accordance with the approval letter received from the relevant regulatory authority.

Subordinated debt is that debt which is ranked lower in priority than other senior debt, including policyholders. In the event of bankruptcy, subordinated debtholders receive payment only after senior debt claims are paid in full.

The eligible amount is the quantum of the approved subordinated debt (as determined in accordance with the approval letter received from the relevant regulatory authority) that can be used in meeting the solvency/capital adequacy requirements of the reporting party.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4134" xlink:to="lbl_DE4134"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4134" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Subordinated Debt Approved Eligible Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4805" xlink:label="loc_DE4805"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4805" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value of ineligible approved subordinated debt, as determined in accordance with the approval letter received from the relevant regulatory authority.

Subordinated debt is that debt which is ranked lower in priority than other senior debt. In the event of bankruptcy, subordinated debtholders receive payment only after senior debt claims are paid in full.

The ineligible amount is the quantum of the approved subordinated debt (as determined in accordance with the approval letter received from the relevant regulatory authority} that cannot be used in meeting the solvency/capital adequacy requirements of the reporting party.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4805" xlink:to="lbl_DE4805"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4805" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Subordinated Debt Approved Ineligible Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4485" xlink:label="loc_DE4485"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4485" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value of liabilities, including allowance for acquisition costs arising in respect of policies. This method of disclosure differs from the Australian Accounting Standards.

Liabilities, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, are present obligations of an entity arising from past events, the settlement of which is expected to result in an outflow from the entity of resources embodying economic benefits.

Acquisition costs, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, are the fixed and variable costs of acquiring new business including commissions and similar distribution costs, and costs of accepting, issuing and initially recording policies. (Acquisition costs relate to the costs incurred in acquiring specific life insurance contracts during the relevant period. They do not include the general growth and development costs incurred by a life insurer.)</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4485" xlink:to="lbl_DE4485"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4485" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Total Including Deferred Acquisition Costs Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5117" xlink:label="loc_DE5117"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5117" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the face value, or principle value, of liabilities incurred during the relevant period that are classified as trustee fees.

Trustee fees are typically amounts payable to the trustee for performing their legal responsibilities as detailed in the Trust Deed.

The face value or principle value of a liability represents the amount that an issuer agrees to pay at the maturity date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5117" xlink:to="lbl_DE5117"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5117" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Trustee Fees Incurred Face Value Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5717" xlink:label="loc_DE5717"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5717" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the net of all incurrance and settlement transactions, during the relevant period, of trustee fees payable.

Trustee fees are typically amounts payable to the trustee for performing their legal responsibilities as detailed in the Trust Deed.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5717" xlink:to="lbl_DE5717"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5717" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Trustee Fees Net Incurrence Settlement Transactions Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4680" xlink:label="loc_DE4680"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4680" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the net market value, or fair value, of trustee fees payable.

Trustee fees are typically amounts payable to the trustee for performing their legal responsibilities as detailed in the Trustee Deed.

Net market value or fair value is the amount which could be expected to be received from the disposal of a liability in an orderly market; or in an arm's length transaction between knowledgeable, willing parties; after deducting costs expected to be incurred in realising the proceeds of such a disposal.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4680" xlink:to="lbl_DE4680"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4680" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Trustee Fees Payable Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5485" xlink:label="loc_DE5485"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5485" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Record the amount paid during the relevant period to settle liabilities classified as trustee fees.

Trustee fees are typically amounts payable to the trustee for performing their legal responsibilities as detailed in the Trust Deed.

The settlement of a liability takes place when all legal or constructive obligations are eliminated.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5485" xlink:to="lbl_DE5485"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5485" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Liabilities Trustee Fees Settlement Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5430" xlink:label="loc_DE5430"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5430" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of assets sold with recourse. These are non-market related off-balance sheet asset sales (to the extent that such assets are not included in on-balance sheet) by an entity where the holder of the asset is entitled to 'put' the asset back to the entity within an agreed period or under certain prescribed circumstances, e.g. deterioration in the value or credit quality of the asset concerned.

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5430" xlink:to="lbl_DE5430"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5430" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Assets Sold With Recourse Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4806" xlink:label="loc_DE4806"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4806" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the value of the assets that are subject to the charge or encumbrance.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4806" xlink:to="lbl_DE4806"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4806" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Assets Subject To Charge Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4942" xlink:label="loc_DE4942"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4942" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of bills endorsed under bill endorsement lines (but are not accepted by, or have the prior endorsement of, an ADI). Report only irrevocable non-market related off-balance sheet obligations that carry the same credit risk as a direct extension of credit, such as an undertaking to make a payment to a third party in the event that a counterparty fails to meet a financial obligation, or an undertaking to a counterparty to acquire a potential claim on another party in the event of default by that party, constitutes a direct credit substitute (i.e. the risk of loss depends on the creditworthiness of the counterparty or the party on whom a potential claim is acquired).

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4942" xlink:to="lbl_DE4942"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4942" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Bill Endorsements Principal Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5145" xlink:label="loc_DE5145"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5145" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the outstanding value of the charge or encumbrance (as at the relevant date) given over assets of the reporting party.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5145" xlink:to="lbl_DE5145"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5145" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Charge Outstanding Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5487" xlink:label="loc_DE5487"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5487" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the principal or face value or amount of the charge or encumbrance given over assets of the reporting party.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5487" xlink:to="lbl_DE5487"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5487" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Charge Principal Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4970" xlink:label="loc_DE4970"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4970" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The purposes are set out in the Life Insurance Act 1995, Sections 38 and 40.

38 (3)  A life company must not mortgage or charge any of the assets of a statutory fund except: 
                     (a)  to secure a bank overdraft; or 
                     (b)  in connection with the undertaking of a major development project and in accordance with section 40; or 
                     (c)  for such other purposes, and subject to such other conditions, as are prescribed by the regulations.

40 (1)  A life company may mortgage or charge an asset of a statutory fund, otherwise than for a purpose of the kind referred to in paragraph 38(3)(a) or (c), if: 
                     (a)  the mortgage or charge is to be given in connection with the undertaking of a major development project; and 
                     (b)  the giving of the mortgage or charge has been approved by APRA.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4970" xlink:to="lbl_DE4970"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4970" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">The enumerated values are: 
Derivatices
Major Development Project
Other
Overdraft</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4970" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Charge Purpose Code</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5284" xlink:label="loc_DE5284"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5284" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The following is not an exhaustive list but is provided as an example:

Fixed charge
A fixed charge is generally given in relation to a specific asset or assets and it will generally limit the ability or right of the life company to deal with those assets.

Floating charge
A floating charge may be given over specific assets or all assets of the life company and may generally only crystallise and become a fixed charge on the occurrence of a specific event that is agreed between the parties (i.e. default on payment, or not maintaining specified interest coverage ratios).</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5284" xlink:to="lbl_DE5284"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5284" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Charge Type Text</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4891" xlink:label="loc_DE4891"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4891" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of the non-market related off-balance sheet contingent liabilities relating to commitments that can be unconditionally revoked at any time without notice.

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4891" xlink:to="lbl_DE4891"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4891" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Commitments That Can Be Unconditionally Revoked At Any Time Without Notice Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5624" xlink:label="loc_DE5624"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5624" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of credit derivatives where protection is sold. Report only irrevocable non-market related off-balance sheet obligations that carry the same credit risk as a direct extension of credit, such as an undertaking to make a payment to a third party in the event that a counterparty fails to meet a financial obligation, or an undertaking to a counterparty to acquire a potential claim on another party in the event of default by that party, constitutes a direct credit substitute (i.e. the risk of loss depends on the creditworthiness of the counterparty or the party on whom a potential claim is acquired).

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5624" xlink:to="lbl_DE5624"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5624" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Credit Derivatives Sold Protection Principal Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5387" xlink:label="loc_DE5387"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5387" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

This is the balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

Report all other irrevocable non-market related off-balance sheet obligations that carry the same credit risk as a direct extension of credit, such as an undertaking to make a payment to a third party in the event that a counterparty fails to meet a financial obligation, or an undertaking to a counterparty to acquire a potential claim on another party in the event of default by that party, constitutes a direct credit substitute (i.e. the risk of loss depends on the creditworthiness of the counterparty or the party on whom a potential claim is acquired).

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5387" xlink:to="lbl_DE5387"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5387" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Direct Credit Substitutes Other Principal Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5404" xlink:label="loc_DE5404"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5404" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of any irrevocable non-market related off-balance sheet obligations that carry the same credit risk as a direct extension of credit, such as an undertaking to make a payment to a third party in the event that a counterparty fails to meet a financial obligation, or an undertaking to a counterparty to acquire a potential claim on another party in the event of default by that party, constitutes a direct credit substitute (i.e. the risk of loss depends on the creditworthiness of the counterparty or the party on whom a potential claim is acquired).

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5404" xlink:to="lbl_DE5404"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5404" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Direct Credit Substitutes Principal Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4627" xlink:label="loc_DE4627"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4627" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The value reported here is the lesser of:

1) the value of the assets subject to the charge; and 

2) the outstanding value of the charge granted.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4627" xlink:to="lbl_DE4627"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4627" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Extent Of Indebtedness Secured By Assets Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5465" xlink:label="loc_DE5465"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5465" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of forward asset purchases. These are non-market related off-balance sheet commitments to purchase assets at a future date and on pre-arranged terms. This includes a loan, security or other asset from another party, including written put options on specified assets with the character of a credit enhancement.
Where an entity purchasing the asset has an unequivocal right to substitute cash settlement in place of accepting delivery of the asset, and the price on settlement is calculated with reference to a general market price indicator (and not to the financial condition of any specific entity), the purchase may be treated as a market-related off-balance sheet transaction.
Written put options expressed in terms of market rates for currencies or financial instruments bearing no credit risk are excluded.

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5465" xlink:to="lbl_DE5465"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5465" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Forward Asset Purchases Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5112" xlink:label="loc_DE5112"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5112" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of any potential credit exposures arising from the issue of guarantees. Report only irrevocable non-market related off-balance sheet obligations that carry the same credit risk as a direct extension of credit, such as an undertaking to make a payment to a third party in the event that a counterparty fails to meet a financial obligation, or an undertaking to a counterparty to acquire a potential claim on another party in the event of default by that party, constitutes a direct credit substitute (i.e. the risk of loss depends on the creditworthiness of the counterparty or the party on whom a potential claim is acquired).

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5112" xlink:to="lbl_DE5112"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5112" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Guarantees Principal Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4929" xlink:label="loc_DE4929"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4929" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of any irrevocable commitments that are not formal standby facilities or credit lines. These are non-market related off-balance sheet contingent liabilities relating to the maximum unused portion of any irrevocable commitments that could be drawn during the remaining period to maturity.

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4929" xlink:to="lbl_DE4929"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4929" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Irrevocable Commitments Other Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5589" xlink:label="loc_DE5589"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5589" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the approved balance of liquidity support facilities contracted by the reporting party to supplement its liquidity requirements.

In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

The approved balance of a facility is the maximum approved amount that can be drawn down in relation to that facility.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5589" xlink:to="lbl_DE5589"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5589" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Liquidity Support Facilities Approved Balance Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5010" xlink:label="loc_DE5010"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5010" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

The approved balance of a facility is the maximum approved amount that can be drawn down in relation to that facility.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5010" xlink:to="lbl_DE5010"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5010" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Liquidity Support Facilities Other Approved Balance Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5505" xlink:label="loc_DE5505"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5505" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

The undrawn balance is the balance of the facility that has not been used or drawn down by the reporting party at the relevant date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5505" xlink:to="lbl_DE5505"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5505" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Liquidity Support Facilities Other Undrawn Balance Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5001" xlink:label="loc_DE5001"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5001" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the undrawn balance of liquidity support facilities contracted by the reporting party to supplement its liquidity requirements.

In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

The undrawn balance is the balance of the facility that has not been used or drawn down by the reporting party at the relevant date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5001" xlink:to="lbl_DE5001"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5001" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Liquidity Support Facilities Undrawn Balance Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5015" xlink:label="loc_DE5015"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5015" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of loans that are approved but not yet drawn. These are non-market related off-balance sheet contingent liabilities where the loans have been approved by the reporting party but the counterparty has yet to draw down the funds in relation to the arrangement.

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5015" xlink:to="lbl_DE5015"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5015" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Loans Approved But Not Yet Advanced Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5619" xlink:label="loc_DE5619"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5619" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

This is the balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5619" xlink:to="lbl_DE5619"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5619" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Non Market Related Other Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5160" xlink:label="loc_DE5160"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5160" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of all non-market related off-balance sheet transactions that give rise to credit risk exposures. 

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5160" xlink:to="lbl_DE5160"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5160" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Non Market Related Total Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5095" xlink:label="loc_DE5095"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5095" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of note issuance and revolving underwriting facilities. These are non-market related off-balance sheet contingent liabilities in relation to arrangements whereby a borrower may draw down funds up to a prescribed limit over a predefined period by making repeated note issues to the market, and where, should the issue prove unable to be placed in the market, the unplaced amount is to be taken up or funds made available by the reporting entity being committed as an underwriter of the facility.

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5095" xlink:to="lbl_DE5095"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5095" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Note Issuance And Revolving Underwriting Facilities Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5036" xlink:label="loc_DE5036"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5036" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of partly paid shares and securities. These are non-market related off-balance sheet contingent liabilities in relation to any amounts owing on the uncalled portion of partly paid shares and securities that represent commitments with certain draw down by the issuer at a future date.

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5036" xlink:to="lbl_DE5036"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5036" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Partly Paid Shares And Securities Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5027" xlink:label="loc_DE5027"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5027" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of performance-related contingencies. These are non-market related off-balance sheet contingent liabilities that involve an irrevocable obligation to pay a third party in the event that a counterparty fails to fulfil or perform a contractual non-monetary obligation, such as delivery of goods by a specified date, etc (i.e. the risk of loss depends on a future event that is not directly related to the creditworthiness of the counterparty involved).
This includes but is not limited to:
- issue of performance bond;
- bid bonds;
- warranties;
- indemnities; and
- standby letters of credit in relation to a non-monetary obligation of a counterparty under a particular transaction.

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5027" xlink:to="lbl_DE5027"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5027" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Performance Related Contingencies Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5534" xlink:label="loc_DE5534"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5534" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of placements of forward deposits. These are non-market related off-balance sheet contingent liabilities in relation to any agreement between an entity and another party whereby the entity will place a deposit at an agreed rate of interest with that party at a predetermined future date.

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5534" xlink:to="lbl_DE5534"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5534" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Placements Of Forward Deposits Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5671" xlink:label="loc_DE5671"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5671" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of sale and repurchase agreements ('Repos'). This relates to non-market related off-balance sheet arrangements whereby an entity sells a loan, security or other asset to another party with a commitment to repurchase the asset at an agreed price on an agreed future date.

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5671" xlink:to="lbl_DE5671"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5671" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Sale And Repurchase Agreements Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5237" xlink:label="loc_DE5237"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5237" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the approved balance of standby facilities that can be drawn down (funds accessed) within two to five days after notice is given by the reporting party of its intention to draw down on the standby facility (i.e. a two-five day waiting period).

In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

A formal standby facility or credit line is a formalised arrangement in which the counterparty has the right but not the obligation to draw down funds to a specified limit.

The approved balance of a facility is the maximum approved amount that can be drawn down in relation to that facility.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5237" xlink:to="lbl_DE5237"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5237" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Standby Facilities 2 To 5 Day Draw Down Approved Balance Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4901" xlink:label="loc_DE4901"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4901" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the undrawn balance of standby facilities that can be drawn down (funds accessed) within two to five days after notice is given by the reporting party of its intention to draw down on the standby facility (i.e. a two-five day waiting period).

In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

A formal standby facility or credit line is a formalised arrangement in which the counterparty has the right but not the obligation to draw down funds to a specified limit.

The undrawn balance is the balance of the facility that has not been used or drawn down by the reporting party at the relevant date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4901" xlink:to="lbl_DE4901"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4901" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Standby Facilities 2 To 5 Day Draw Down Undrawn Balance Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5149" xlink:label="loc_DE5149"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5149" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the approved balance of standby facilities that can be drawn down (funds accessed) five days after notice is given by the reporting party of its intention to draw down on the standby facility (i.e. a five day waiting period).

In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

A formal standby facility or credit line is a formalised arrangement in which the counterparty has the right but not the obligation to draw down funds to a specified limit.

The approved balance of a facility is the maximum approved amount that can be drawn down in relation to that facility.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5149" xlink:to="lbl_DE5149"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5149" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Standby Facilities Greater Than 5 Day Draw Down Approved Balance Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5311" xlink:label="loc_DE5311"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5311" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the undrawn balance of standby facilities that can be drawn down (funds accessed) five days after notice is given by the reporting party of its intention to draw down on the standby facility (i.e. a five day waiting period).

In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

A formal standby facility or credit line is a formalised arrangement in which the counterparty has the right but not the obligation to draw down funds to a specified limit.

The undrawn balance is the balance of the facility that has not been used or drawn down by the reporting party at the relevant date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5311" xlink:to="lbl_DE5311"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5311" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Standby Facilities Greater Than 5 Day Draw Down Undrawn Balance Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5574" xlink:label="loc_DE5574"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5574" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the approved balance of standby facilities that can be drawn down (funds accessed) on the same day that notice is given by the reporting party of its intention to draw down on the standby facility.

In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

A formal standby facility or credit line is a formalised arrangement in which the counterparty has the right but not the obligation to draw down funds to a specified limit.

The approved balance of a facility is the maximum approved amount that can be drawn down in relation to that facility.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5574" xlink:to="lbl_DE5574"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5574" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Standby Facilities Same Day Draw Down Approved Balance Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4943" xlink:label="loc_DE4943"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4943" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Report the undrawn balance of standby facilities that can be drawn down (funds accessed) on the same day that notice is given by the reporting party of its intention to draw down on the standby facility.

In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

A formal standby facility or credit line is a formalised arrangement in which the counterparty has the right but not the obligation to draw down funds to a specified limit.

The undrawn balance is the balance of the facility that has not been used or drawn down by the reporting party at the relevant date.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4943" xlink:to="lbl_DE4943"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4943" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Standby Facilities Same Day Draw Down Undrawn Balance Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE4905" xlink:label="loc_DE4905"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4905" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of issued standby letters of credit serving as financial guarantees for loans, securities and any other financial liabilities. Report only irrevocable non-market related off-balance sheet obligations that carry the same credit risk as a direct extension of credit, such as an undertaking to make a payment to a third party in the event that a counterparty fails to meet a financial obligation, or an undertaking to a counterparty to acquire a potential claim on another party in the event of default by that party, constitutes a direct credit substitute (i.e. the risk of loss depends on the creditworthiness of the counterparty or the party on whom a potential claim is acquired).

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE4905" xlink:to="lbl_DE4905"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE4905" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Standby Letters Of Credit Principal Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5054" xlink:label="loc_DE5054"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5054" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of trade-related contingencies. These are non-market related off-balance sheet contingent liabilities arising from trade-related obligations that are secured against an underlying shipment of goods.
This includes but is not limited to:
- documentary letters of credit issued;
- acceptances on trade bills;
- shipping guarantees issued; and
- any other trade-related contingencies.

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5054" xlink:to="lbl_DE5054"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5054" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Trade Related Contingencies Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo1.02.05.data.xsd#DE5051" xlink:label="loc_DE5051"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5051" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">In reporting this item the reporting party is to follow the basis that is used for the preparation of the annual financial statements in accordance with the Australian accounting standards. Actuarial valuations and calculations used in deriving the value of the item must be in accordance with prudential standards.

Report the principal amount of the non-market related off-balance sheet contingent liabilities relating to formal standby facilities or credit lines.

A formal standby facility or credit line is a formalised arrangement in which the counterparty has the right but not the obligation to draw down funds to a specified limit.

The principal amount refers to the face value or gross amount of a given off-balance sheet transaction and not the fair value. The principal amount must be reported as a positive value, even for short positions in derivative financial instruments.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE5051" xlink:to="lbl_DE5051"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE5051" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Off Balance Sheet Undrawn Formal Standby Facilities And Credit Lines Amount</link:label>
    </link:labelLink>
</link:linkbase>
