<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Disclaimer: http://www.sbr.gov.au/content/taxonomy_introduction_3_0.htm#Disclaimer -->
<link:linkbase xmlns:link="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xbrli="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance">
    <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#businessDefinition"/>
    <link:labelLink xlink:type="extended" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/link">
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo5.02.10.data.xsd#bafpo5.02.10_bafpo5Abstract" xlink:label="loc_bafpo5.02.10_bafpo5Abstract"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_bafpo5Abstract" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Financial Position 5</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_bafpo5.02.10_bafpo5Abstract" xlink:to="lbl_bafpo5Abstract"/>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo5.02.10.data.xsd#DE13000" xlink:label="loc_DE13000"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE13000" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Loans And Receivables Including Accrued Income Excluding Deferred Acquisition Costs Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE13000" xlink:to="lbl_DE13000"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE13000" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, as at the relevant date, of receivables, including outstanding premiums, but not deferred acquisition costs arising in respect of policies. Do not include accrued income from investment assets as well as investment income due but not received. This method of disclosure differs from the Australian Accounting Standards.

Acquisition costs, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, are the fixed and variable costs of acquiring new business including commissions and similar distribution costs, and costs of accepting, issuing and initially recording policies.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo5.02.10.data.xsd#DE12994" xlink:label="loc_DE12994"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12994" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Loans And Receivables Income Asset Holding Not Equity Securities Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE12994" xlink:to="lbl_DE12994"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12994" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, as at the relevant date, of income that is receivable by the reporting entity. For the purposes of this item, include only income from the holding of assets that are not equity securities (e.g. Interest and rental income that is accrued but not yet received). 

Equity securities are, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, contracts that evidence a residual interest in the assets of an entity after deducting all its liabilities. This includes equity securities lent or sold by the entity under repurchase agreements, where the transaction does not result in the transfer of the rights of ownership of the securities away from the entity to another party.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo5.02.10.data.xsd#DE12995" xlink:label="loc_DE12995"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12995" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Loans And Receivables Insurance Recoveries Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE12995" xlink:to="lbl_DE12995"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12995" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, as at the relevant date, of recoveries receivable by the reporting entity in relation to paid and unpaid insurance claims.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo5.02.10.data.xsd#DE12996" xlink:label="loc_DE12996"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12996" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Loans And Receivables Insurance Recoveries Not Reinsurance Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE12996" xlink:to="lbl_DE12996"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12996" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, as at the relevant date, for recoveries under arrangements other than reinsurance arrangements, receivable by the reporting insurer associated with the outstanding claims liability (OCL). This item is to be determined in accordance with relevant accounting standard.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo5.02.10.data.xsd#DE12997" xlink:label="loc_DE12997"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12997" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Loans And Receivables Insurance Recoveries Not Reinsurance Outstanding Claims Liability Central Estimate Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE12997" xlink:to="lbl_DE12997"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12997" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, as at the relevant date, of the central estimate of recoveries, other than reinsurance recoveries, receivable by the reporting entity in relation to outstanding (unpaid) claims. This item is to be determined in accordance with relevant prudential standards. Recoveries to be included at this item include salvage, subrogation, and input tax credit recoveries, amongst others.

The central estimate will be measured as the present value of the future expected recoveries except from reinsurance, i.e. discounted for future investment income, determined in accordance with relevant prudential standards. The central estimate is intended to reflect the mean value in the range of possible values for the outcome (that is, the mean of the distribution of probabilistic outcomes), and so does not include any risk margin.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo5.02.10.data.xsd#DE12998" xlink:label="loc_DE12998"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12998" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Loans And Receivables Insurance Recoveries Not Reinsurance Premiums Liabilities Prudential Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE12998" xlink:to="lbl_DE12998"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12998" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, as at the relevant date, of the central estimate of recoveries, other than reinsurance recoveries, receivable by the reporting entity associated with the premiums liabilities. This item is to be determined in accordance with relevant prudential standards. 

The central estimate will be measured as the present value of the future expected recoveries except from reinsurance, i.e. discounted for future investment income, determined in accordance with relevant prudential standards. The central estimate is intended to reflect the mean value in the range of possible values for the outcome (that is, the mean of the distribution of probabilistic outcomes), and so does not include any risk margin.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo5.02.10.data.xsd#DE12999" xlink:label="loc_DE12999"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12999" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Loans And Receivables Insurance Recoveries Reinsurance Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE12999" xlink:to="lbl_DE12999"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12999" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, as at the relevant date, for reinsurance recoverables, being amounts due to the reporting insurer under a reinsurance arrangement that arise from the recognition of outstanding claims liability (OCL). This item is to be determined in accordance with relevant accounting standard.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo5.02.10.data.xsd#DE12591" xlink:label="loc_DE12591"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12591" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Loans And Receivables Outstanding Claims Liability Recoveries Not Reinsurance Gross Input Tax Credit Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE12591" xlink:to="lbl_DE12591"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE12591" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, as at the relevant date, of recoveries receivable by the reporting party in relation to Outstanding Claims Liability (OCL) other than reinsurance recoveries, gross of related input tax credit, and net of any provisions for depreciation or impairment.

OCL relates to all claims incurred prior to the valuation date, whether or not they have been reported to the reporting party. The value of the OCL must include an amount in respect of the expenses that the reporting party expects to incur in settling these claims. The value of OCL must not include any Government charges directly imposed on the reporting party such as levies, duties and taxes, but must be gross of input tax credit recoveries.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo5.02.10.data.xsd#DE13003" xlink:label="loc_DE13003"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE13003" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Loans And Receivables Receivables Total General Insurance Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE13003" xlink:to="lbl_DE13003"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE13003" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, as at the relevant date, of total receivables, including investment income, total net recoveries other than reinsurance receivable, premium receivables, net amount recoverable from reinsurance contracts on outstanding claims and paid claims, other reinsurance assets, current tax assets, GST receivable, and any other general insurance receivables. This method of disclosure differs from the Australian Accounting Standards.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo5.02.10.data.xsd#DE13001" xlink:label="loc_DE13001"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE13001" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Loans And Receivables Reinsurance Recoveries Expected Premiums Liabilities Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE13001" xlink:to="lbl_DE13001"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE13001" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, as at the relevant date, of the central estimate of expected reinsurance recoveries receivable by the reporting entity associated with the premiums liabilities. This item is to be determined in accordance with relevant prudential standards. 

The central estimate will be measured as the present value of the future expected reinsurance recoveries, i.e. discounted for future investment income, determined in accordance with relevant prudential standards. The central estimate is intended to reflect the mean value in the range of possible values for the outcome (that is, the mean of the distribution of probabilistic outcomes), and so does not include any risk margin.

Expected reinsurance recoveries means any amounts due to an insurer, or to an entity that carries on international business within a Level 2 insurance group, from a reinsurer that arise from the recognition of premiums liabilities referred to in the GI Prudential Standards. This is distinguished from reinsurance recoverables.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo5.02.10.data.xsd#DE13002" xlink:label="loc_DE13002"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE13002" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Loans And Receivables Seed Capital Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE13002" xlink:to="lbl_DE13002"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE13002" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, as at the relevant date, of receivables classified as seed capital. Seed capital is the preliminary contribution of funding toward the financing of a new business. Commonly this is in the form of a loan, usually provided by a related entity.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpo5.02.10.data.xsd#DE13004" xlink:label="loc_DE13004"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE13004" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Assets Loans And Receivables Total Receivables Life Insurance Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE13004" xlink:to="lbl_DE13004"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE13004" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, as at the relevant date, of total receivables, including outstanding premiums, but not deferred acquisition costs arising in respect of policies. Do not include accrued income from investment assets. This method of disclosure differs from the Australian Accounting Standards. Acquisition costs, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, are the fixed and variable costs of acquiring new business including commissions and similar distribution costs, and costs of accepting, issuing and initially recording policies. (Acquisition costs relate to the costs incurred in acquiring specific life insurance contracts during the relevant period. They do not include the general growth and development costs incurred by a life insurer).</link:label>
    </link:labelLink>
</link:linkbase>
