<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Disclaimer: http://www.sbr.gov.au/content/taxonomy_introduction_3_0.htm#Disclaimer -->
<link:linkbase xmlns:link="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xbrli="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink">
  <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#businessDefinition"/>
  <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#dataElementGuidance"/>
  <link:labelLink xlink:type="extended" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/link">
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#gfagc.02.01_gfagcAbstract" xlink:label="loc_gfagc.02.01_gfagcAbstract"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_gfagcAbstract" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Concessions</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_gfagc.02.01_gfagcAbstract" xlink:to="lbl_gfagcAbstract"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3529" xlink:label="loc_DE3529"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3529" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Small Business And General Business Tax Break Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3529" xlink:to="lbl_DE3529"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3529" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The small business and general business tax break in the form of an investment allowance is  available for expenditure on eligible new tangible depreciating assets.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3529" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">The tax break provides the following deductions for:
small business entities (turnover of less than $2 million a year)
? an additional tax deduction of 50% of the cost of eligible new tangible depreciating assets is available where the business
- commits to investing in the asset between 13 December 2008 and 31 December 2009 inclusive, and 
- first uses the asset, or installs it ready for use, or (in the case of new investment in an existing asset) brings the asset to its modified or improved state, on or before 31 December 2010

other business entities (turnover of $2 million or more a year)
? an additional tax deduction of 30% of the cost of eligible new tangible depreciating assets is available where the business
- commits to investing in the asset between 13 December 2008 and 30 June 2009 inclusive, and
- first uses the asset, or installs it ready for use, or (in the case of new investment in an existing asset) brings the asset to its modified or improved state, on or before 30 June 2010 
? an additional tax deduction of 10% of the cost of eligible new tangible depreciating assets is available where the business
- commits to investing in the asset between 13 December 2008 and 30 June 2009 inclusive, and
- first uses the asset, or installs it ready for use, or (in the case of new investment in an existing asset) brings the asset to its modified or improved state, between 1 July 2010 and 31 December 2010
? an additional tax deduction of 10% of the cost of eligible new tangible depreciating assets is available where the business
- commits to investing in the asset between 1 July 2009 and 31 December 2009 inclusive, and 
- first uses the asset, or installs it ready for use, or (in the case of new investment in an existing asset) brings the asset to its modified or improved state, on or before 31 December 2010.Generally, a business ?commits? to investing when:
- it enters into a contract under which the asset is held
- it starts to construct the asset, or n it starts to hold the asset in some other way.

The tax break applies to new tangible depreciating assets for which a deduction is available under Subdivision 40-B of the ITAA1997 and certain new investments in existing assets.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3285" xlink:label="loc_DE3285"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3285" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Capital Gains Discount And Small Business Concessions Total Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3285" xlink:to="lbl_DE3285"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3285" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total amount of CGT discount and small business concessions</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3285" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the total of amounts of business concessions using the indexation method .</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3282" xlink:label="loc_DE3282"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3282" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Capital Gains Small Business Active Asset Reduction Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3282" xlink:to="lbl_DE3282"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3282" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The small business active asset reduction concession applied to the capital gains</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3282" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount transferred from the amount calculated on the worksheet.  Inform the appropriate concession. In order to qualify for the small business 50% active asset reduction on a capital gain, the basic conditions  need to be satisfied. If the basic conditions are satisfied the capital gain can be reduced by 50% (after applying any current year capital losses and any unapplied net capital losses from a previous year). If as an individual or trust and both the CGT discount and the small business 50% active asset reduction apply, reduce the capital gain by 50%, then 50% of the remainder ? that is, a total of 75%.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3289" xlink:label="loc_DE3289"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3289" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Capital Gains Small Business Exemption Asset Or Event Code</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3289" xlink:to="lbl_DE3289"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3289" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Code to indicate the type of Capital Gains Tax (CGT) asset or CGT event from which the entity made the capital gain.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3289" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the appropriate code that best describes the Capital Gains Tax (CGT) asset or CGT event from which the entity made the capital gain. 
S = shares, U = units in unit trusts, R = real estate, G = goodwill, O = other CGT assets or CGT events not listed above.
If the entity made capital gains from more than one CGT asset or CGT event, inform the relevant field with the appropriate code which best describes the type of CGT asset or CGT event that produced the largest amount of capital gain.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3288" xlink:label="loc_DE3288"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3288" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Capital Gains Small Business Exemption Exempt Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3288" xlink:to="lbl_DE3288"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3288" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total amount of any capital gains disregarded by the small business under the applicable exemption relating to the number of years that the asset has been held.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3288" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the total amount of any capital gains disregarded by the small business 15-year exemption. It is one of the Capital Gains Tax (CGT) concessions available to small business. It allows an individual to disregard the capital gain made on an asset owned and actively used in the business for 15 years if they satisfy all the conditions.  If the small business 15-year exemption conditions are met,  the capital gain can be disregarded entirely and there is no need to apply any further concessions. Do to apply capital losses before you apply the 15-year exemption.  If the capital gain is from a depreciating asset, do not use the 15-year exemption.  Qualifying for the small business 15-year exemption means that the basic conditions for the small business CGT concessions are satisfied  (the asset must have been an active asset for at least half of the relevant 15-year period, not half of the full period of ownership), that the CGT asset was continuously owned for the 15-year period ending just before the CGT event, that as an individual in business, at the time of the CGT event the individual was 55 years or more and the event was connected with your retirement, or the individual was permanently incapacitated, that as an individual in business and the CGT asset is a share in a company or an interest in a trust, the company or trust had a controlling individual for the entire time you owned the share or interest (not necessarily the same individual for the whole period), or that as a company or trust, the company or trust had a controlling individual for the entire time it owned the CGT asset (not necessarily the same individual for the whole period).  Further, at the time of the CGT event the controlling individual must have been 55 years or more and the event must have been connected with their retirement, or they must have been permanently incapacitated. For CGT assets acquired or transferred under the rollover provisions relating to assets compulsorily acquired, lost or destroyed, or those relating to marriage breakdown, there are modified rules about the requirement that the asset be continuously owned for at least 15 years.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3283" xlink:label="loc_DE3283"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3283" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Capital Gains Small Business Retirement Exemption Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3283" xlink:to="lbl_DE3283"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3283" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The small business retirement exemption concession applied to the capital gains.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3283" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount transferred from the amount calculated on the worksheet. The concession interacts with the eligible termination payment provisions. Broadly, it requires amounts to be paid (rolled over) into a complying superannuation fund, a complying approved deposit fund or a retirement savings account under the eligible termination payment provisions if the recipient is under 55. If the small business retirement exemption is applied after the small business 50% active asset reduction,  the exemption is applied to the remaining 50% of the gain. If the Capital Gains Tax (CGT) discount has also applied,  the exemption is applied to the remaining 25% of the capital gain. If  this concession is chosen, disregard only the amount of capital gain equal to the exempt amount (that is, the amount chosen to be disregarded).  Any capital gain that exceeds the exempt amount cannot be disregarded.  An individual in business can use the small business retirement exemption to disregard all or part of a capital gain remaining after other concessions have applied if the basic conditions are satisfied, if a written record of the amount you have chosen to disregard is kept (the exempt amount), and if under 55 years just before the capital proceeds from the CGT event were received, an amount equal to the exempt amount under the eligible termination was rolled over.  For those over 55 years or more, there is no requirement to roll over any amount. The exempt amount  disregarded under this concession is taken to be an eligible termination payment under the eligible termination payment provisions. It must not exceed the CGT retirement exemption limit.  If a company or trust (other than a public entity),  the small business retirement exemption can  be used to disregard all or part of a capital gain remaining after other concessions have applied if the basic conditions are satisfied, if the controlling individual test is satisfied, if a written record of the amount chosen to be disregarded is kept (the exempt amount) and, where there are two CGT concession stakeholders, of each stakeholder?s percentage of the exempt amount (one may be nil, but both must add up to 100%).  Make an eligible termination payment for each of CGT concession stakeholder based on each individual?s percentage of the exempt amount. The payment must be made by the end of seven days after the company or trust chooses to disregard the capital gain or receives an amount of capital proceeds from the CGT event, whichever occurs later, and where a stakeholder is under 55 years just before receiving the eligible termination payment, roll over an amount equal to that payment under the eligible termination payment provisions. The exempt amount must not exceed the CGT retirement exemption limit of each individual receiving an eligible termination payment.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3284" xlink:label="loc_DE3284"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3284" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Capital Gains Small Business Rollover Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3284" xlink:to="lbl_DE3284"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3284" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The small business rollover allows you to defer all or part of a capital gain made from a CGT event if you acquire a replacement asset or improve an existing asset.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3284" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount transferred from the amount calculated on the worksheet.  The small business rollover allows a capital gain from a CGT event that happens in relation to a small business asset to be deferred if a replacement asset is acquired or an improvement is made to an existing asset and certain conditions are met.  If these conditions are met and the rollover is chosen, the amount of any remaining gain by up to the cost of the replacement asset can be deferred (including any incidental costs).  If the way a replacement asset is used changes or there is a change in circumstances, the deferred capital gain will 'crystallise'.  This means that a capital gain will be made equal to the deferred gain.  If the small business rollover is applied after the small business 50% asset reduction, apply it to the remanning 50% of the gain.  If the CGT discount has also applied, apply the rollover to the remaining 25% of the capital gain.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3357" xlink:label="loc_DE3357"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3357" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Claims Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3357" xlink:to="lbl_DE3357"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3357" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Calculation of the claim amount on Australian owned research and development expenditure claimable at 100%. This amount may be positive or negative.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3357" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en"> Inform the relevant field with the total of allocated base amounts by 100%.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3358" xlink:label="loc_DE3358"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3358" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Excluding Extra Incremental Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3358" xlink:to="lbl_DE3358"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3358" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total of expenditure on Australian owned R&amp;D multiplied by the applicable percentage of either 100% or 125%. This amount may be positive or negative</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3358" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount that is to be transferred to Australian owned Research and Development (R&amp;D) tax concession - not including the relevant field of the Company tax return.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3366" xlink:label="loc_DE3366"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3366" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Extra Incremental Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3366" xlink:to="lbl_DE3366"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3366" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The amount of Australian owned R&amp;D ? extra incremental 50% deduction available to eligible companies for an increase in expenditure on Australian owned R&amp;D above a three year average.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3366" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of the company?s deduction under the Research and Development (R&amp;D) incremental concession on the Schedule and Incremental R&amp;D (additional 50%) deduction in the relevant field on the Company tax return.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3480" xlink:label="loc_DE3480"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3480" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Group Code</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3480" xlink:to="lbl_DE3480"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3480" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicates if the company is a grouped taxpayer in accordance with the grouping rules in section 73L of the Income Tax Assessment Act 1936 and another taxpayer in the same group is also claiming the same R&amp;D ? extra incremental percentage deduction.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3480" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">G = Grouped, B = Blank</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3479" xlink:label="loc_DE3479"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3479" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Including Extra Incremental Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3479" xlink:to="lbl_DE3479"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3479" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The amount of the Australian owned R&amp;D extra 50% deduction shown on the Research and development tax concession schedule, Australian owned R&amp;D ? extra incremental 50% deduction.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3479" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of incremental R&amp;D (additional 50%) deduction.
The amount on the company tax return must be the same as the amount on the research and development tax concession schedule. If the company is a grouped taxpayer and another taxpayer in the same group is also claiming the additional 50% deduction, you are required to place a code into the Incremental R&amp;D additional 50% deduction code field.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3369" xlink:label="loc_DE3369"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3369" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Incremental Tax Concession Adjustment Foreign Owned Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3369" xlink:to="lbl_DE3369"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3369" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The net effect of adjustments to reduced expenditure on foreign owned R&amp;D claimable at 100% for the eligible company for the current year.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3364" xlink:label="loc_DE3364"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3364" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Incremental Tax Concession Adjustment Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3364" xlink:to="lbl_DE3364"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3364" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The net effect of adjustments to reduced expenditure on Australian owned R&amp;D claimable at 100% for the eligible company for the current year</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3364" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with any adjustments which may be required if any of the following circumstances apply;  the company has incurred some R&amp;D expenditure which is not deductible (for example, in relation to unregistered activities).  An intra-group mark-up should be included in any adjustments. The amount of intra-group mark-up is shown Adjustment to Y0. Note: If no other amounts are included at  Adjustment to Y0, inform this field with a negative value.  
If a company has left or joined a consolidated group an adjustment (positive or negative) may be required at Adjustment to Y0.  It is also used to adjust incremental expenditure claimable at 100% and incremental expenditure that is not deductible.  Total of additional schedule where applicable is used to adjust the incremental expenditure claimable at 125%. A negative value may be inserted in these rows if necessary.  The types of adjustments that may be required to inform the field of the Y0 amount may also likely affect the amount reported in respect of Y?1, Y?2 and Y?3 for the company and other group members.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3363" xlink:label="loc_DE3363"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3363" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Incremental Tax Concession Eligibility And Claim Australian Owned Indicator</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3363" xlink:to="lbl_DE3363"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3363" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Question to determine if the company is eligible for and wants to claim the Australian owned research and development (R&amp;D) incremental tax concession</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3363" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol if the company wants to claim the Australian owned Research and Development (R&amp;D) incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3367" xlink:label="loc_DE3367"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3367" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Incremental Tax Concession Eligibility And Claim Foreign Owned Indicator</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3367" xlink:to="lbl_DE3367"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3367" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Question to determine if the company is eligible for and wants to claim the foreign owned research and development (R&amp;D) incremental tax concession</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3367" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the appropriate symbol in the relevant field if the company wants to claim the Foreign owned Research and Development (R&amp;D) incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3365" xlink:label="loc_DE3365"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3365" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Incremental Tax Concession Eligibility Prior Year Indicator</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3365" xlink:to="lbl_DE3365"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3365" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Question regarding eligibility to claim an incremental tax concession in the specified year.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3365" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with a Y for Yes or N for No to the question of whether the company, or any of its group members, was eligible, or deemed to be eligible, to claim an incremental tax concession in a prior year.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3368" xlink:label="loc_DE3368"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Incremental Tax Concession Reduced Expenditure Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3368" xlink:to="lbl_DE3368"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Incremental Tax concession, reduced expenditure on R&amp;D</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3368" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">The company should inform the field by calculating the amount of incremental expenditure for the current year of income (Y0) and the immediate prior three years of income (Y?1, Y?2, and Y?3) for the company and for all other entities with group membership periods during those four income years.  Inform with the amounts of incremental expenditures for each company in the columns labelled Y0, Y?1, Y?2, and Y?3   Total each column to determine the R&amp;D spend for each year. Ensure that incremental expenditure claimed for a consolidated group informs the relevant field once only.  Do not disaggregate incremental expenditure for each member of the consolidated group. The amount for each year must be a positive amount, otherwise the company is not eligible to claim the incremental tax concession.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3371" xlink:label="loc_DE3371"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3371" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Tax Offset  Entity Turnover Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3371" xlink:to="lbl_DE3371"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3371" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The amount of turnover of an entity that is grouped with the company at any time in the year of income</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3371" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of each entity?s aggregate Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure, and the R&amp;D group turnover respectively against the entity?s tax file number. If  certain expenditure on R&amp;D activities  cannot be deducted under the R&amp;D tax concession (for example, capital works deductions for buildings used for the purpose of carrying out R&amp;D activities) that expenditure will still form a part of the aggregate R&amp;D amount. If the relevant amounts are used  from part A to determine the aggregate R&amp;D amount of the company,  the above will need to be taken into account and any necessary adjustments made. Such adjustments relating to the aggregate R&amp;D amount should be included at amount in part B of the R&amp;D schedule. These adjustments must also be incorporated in the calculation of the aggregate R&amp;D amount of the company and R&amp;D group members  in the R&amp;D schedule. Adjustments to the R&amp;D group turnover should also be taken into account to calculate the R&amp;D group turnover recorded at that item.  If the group aggregate amount is $1,000,000 or less and the group turnover amount is less than $5,000,000, the company may choose to claim the R&amp;D tax offset.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3370" xlink:label="loc_DE3370"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3370" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Tax Offset Claim Indicator</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3370" xlink:to="lbl_DE3370"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3370" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Question to determine if the company wants to claim the R&amp;D tax offset</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3370" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">If the company chooses to take the offset, inform the Yes field with the appropriate symbol. If the company is ineligible to claim the offset, inform the No field with the appropriate symbol.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="gfagc.02.01.data.xsd#DE3568" xlink:label="loc_DE3568"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Concession Research And Development Incremental Tax Concession Reduced Expenditure Total Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3568" xlink:to="lbl_DE3568"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Incremental Tax concession, reduced expenditure on Research and Development total amount</link:label>
  </link:labelLink>
</link:linkbase>
