<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Disclaimer: http://www.sbr.gov.au/content/taxonomy_introduction_3_0.htm#Disclaimer -->
<link:linkbase xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase http://www.xbrl.org/2003/xbrl-linkbase-2003-12-31.xsd" xmlns:link="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase" xmlns:xbrli="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink">
  <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#sbrReportLabel"/>
  <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#Label"/>
  <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#reportGuidance"/>
  <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/rprt/ato/ls/ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00/labRole" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#ls.0001..02.00.lodge.requestlabLinkInfoCls"/>
  <link:labelLink xlink:type="extended" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/rprt/ato/ls/ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00/labRole">
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/py/pyde/pyde.02.00.data.xsd#DE64" xlink:label="loc_DE64"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE64" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Organisational Name Type Code</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE64" xlink:to="lbl_DE64" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/py/pyde/pyde.02.00.data.xsd#DE55" xlink:label="loc_DE55"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Name of Business Entity</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE55" xlink:to="lbl_DE55" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE55" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Name of entity - Inform the relevant field with the name of the entity. The name shown must be the same as that shown on the entity's tax return.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/py/pyid/pyid.02.00.data.xsd#DE26" xlink:label="loc_DE26"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE26" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Australian Business Number of Business Entity</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE26" xlink:to="lbl_DE26" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE26" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Australian business number (ABN)  - Inform the relevant field with the Australian Business Number (ABN), if any, of the entity.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.00.data.xsd#DE2115" xlink:label="loc_DE2115"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2115" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Whether continuity of majority ownership test passed - company and listed widely held trust only - Year of loss - Current Year</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2115" xlink:to="lbl_DE2115" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2115" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Whether continuity of majority ownership test passed - company and listed widely held trust only - Year of loss - Current Year-1</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2115" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Whether continuity of majority ownership test passed - company and listed widely held trust only - Year of loss - Current Year-2</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2115" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Whether continuity of majority ownership test passed - company and listed widely held trust only - Year of loss - Current Year-3</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2115" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Whether continuity of majority ownership test passed - company and listed widely held trust only - Year of loss - Current year-4</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2115" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Whether continuity of majority ownership test passed- company and listed widely held trust only - Current Year-5  and earlier income years</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2115" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Whether continuity of majority ownership test passed - Year of loss - Current Year - Inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol in the Yes box if, during the current income year, the entity seeks to utilise a loss of the relevant year and the entity has passed the continuity of majority ownership test - if the entity is a company, or  the 50% stake test - if the entity is a listed widely held trust in respect of the loss of that particular year.
Inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol in the No box for each year in respect of which the entity seeks to deduct a loss if the continuity of majority ownership test or the 50% stake test - as applicable - has not been satisfied in respect of that loss and the entity is required to satisfy the same business test. If there was no loss deducted (or, if applicable, not transferred in or transferred out) in respect of a particular year, leave the field next to that year blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2115" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Whether continuity of majority ownership test passed - Year of loss - Current Year-1 - Inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol if, during the current year-1 income year, the entity seeks to utilise a loss of the relevant year and the entity has passed  the continuity of majority ownership test - if the entity is a company, or the 50% stake test - if the entity is a listed widely held trust in respect of the loss of that particular year.
Inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol for each year in respect of which the entity seeks to deduct a loss if the continuity of majority ownership test or the 50% stake test - as applicable - has not been satisfied in respect of that loss and the entity is required to satisfy the same business test. If there was no loss deducted (or, if applicable, not transferred in or transferred out) in respect of a particular year, leave the field next to that year blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2115" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Whether continuity of majority ownership test passed - Year of loss - Current Year-2 - Inform the relevant field with the relevant symbol if, during the 2004-05 income year, the entity seeks to utilise a loss of the relevant year and the entity has passed the continuity of majority ownership test - if the entity is a company, or the 50% stake test - if the entity is a listed widely held trust in respect of the loss of that particular year.
Inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol for each year in respect of which the entity seeks to deduct a loss if the continuity of majority ownership test or the 50% stake test - as applicable - has not been satisfied in respect of that loss and the entity is required to satisfy the same business test. If there was no loss deducted (or, if applicable, not transferred in or transferred out) in respect of a particular year, leave the field next to that year blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2115" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Whether continuity of majority ownership test passed - Year of loss - Current Year-3 - Inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol if, during the current year-3 income year, the entity seeks to utilise a loss of the relevant year and the entity has passed  the continuity of majority ownership test - if the entity is a company, or the 50% stake test - if the entity is a listed widely held trust in respect of the loss of that particular year.
Inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol for each year in respect of which the entity seeks to deduct a loss if the continuity of majority ownership test or the 50% stake test - as applicable - has not been satisfied in respect of that loss and the entity is required to satisfy the same business test. If there was no loss deducted (or, if applicable, not transferred in or transferred out) in respect of a particular year, leave the field next to that year blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2115" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Whether continuity of majority ownership test passed - Year of loss - Current year-4 - Inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol if, during the current year-4 income years, the entity seeks to utilise a loss of the relevant year and the entity has passed the continuity of majority ownership test - if the entity is a company, or the 50% stake test - if the entity is a listed widely held trust in respect of the loss of that particular year.
Inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol for each year in respect of which the entity seeks to deduct a loss if the continuity of majority ownership test or the 50% stake test - as applicable - has not been satisfied in respect of that loss and the entity is required to satisfy the same business test. If there was no loss deducted (or, if applicable, not transferred in or transferred out) in respect of a particular year, leave the field next to that year blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2115" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Whether continuity of majority ownership test passed - Current Year-5  and earlier income years - Inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol if, during the current year-5 and earlier income years, the entity seeks to utilise a loss of the relevant year and the entity has passed the continuity of majority ownership test - if the entity is a company, or the 50% stake test - if the entity is a listed widely held trust in respect of the loss of that particular year.
Inform the relevant field with the appropriate symbol for each year in respect of which the entity seeks to deduct a loss if the continuity of majority ownership test or the 50% stake test - as applicable - has not been satisfied in respect of that loss and the entity is required to satisfy the same business test. If there was no loss deducted (or, if applicable, not transferred in or transferred out) in respect of a particular year, leave the field next to that year blank.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.00.data.xsd#DE2117" xlink:label="loc_DE2117"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2117" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - SUBTRACT Tax losses deducted - Tax losses (including convertible foreign losses) deducted during the income year under section 36-17 of the ITAA 1997.</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2117" xlink:to="lbl_DE2117" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.00.data.xsd#DE2118" xlink:label="loc_DE2118"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years - excludes film losses - Year of loss- Current Year</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2118" xlink:to="lbl_DE2118" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years- excludes film losses - Year of loss- Current Year-1</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years- excludes film losses - Year of loss- Current year-2</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years- excludes film losses-  Year of loss -Current year-3</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years - excludes film losses - Year of loss -Current year-4</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years - excludes film losses - Year of loss -Current year-5 and earlier income years</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years - excludes film losses - Total</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years - Year of loss- Current Year - Inform the relevant field with the unapplied amount of the tax loss incurred by the entity in the current income year and carried forward to later income years.eg. For the 2008-09 financial year version, the current year will be 2008-09 and the date is still visible on the form and electronic specifications. If no tax loss was incurred in the current year income year, or if the tax loss incurred in that year has been applied in full, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years - Year of loss- Current Year-1 - Inform the relevant field with the unapplied amount of the tax loss incurred by the entity in the previous 1 year income year and carried forward to later income years.eg. For the 2008-09 financial year, current year -1 will be 2007-08.  If there is no current year - 1  tax loss carried forward or if the tax loss incurred in that year has been applied in full, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years - Year of loss- Current year-2 - Inform the relevant field with the unapplied amount of the tax loss incurred by the entity in the current year-2 income year and carried forward to later income years. If no tax loss was incurred in the current year-3 income year, or if the tax loss incurred in that year has been applied in full, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years-  Year of loss -Current year-3 - Inform the relevant field with the unapplied amount of the tax loss incurred by the entity in the current year-3 income year and carried forward to later income years. If no tax loss was incurred in thecurrent year-3 income year, or if the tax loss incurred in that year has been applied in full, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years - Year of loss -Current year-4 - Inform the relevant field with the total amount of unapplied tax losses incurred by the entity in the current year-4 income years where those losses are available to be carried forward to later income years. If no tax losses were incurred in the current-4 income years, or if tax losses incurred in those years have been applied in full, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years - Year of loss -Current year-5 and earlier income years - Inform the relevant field with the total amount of unapplied tax losses incurred by the entity in the current year-5 and earlier income years where those losses are available to be carried forward to later income years. If no tax losses were incurred in the current-5 and earlier income years, or if tax losses incurred in those years have been applied in full, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2118" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses carried forward to later income years - Total - This amount is the sum total of the amounts shown at labels B, C, D, E, F and G of Part A of the losses schedule.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.00.data.xsd#DE2119" xlink:label="loc_DE2119"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2119" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Amount of losses deducted for which the continuity of majority ownership test is not passed but the same business test is satisfied - company and listed  widely held trust only - excludes film losses -  Tax losses</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2119" xlink:to="lbl_DE2119" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2119" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Amount of losses deducted for which the continuity of majority ownership test is not passed but the same business test is satisfied - Tax losses - Inform the relevant field with the amount of tax losses deducted by the entity that do not meet the continuity of majority ownership test but satisfy the same business test.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.00.data.xsd#DE2120" xlink:label="loc_DE2120"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2120" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Losses carried forward to later income years for which the same business test must be satisfied -company and listed widely held trust only - excludes film losses - Tax losses</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2120" xlink:to="lbl_DE2120" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2120" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Losses carried forward to later income years for which the same business test must be satisfied - Tax losses - Inform the relevant field with the total amount of tax losses carried forward to later income years for which the same business test must be satisfied for the entity to deduct those tax losses in later income years.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.00.data.xsd#DE2121" xlink:label="loc_DE2121"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2121" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Do current year loss provisions apply? - company and listed widely held trust only</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2121" xlink:to="lbl_DE2121" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2121" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Do current year loss provisions apply? - Inform the relevant field with the relevant symbol if the company is required to calculate its taxable income or tax loss or its net capital gain or net capital loss. Inform the relevant field with the relevant symbol if the company is not required to calculate its taxable income or tax loss or its net capital gain or net capital loss. A company is required to calculate its taxable income and tax loss where it does not satisfy the continuity of majority ownership test for the whole income year.  The current year loss provisions also apply where, during the income year, a person begins to control, or becomes able to control, the voting power in the company for the purpose or one of the purposes of gaining an advantage or gaining such a benefit for someone else.  However, the current year loss rules do not apply in either case if the same business test is satisfied.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.00.data.xsd#DE2122" xlink:label="loc_DE2122"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2122" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Has a changeover time occurred in relation to the company after 1.00 pm by legal time in the Australian Capital Territory on 11 November 1999? - Unrealised losses - company only</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2122" xlink:to="lbl_DE2122" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2122" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Has a changeover time occurred in relation to the company after 1.00 pm by legal time in the Australian Capital Territory on 11 November 1999? - If the answer is YES, inform the relevant field with the relevant symbol. If the answer is NO, inform the relevant field with the relevant symbol.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.00.data.xsd#DE2123" xlink:label="loc_DE2123"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2123" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">At the changeover time did the company satisfy the maximum net asset value test under section 152-15 of ITAA 1997? - Unrealised losses - company only</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2123" xlink:to="lbl_DE2123" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2123" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">At the changeover time did the company satisfy the maximum net asset value test under section 152-15 of ITAA 1997? - Inform the relevant field with the relevant symbol and if the answer is yes do not complete the following questions about whether the company determined it had an unrealised net loss at the changeover time or the amount of the unrealised net loss.  Inform the relevant field with the relevant symbol and answer the following question about whether the company determined it had an unrealised net loss at the changeover time. Any company that has a net value of CGT assets of $6 million or less,  at the time it failed the continuity of majority ownership test, is not subject to the operation of the maximum net asset value test. The maximum threshold amount of $6 million includes the net value of the CGT assets of the company and any entity connected or affiliated with the company.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.00.data.xsd#DE2124" xlink:label="loc_DE2124"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2124" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">If the changeover time did not satisfy the net asset value test, indicate if the company has determined it had an unrealised net loss at the changeover time - Unrealised losses - Company only</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2124" xlink:to="lbl_DE2124" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2124" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">If the changeover time did not satisfy the net asset value test, indicate if the company has determined it had an unrealised net loss at the changeover time. - Inform the relevant field with the relevant symbol and enter the amount of the unrealised net loss. Inform the relevant field with the relevant symbol and do not enter and amount at the unrealised net loss box. If a company has failed the continuity of majority ownership test on tow or more occasions since the commencement time, complete unrealised losses in respect of the unrealised net loss each time that it experiences a changeover time. The Act does not specify when a company has to calculate whether it has an unrealised net loss. However, this calculation must be done before claiming any loss or deduction on an asset that was held at the changeover time. Where no calculation has been undertaken as at the date of lodging the company's income tax return, print X in the No box and do not enter an amount at the unrealised net loss.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.00.data.xsd#DE2125" xlink:label="loc_DE2125"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2125" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">The amount of the unrealised net loss calculated under section 165-115E of ITAA 1997, if applicable - Unrealised losses - Company only</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2125" xlink:to="lbl_DE2125" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2125" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">The amount of the unrealised net loss calculated under section 165-115E of ITAA 1997, if applicable - Inform the relevant field with the amount of unrealised net loss the company has at the changeover time.   Inform the relevant field with a zero (0)  if the company has an unrealised net gain at the changeover time. An unrealised net loss is, broadly, the excess of the company's  unrealised losses on assets over unrealised gains on assets at the changeover time. This is determined by deeming such assets to be disposed of at market value at the changeover time. A company may choose to exclude every asset that it acquired for less than $10,000 from the calculation of the amount. A company may also choose to use the written down value of depreciable plant - not a building or structure - at the changeover time rather than its market value at that time provided the expenditure incurred by the company to acquire the plant was less than $1 million, and it would be reasonable for the company to conclude that the market value of the plant at the changeover time was not less than 80% of its written down value at that time. The question whether a company has an unrealised net loss at a changeover time is calculated using the steps in the method statement.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3246" xlink:label="loc_DE3246"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3246" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Losses carried forward to later income years for which the same business test must be satisfied -company and listed widely held trust only - excludes film losses -Net capital losses</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3246" xlink:to="lbl_DE3246" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3246" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Losses carried forward to later income years for which the same business test must be satisfied - Net capital losses - Inform the relevant field with the total amount of net capital losses carried forward to later income years for which the same business test must be satisfied for the company to apply those net capital losses in later income years.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3247" xlink:label="loc_DE3247"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3247" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Life Insurance Companies - Complying superannuation/FHSA class tax losses carried forward to later income years</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3247" xlink:to="lbl_DE3247" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3247" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Life Insurance Companies - Complying superannuation/FHSA class tax losses carried forward to later income years - Inform the relevant field with the amount of complying superannuation class tax losses carried forward to later income years. Generally, a life insurance company will have a tax loss of the complying superannuation//FHSA class for an income year if the company's complying superannuation deductions for that income year exceed the sum of the complying superannuation/FHSA assessable income for that income year, and net exempt income for the income year that is attributable.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3248" xlink:label="loc_DE3248"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3248" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Life Insurance Companies - Complying superannuation/FHSA net capital losses carried forward to later income years</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3248" xlink:to="lbl_DE3248" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3248" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Life Insurance Companies - Complying superannuation/FHSA net capital losses carried forward to later income years - Inform the relevant field with the amount of complying superannuation/FHSA net capital losses carried forward to later income years. Generally, a life insurance company will have a tax loss for an income year if the life company's deductions for that income year exceed the sum of the assessable income for that income year, and net exempt income for the income year that is attributable to the complying superannuation/FHSA assets.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3249" xlink:label="loc_DE3249"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3249" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses - Controlled foreign company (CFC) losses - CFC losses deducted</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3249" xlink:to="lbl_DE3249" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3249" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses - Controlled foreign company (CFC) losses - CFC losses deducted - Inform the relevant field with the total of the entity's share of losses of CFCs, if any, from statutory accounting periods that end within prior income years, that have been claimed as notional allowable deductions for statutory accounting periods that end within the current income year.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3250" xlink:label="loc_DE3250"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3250" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Controlled foreign company (CFC) losses - CFC losses carried forward</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3250" xlink:to="lbl_DE3250" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3250" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Controlled foreign company (CFC) losses - CFC losses carried forward - Inform the relevant field with the total amount of the entity's share of losses of CFCs, if any, that is available to be carried forward to statutory accounting periods that end in later income years.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3251" xlink:label="loc_DE3251"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3251" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses - less Loss amount attributable to non-assessable non exempt income - Companies only</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3251" xlink:to="lbl_DE3251" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3251" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses - less Loss amount attributable to non-assessable non exempt income - Companies only - Show loss amount attributable to non assessable non exempt income ie. Foreign loss</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3252" xlink:label="loc_DE3252"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3252" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses - All other foreign source income, excluding CFC losses, Less - Loss amount attributable to non-assessable non-exempt income - companies only (Net all other foreign source income)</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3252" xlink:to="lbl_DE3252" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3252" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses -subtotal of "Less Loss amount attributable to non-assessable non exempt income - Companies only"  and  "Foreign source losses - All other foreign source income" - Subtract amount of "Less Loss amount attributable to non-assessable non exempt income - Companies only"  from  "Foreign source losses - All other foreign source income"</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3253" xlink:label="loc_DE3253"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3253" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses - Total of Interest income losses, modified passive income losses, offshore banking income losses and net all other foreign source income losses (Total assessable foreign source income losses), excluding CFC losses</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3253" xlink:to="lbl_DE3253" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3253" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses -total of "Foreign source losses - Interest income" + "Foreign source losses - Modified passive income" + "Foreign source losses - Offshore banking income" + "amount of Less Loss amount attributable to non-assessable non exempt income - Companies only  from D  Foreign source losses - All other foreign source income" - Total of A "Foreign source losses - Interest income" + "Foreign source losses - Modified passive income" +  "Foreign source losses - Offshore banking income" +  "amount of Less Loss amount attributable to non-assessable non exempt income - Companies only  from Foreign source losses - All other foreign source income"</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3254" xlink:label="loc_DE3254"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3254" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses - 50% of Total assessable foreign source income losses that were incurred for the 1998-99 to 2000-2001 income years (Starting Total), excluding CFC losses</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3254" xlink:to="lbl_DE3254" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3254" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses- 50% of losses at Total of "Foreign source losses - Interest income" +  "Foreign source losses - Modified passive income" +  "Foreign source losses - Offshore banking income" +  "amount of Less Loss amount attributable to non-assessable non exempt income - Companies only  from   Foreign source losses - All other foreign source income" that were incurred for the income years older than 7 but less than 10 - 50% of losses at Total of A "Foreign source losses - Interest income" +  "Foreign source losses - Modified passive income" +  "Foreign source losses - Offshore banking income" +  "amount of Less Loss amount attributable to non-assessable non exempt income - Companies only  from   Foreign source losses - All other foreign source income" that were incurred for the income years older than 7 but less than 10</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3255" xlink:label="loc_DE3255"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3255" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses - Total amount of convertible foreign losses reduced where choice made to limit the starting total to $10,000, excluding CFC losses</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3255" xlink:to="lbl_DE3255" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3255" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses - total amount of convertible foreign losses reduced where choice made to limit the starting total of $10,000 - Total amount of convertible foreign losses reduced where choice made to limit the starting total of $10,000</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3256" xlink:label="loc_DE3256"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3256" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses - Total convertible foreign losses income - Total assessable foreign source income less starting total and less the total amount of convertible foreign losses reduced where the choice is made to limit the starting total to $10,000, excluding CFC losses</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3256" xlink:to="lbl_DE3256" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3256" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses - starting total for convertible foreign losses - Total of  "Foreign source losses - Interest income" +  "Foreign source losses - Modified passive income" +  "Foreign source losses - Offshore banking income" +  "amount of Less Loss amount attributable to non-assessable non exempt income - Companies only  from   Foreign source losses - All other foreign source income" less 50% of losses at Total of  "Foreign source losses - Interest income" +  "Foreign source losses - Modified passive income" +  "Foreign source losses - Offshore banking income" +  "amount of Less Loss amount attributable to non-assessable non exempt income - Companies only  from Foreign source losses - All other foreign source  + Total amount of convertible foreign losses reduced where choice made to limit the starting total of $10,000</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3257" xlink:label="loc_DE3257"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3257" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign loss component of a tax loss - excludes losses of CFCs - Foreign loss component of tax losses deducted - included at the tax losses deducted label of your tax return</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3257" xlink:to="lbl_DE3257" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3257" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign loss component of a tax loss-excludes losses of CFCs
Foreign loss component of tax losses deducted - include the tax losses deducted on your tax return - Foreign loss component of a tax loss-excludes losses of CFCs
Foreign loss component of tax losses deducted - include the tax losses deducted on your tax return</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3258" xlink:label="loc_DE3258"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3258" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign loss component of a tax loss - excludes losses of CFCs - Foreign loss component of tax losses carried forward - included at the tax losses carried forward to later income years on your tax return</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3258" xlink:to="lbl_DE3258" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3258" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign loss component of a tax loss-excludes losses of CFCs
Foreign loss component of tax losses carried forward - included at the tax losses carried forward to later income years on your tax return - Foreign loss component of tax losses carried forward - included at the tax losses carried forward to later income years on your tax return</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3260" xlink:label="loc_DE3260"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3260" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses - Controlled foreign company losses - Convertible CFC losses - The total of the entity's share of convertible CFC losses for the earlier statutory accounting periods</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3260" xlink:to="lbl_DE3260" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3260" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Controlled foreign company losses - Convertible CFC losses - Show  the total of the entity's share of convertible CFC losses for the earlier statutory accounting periods</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3261" xlink:label="loc_DE3261"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3261" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - Balance of the undeducted and not transferred amount of tax losses, excluding net capital losses and film losses, brought forward from the prior income year</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3261" xlink:to="lbl_DE3261" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3261" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - Balance of tax losses brought forward from prior year - The undeducted and not transferred - amount of tax losses incurred by the entity and brought forward to the current  income year under section 36-17 of the ITAA 1997.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3262" xlink:label="loc_DE3262"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3262" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - ADD Amount of overall foreign losses converted to tax losses, excluding capital losses, net capital losses and film losses, in the current year</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3262" xlink:to="lbl_DE3262" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3262" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - ADD Amount of convertible foreign losses - Any overall foreign losses (excluding capital losses) converted to tax losses in the current year.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3264" xlink:label="loc_DE3264"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3264" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - SUBTRACT Amount of net forgiven debt applied to reduce tax losses, excluding net capital losses and film losses</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3264" xlink:to="lbl_DE3264" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3264" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - SUBTRACT Net forgiven amount of debt - Tax losses brought forward are reduced by any commercial debt forgiveness amounts (Division 245 of Schedule 2C to the ITAA 1936).  If a commercial debt owed by the company is forgiven during the income year, apply the net amount of debts forgiven to reduce the company's deductible revenue losses, net capital losses, certain undeducted revenue or capital expenditure and the cost base of CGT assets, in that order.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3265" xlink:label="loc_DE3265"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3265" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - ADD Tax loss, excluding net capital losses and film losses, incurred during current year, disregarding net exempt income and excess franking credit</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3265" xlink:to="lbl_DE3265" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3265" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - ADD Tax loss incurred (if any) during current year - There is a limit on the total of the amount you can deduct for the income year for gifts and contributions (section 26-55 of the ITAA 1997). A tax loss cannot be produced or increased by the deduction allowable under Division 30 of the ITAA 1997, which is about deductions for gifts or contributions.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3266" xlink:label="loc_DE3266"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3266" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - ADD Tax loss amount, excluding net capital losses and film losses, from conversion of excess franking offsets</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3266" xlink:to="lbl_DE3266" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3266" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - ADD Tax loss amount from conversion of excess franking offsets - If the entity has excess franking offsets, it must convert the excess franking offsets into an amount of tax loss to carry forward to later income years. You convert the amount of excess franking offsets into a tax loss by dividing the excess franking offsets amount by the corporate tax rate which gives you the tax loss amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3267" xlink:label="loc_DE3267"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3267" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - SUBTRACT Net exempt income to be taken into account in calculating the company's tax loss or carried forward tax loss, excluding net capital losses and film losses</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3267" xlink:to="lbl_DE3267" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3267" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - SUBTRACT Net exempt income - You are required to first deduct a prior year tax loss from any net exempt income in the later income year. If the entity has:
* net exempt income; and 
* assessable income exceeds allowable deductions (other than the tax loss), 
the tax loss has to be first applied against net exempt income and then the entity can deduct the amount of the tax loss (if any remains) that it chooses subject to limitation. (subsection 36-17(3) of the ITAA 1997).

Conversely, if the entity has:
* net exempt income; and 
* allowable deductions (other than the tax loss) exceed assessable income, 
that excess must be applied against net exempt income and then the tax loss must be applied against any net exempt income that remains. (subsection 36-17(4) of the ITAA 1997).</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3268" xlink:label="loc_DE3268"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3268" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - SUBTRACT Tax losses forgone, excluding net capital losses and film losses</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3268" xlink:to="lbl_DE3268" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3268" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - SUBTRACT Tax losses forgone - A company cannot deduct a tax loss unless: 
   (a) it has the same owners and the same control throughout the period from the start of the loss year to the end of the income year; or 
   (b) it satisfies the same business test by carrying on the same business, entering into no new kinds of transactions and conducting no new kinds of business. See Subdivision 165-A of the ITAA 1997.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3269" xlink:label="loc_DE3269"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3269" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - SUBTRACT Tax losses, excluding net capital losses and film losses,  transferred out under Subdivision 170-A of the ITAA 1997</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3269" xlink:to="lbl_DE3269" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3269" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - SUBTRACT Tax losses transferred out under Subdivision 170-A (only for transfers involving a foreign bank branch or a PE of a foreign financial entity) - The amount of tax losses transferred out by the company to group companies under Subdivision 170-A of the ITAA 1997
A group company may transfer the whole or a part of a tax loss to another company where:
   * both companies are members of the same wholly-owned group, and
   * one of the companies is:
        - an Australian branch of a foreign bank, or
        - an Australian PE of a foreign financial entity if the tax loss is for an income year commencing on or after 26 June 2005, and
   *the other company is: 
       - the head company of a consolidated group or MEC group, or
       - not a member of a consolidatable group, and
   *the further conditions in Subdivision 170-A of the ITAA 1997 are satisfied.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3270" xlink:label="loc_DE3270"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3270" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - Total tax losses carried forward to later income years</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3270" xlink:to="lbl_DE3270" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3270" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Tax losses reconciliation statement - Total tax losses carried forward to later income years - The total of tax losses carried forward to later income years.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3327" xlink:label="loc_DE3327"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3327" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Amount of losses deducted for which the continuity of majority ownership test is not passed but the same business test is satisfied - company and listed  widely held trust only - excludes film losses - Net capital losses</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3327" xlink:to="lbl_DE3327" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3327" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Amount of losses deducted for which the continuity of majority ownership test is not passed but the same business test is satisfied - Net capital losses - Inform the relevant field with the amount of net capital losses applied by a company that do not meet the continuity of majority ownership test but satisfies the same business test.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3328" xlink:label="loc_DE3328"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3328" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses carried forward - excludes losses of CFCs- Interest income</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3328" xlink:to="lbl_DE3328" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3328" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses carried forward - excludes losses of CFCs - Modified passive income</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3328" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses carried forward - excludes losses of CFCs - Offshore banking income</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3328" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses carried forward - excludes losses of CFCs - All other foreign source income</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3328" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses carried forward - excludes losses of CFCs- Interest income  - Inform the relevant field with the amount of foreign source loss, if any, relating to Interest income that is available to be carried forward to later income years.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3328" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses carried forward - excludes losses of CFCs - Modified passive income  - Inform the relevant field with the amount of foreign source loss, if any, relating to Modified passive income that is available to be carried forward to later income years.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3328" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses carried forward - excludes losses of CFCs - Offshore banking income - Inform the relevant field with the amount of foreign source loss, if any, relating to Interest income that is available to be carried forward to later income years.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3328" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Foreign source losses carried forward - excludes losses of CFCs - All other foreign source income  - Inform the relevant field with the amount of foreign source loss, if any, relating to all other foreign source income that is available to be carried forward to later income years.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="../../../../sbr_au_taxonomy/icls/rvc/rvctc/rvctc3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3329" xlink:label="loc_DE3329"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years - excludes film losses - Year of loss-Current year</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3329" xlink:to="lbl_DE3329" order="1.0"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years - excluding film losses - Year of loss -Current year-1</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years - excluding film losses - Year of loss -Current Year-2</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years - excludes film losses - Year of loss- Current year-3</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years- excluding film losses - Year of loss - Current year-4</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years - Excludes film losses -  Year of loss -Current year-5 and earlier income years</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years - Excludes film losses - Total</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years - Year of loss-Current year - Inform the relevant field with the amount of any unapplied net capital loss made by the entity in the current income year that can be carried forward and applied to reduce capital gains in later income years. If there is no net capital loss from the current income year available to be carried forward to later income years, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years - Year of loss -Current year-1 - Inform the relevant field with the amount of any unapplied net capital loss made by the entity in the current year-1 income year that can be carried forward and applied to reduce capital gains in later income years. If no net capital loss was made in the current year-1 income year, or if the net capital loss made in that year has been applied in full, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years - Year of loss -Current Year-2 - Inform the relevant field with the amount of any unapplied net capital loss made by the entity in the current year-2 income year that can be carried forward and applied to reduce capital gains in later income years. If no net capital loss was made in the current year-2 income year, or if the net capital loss made in that year has been applied in full, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years - Year of loss- Current year-3 - Inform the relevant field with the amount of any unapplied net capital loss made by the entity in the current year -3 income year that can be carried forward and applied to reduce capital gains in later income years.  If no net capital loss was made in the current year -3 income year, or if the net capital loss made in that year has been applied in full, leave the field  blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years - Year of loss - Current year-4 - Inform the relevant field with the amount of any unapplied net capital losses made by the entity in the current year-4 income years that can be carried forward and applied to reduce capital gains in later income years. If no net capital losses were made in the current year-4 income years, or if net capital losses made in those years have been applied in full, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years - Year of loss -Current year-5 and earlier income years - Inform the relevant field with the amount of any unapplied net capital loss made by the entity in the current year-5 income year that can be carried forward and applied to reduce capital gains in later income years. If there is no net capital loss from the current year-5 income year available to be carried forward to later income years, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3329" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/reportGuidance" xml:lang="en">Net capital losses carried forward to later income years - Total - This amount is the sum total of the amounts shown at labels H, I, J, K, L and M of Part A of the losses schedule.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1295" xlink:label="loc_RA1295"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1295" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">LSLodgeRequest [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1295" xlink:to="lbl_RA1295" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1297" xlink:label="loc_RA1297"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1297" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">Report [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1297" xlink:to="lbl_RA1297" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1296" xlink:label="loc_RA1296"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1296" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1296" xlink:to="lbl_RA1296" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1461" xlink:label="loc_RA1461"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1461" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.AllOtherForeignSourceIncome [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1461" xlink:to="lbl_RA1461" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1458" xlink:label="loc_RA1458"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1458" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.InterestIncome [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1458" xlink:to="lbl_RA1458" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1459" xlink:label="loc_RA1459"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1459" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.ModifiedPassiveIncome [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1459" xlink:to="lbl_RA1459" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1460" xlink:label="loc_RA1460"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1460" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.OffshoreBankingIncome [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1460" xlink:to="lbl_RA1460" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1462" xlink:label="loc_RA1462"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1462" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.SumAmount [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1462" xlink:to="lbl_RA1462" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1469" xlink:label="loc_RA1469"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1469" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.Y0Minus10SAP [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1469" xlink:to="lbl_RA1469" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1452" xlink:label="loc_RA1452"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1452" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.Y0 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1452" xlink:to="lbl_RA1452" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1463" xlink:label="loc_RA1463"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1463" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.Y0.Neg [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1463" xlink:to="lbl_RA1463" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1453" xlink:label="loc_RA1453"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1453" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.Y0Minus1 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1453" xlink:to="lbl_RA1453" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1464" xlink:label="loc_RA1464"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1464" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.Y0Minus1.Neg [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1464" xlink:to="lbl_RA1464" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1454" xlink:label="loc_RA1454"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1454" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.Y0Minus2 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1454" xlink:to="lbl_RA1454" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1465" xlink:label="loc_RA1465"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1465" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.Y0Minus2.Neg [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1465" xlink:to="lbl_RA1465" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1455" xlink:label="loc_RA1455"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1455" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.Y0Minus3 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1455" xlink:to="lbl_RA1455" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1466" xlink:label="loc_RA1466"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1466" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.Y0Minus3.Neg [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1466" xlink:to="lbl_RA1466" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1456" xlink:label="loc_RA1456"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1456" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.Y0Minus4 [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1456" xlink:to="lbl_RA1456" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1467" xlink:label="loc_RA1467"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1467" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.Y0Minus4.Neg [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1467" xlink:to="lbl_RA1467" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1457" xlink:label="loc_RA1457"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1457" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.Y0Minus5Plus [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1457" xlink:to="lbl_RA1457" order="1.0"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="ls.0001.lodge.request.02.00.report.xsd#RA1468" xlink:label="loc_RA1468"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_RA1468" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/rprt/Label" xml:lang="en">ReportingParty.Y0Minus5Plus.Neg [Abstract]</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_RA1468" xlink:to="lbl_RA1468" order="1.0"/>
  </link:labelLink>
</link:linkbase>
