<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Disclaimer: http://www.sbr.gov.au/content/taxonomy_introduction_3_0.htm#Disclaimer -->
<link:linkbase xmlns:link="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xbrli="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance">
    <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#businessDefinition"/>
    <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#dataElementGuidance"/>
    <link:labelLink xlink:type="extended" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/link">
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#bafot.02.02_bafotAbstract" xlink:label="loc_bafot.02.02_bafotAbstract"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_bafotAbstract" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Other Accounting And Financial Disclosures</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_bafot.02.02_bafotAbstract" xlink:to="lbl_bafotAbstract"/>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3419" xlink:label="loc_DE3419"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3419" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Ability To Directly Or Indirectly Control Or Direct A Non Resident Trust Indicator</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3419" xlink:to="lbl_DE3419"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3419" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicator to determine whether the entity was able to control or direct (directly or indirectly) a non-resident trust estate.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3419" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field whether the entity was able to control a non-resident trust estate at any time during the income year.
Unless otherwise specified, the terms used in items 14 to 19 have the same meaning as set out in Divisions 6 and 6AAA of the Income Tax Assessment Act 1936.
Control in relation to a trust estate is defined in section 102AAG of the Income Tax Assessment Act 1936. Answer this element either in the affirmative or the negative.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3412" xlink:label="loc_DE3412"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3412" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Accumulated Losses Transferred From Controlled Foreign Company Or Controlled Foreign Trust Of Unlisted Country To Related Entity In Listed Country Indicator</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3412" xlink:to="lbl_DE3412"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3412" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicator to determine whether transfers of accumulated losses were made from any unlisted country Controlled Foreign Company or Controlled Foreign Trust to a related entity in a listed country.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3411" xlink:label="loc_DE3411"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3411" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Accumulated Profits Transferred From Controlled Foreign Company Or Controlled Foreign Trust Of Unlisted Country To Related Entity In Listed Country Indicator</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3411" xlink:to="lbl_DE3411"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3411" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicator to determine whether transfers of accumulated profits were made from any unlisted country Controlled Foreign Company or Controlled Foreign Trust to a related entity in a listed country.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3411" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field whether or not transfers of accumulated profits were made from any unlisted countries Controlled Foreign Company or controlled Foreign Trust to a related entity in a listed country during the year of income?
Transfer includes sale, acquisition, gift, deed of assignment, declaration</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3397" xlink:label="loc_DE3397"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3397" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Acquisitions And Disposals Pricing Method Code</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3397" xlink:to="lbl_DE3397"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3397" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The method used for pricing acquisitions and disposals where the reporting party acquired capital assets from, or disposed of capital assests to related parties.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3397" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the appropriate code.
1 = Nil consideration, 2 = Cost price, 3 = Written-down value, 4 = Discounted cash flow, 5 = Director?s valuation, 6 = Independent valuation, 7 = Quoted market price, 8 = Other methods
Where you have acquired capital assets from, or have disposed of capital assets to international related parties, use the codes to indicate the four principal methods you used for pricing those acquisitions or disposals. Use the codes to list the four principal methods used for pricing acquisitions and disposals you used, in descending order of total dollar value, starting at the left hand side. If you used fewer than four methods leave the remaining spaces blank.

Cost price refers to the price the seller originally paid for the asset, including ancillary costs such as freight or handling. Written-down value refers to a pricing method based on either the taxation ?adjustable value? or accounting residual value after depreciation has been allowed. Discounted cash flow is a pricing method where the price of an asset is based on the discounted cash flow at the time of acquisition or disposal. Director?s valuation refers to a pricing method that is based on the directors? opinion of an asset?s value, and not on any of the methods listed in codes 1 to 8. Independent valuation is a pricing method by which a suitably qualified person, acting at arm?s length to both the buyer and seller, assesses the value of an asset. Quoted market price refers to a price quoted on a public listed market, such as a public stock exchange, or commodities market. Other methods means any other pricing method that is not mentioned here.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3536" xlink:label="loc_DE3536"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3536" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Arms Length Pricing Method Code</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3536" xlink:to="lbl_DE3536"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3536" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The arm's length pricing method used to set or review consideration of a revenue (non-capital) nature.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3536" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field of  the four principal methods in descending order of total dollar value, using the appropriate code. See the ATO website for an explanation of the methods in Taxation Ruling TR 97/20 and Taxation Ruling TR 1999/1. 

1 = Comparable uncontrolled price (CUP) method, 2 = Resale price method, 3 = Cost-plus method, 4 = Profit split method, 5 = Transactional net margin method, 6 = Marginal costing, 7 = Cost-contribution arrangement, 8 = Apportionment of costs, 9 = Apportionment of income, 10 = Fixed mark-up applied to cost, 11 = Fixed percentage of resale price, 12 = Other arm's length methods. 

In order to establish appropriate arm's length pricing under a particular method, a sampling of the dealings may be sufficient if carried out according to accepted statistical practice. Note that where total dollar value of related-party dealings is to be calculated, these dealings should not be 'netted off' (other than in the case of certain derivative instruments). That is, do not set off incomings and outgoings against each other to result in a lesser amount. Instead, add the amounts, both income derived and expenses incurred, to obtain the sum total of all such dealings.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3416" xlink:label="loc_DE3416"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3416" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Beneficiary Of Non Resident Trust Estate Indicator</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3416" xlink:to="lbl_DE3416"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3416" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicator to determine whether the reporting party was a beneficiary of a non-resident trust estate.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3416" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field whether the entity was a beneficiary of a non- resident trust estate at nay time during the year of income.
Unless otherwise specified, the terms used in items 14 to 19 have the same meaning as set out in Divisions 6 and 6AAA of ITAA 1936. This item asks whether the entity was a beneficiary of a non-resident trust estate at any time during the year of income.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3398" xlink:label="loc_DE3398"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3398" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Capital Nature Percentage Bracket Dollar Value Code</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3398" xlink:to="lbl_DE3398"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3398" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Total of acquisitions and disposals as a percentage of the dollar value of related party dealings of both a revenue and capital nature.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3398" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the appropriate code.
1 = 0% , 2 = 1% to less than 25%, 3 = 25% to less than 50%, 4 = 50% to less than 75%, 5 = 75% to less than 100%, 6 = 100%
Identify the percentage of your related-party international dealings that are capital in nature. Use the codes listed to indicate the total dollar value of the related party international dealings of a non-revenue (capital) nature as a percentage of total dollar value of related party international dealings of a revenue and non-revenue (capital and non-capital) nature referred to in elements:
- Tangible property,
- Royalties, rent and intangible property,
- Services and
- Other only.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3396" xlink:label="loc_DE3396"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3396" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Capital Nature Indicator</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3396" xlink:to="lbl_DE3396"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3396" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicator to determine whether the reporting party had any related party dealings of a non-revenue (capital) nature in which you acquired an interest in an asset, or a Capital Gains Tax event occurred (including disposal).</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3396" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the appropriate code to answer the question.
This question requires a yes or no answer. You should answer yes if you have acquired an interest in an asset as a result of dealings of a non-revenue (capital) nature with international related parties, or if you have had dealings with an international related party that would be classified as a CGT event in terms of Part 3-1 of the Income Tax Assessment Act 1997. The words ?acquired?, ?CGT event?, ?disposal? and ?asset? are used in this item within the context of Part 3-1 of the Income Tax Assessment Act 1997. The question does not refer to trading stock held in the ordinary course of business.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3401" xlink:label="loc_DE3401"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3401" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Direct Or Indirect Interest In Controlled Foreign Companies And Controlled Foreign Trusts Count</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3401" xlink:to="lbl_DE3401"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3401" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The number of controlled foreign companies and controlled foreign trusts where the reporting party had either a direct or indirect interest.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3401" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Determine whether the controlled foreign companies and controlled foreign trusts are residents of listed countries, section 404 countries or unlisted countries.
Inform the field of the total number of controlled foreign companies and controlled foreign trusts at the start of the entity?s accounting period.
If the number of controlled foreign companies and controlled foreign trusts is less than 10, show 0 (zero) as the first digit. If the number of controlled foreign companies and controlled foreign trusts is more than 99, show 99. If the number of controlled foreign companies and controlled foreign trusts is zero, leave blank.
Listed countries are listed in Part 2 of Schedule 10 of the Income Tax Regulations, see the ATO website for the relevant detail.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3421" xlink:label="loc_DE3421"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3421" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Exempt Interest In Foreign Investment Funds Or Foreign Life Policies Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3421" xlink:to="lbl_DE3421"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3421" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The value of interests held in foreign investment funds or foreign life policies that are exempt under the specified sections of the ITAA 1936.

An interest in a foreign investment fund that is a foreign company is:
(a) a share in the company other than an eligible finance share within the meaning of section 327; or
(b) an option, convertible note, or other instrument, that confers an entitlement to acquire such a share.

An interest in a foreign investment fund that is a foreign trust is:
(a) an interest in the corpus or income of the trust (including, in the case of a unit trust, an interest constituted by a unit in the unit trust); or
(b) an option, convertible note, or other instrument, that confers an entitlement to acquire an interest referred to in paragraph (a).

A person has an interest in a foreign life policy if the person has the legal title to the foreign life policy and, if only one person has the legal title to the foreign life policy, a reference in this Part to the person's interest or interests in the foreign life policy is taken to be a reference to the foreign life policy.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3421" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field of the amounts relating to the current value, at the end of the notional accounting period of interests held in foreign investment funds or foreign life policies that are exempt under the specified sections of ITAA 1936.
The  codes correspond to the various sections of ITAA 1936. Show only principal 10 in descending order of total dollar value.
FIF is defined in section 481 of ITAA 1936. FLP is defined in section 482 of ITAA 1936. Interest in a FIF or FLP is defined in section 483 of ITAA 1936. Notional accounting period in respect of a FIF is defined in section 486 of ITAA 1936. Notional accounting period in respect of an FLP is defined in section 487 of ITAA 1936.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3420" xlink:label="loc_DE3420"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3420" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Exempt Interest In Foreign Investment Funds Or Foreign Life Policies Code</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3420" xlink:to="lbl_DE3420"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3420" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Interests held in foreign investment funds or foreign life policies that are exempt under sections of ITAA 1936. The  codes correspond to the various sections of ITAA 1936.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3420" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the following code values:
01 = 497 Interests in a foreign company engaged in eligible company activities 
02 = 503 Interests in a foreign bank
03 = 504 Interests in a foreign holding company of a foreign bank
04 = 506 Interests in a foreign life insurance company
05 = 507A Interests in a foreign holding company of a foreign life insurance company
06 = 509 Interests in a foreign general insurance company
07 = 509A Interests in a foreign holding company of a foreign general insurance company
08 = 511 Interests in a foreign company engaged in certain activities
09 = 511A Interests in a foreign holding company of a foreign real property company
10 = 513 Interests in certain USA entities
11 = 515 Interests of less than $50,000
12 = 519B Exemption for complying superannuation entities, certain assets of life insurance companies and certain fixed trusts
13 = 521 Interests that are trading stock
14 = 523 Interests in a foreign company principally engaged in several activities
15 = 523A Interests in a foreign holding company of a foreign mixed activity company
16 = 525 Interests not exceeding 10% of the value of all FIF interests
17 = 527 Certain interests of underwriting members of Lloyd?sInform the relevant field the codes relating to the current value, at the end of the notional accounting period of interests held in foreign investment funds or foreign life policies that are exempt under the specified sections of ITAA 1936.
The  codes correspond to the various sections of ITAA 1936. Show only principal 10 in descending order of total dollar value.
FIF is defined in section 481 of ITAA 1936. FLP is defined in section 482 of ITAA 1936. Interest in a FIF or FLP is defined in section 483 of ITAA 1936. Notional accounting period in respect of a FIF is defined in section 486 of ITAA 1936. Notional accounting period in respect of an FLP is defined in section 487 of ITAA 1936.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3563" xlink:label="loc_DE3563"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3563" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Functional Currency Code</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3563" xlink:to="lbl_DE3563"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3563" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">If the company keeps its accounts solely or predominantly in a foreign currency (its applicable functional currency) and has elected to use that functional currency for its tax accounts which it then translates to Australian dollars (A$) to complete its t</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3392" xlink:label="loc_DE3392"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3392" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Income And Expense Items Step One And Two Of Taxation Ruling Percentage Bracket Code</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3392" xlink:to="lbl_DE3392"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3392" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The percentage of the total dollar value of related-party dealings excluding loans, where it relates to documentation of steps 1 and 2 (characterisation and selection) of Taxation Ruling TR 98/11.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3392" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the appropriate code.
1 = 0% , 2 = 1% to less than 25%, 3 = 25% to less than 50%, 4 = 50% to less than 75%, 5 = 75% to less than 100%, 6 = 100%
Use one of the numeric codes to state the percentage of the total dollar value of related-party international dealings:
- Tangible property,
- Royalties, rent and intangible property,
- Services and
- Other only;
for which you have written documentation supporting your processes in steps 1 and 2 (characterisation and selection) of chapter 5 of Taxation Ruling TR 98/11 - see the ATO website.
Note that the calculations need only be sufficient to allow the percentage range to be estimated or determined. However, this estimating process must be based on rational and objective premises.
A statistical sample may be an appropriate method of calculating the relevant percentage, provided the sample selection and mathematical considerations are consistent with generally accepted statistical methods.
Keep your working papers if you have used a sampling process to make this estimate.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3393" xlink:label="loc_DE3393"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3393" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Income And Expense Items Step Three Taxation Of Ruling Percentage Bracket Code</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3393" xlink:to="lbl_DE3393"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3393" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The percentage of the total dollar value of related-party dealings excluding loans, where it relates to documentation step 3 of Taxation Ruling TR 98/11.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3393" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the appropriate code.
1 = 0% , 2 = 1% to less than 25%, 3 = 25% to less than 50%, 4 = 50% to less than 75%, 5 = 75% to less than 100%, 6 = 100%
Use one of the codes shown in item  - Step 1 and step 2 of Taxation Ruling TR 98/11 - to state the percentage of the total dollar value of related-party international dealings identified in:
- Tangible property,
- Royalties, rent and intangible property,
- Services and
- Other only.
You should have written  documentation supporting your processes in step 3 of chapter 5 of Taxation Ruling TR 98/11 - see ATO website.
You need only estimate the percentage, provided the estimate is objectively and rationally determined. Use, for example, a sampling
technique based on accepted statistical methods. Keep your working papers that relate to this item.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3417" xlink:label="loc_DE3417"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3417" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Interest In Or Entitlement To Acquire Interest In Non Resident Trust Estate Indicator</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3417" xlink:to="lbl_DE3417"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3417" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicator to determine whether the reporting party had an interest in a non-resident trust estate, or was entitled to acquire an interest in a non-resident trust estate.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3417" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field whether of not the entity had an interest in a non-resident, or was entitled to acquire an interest in a non-resident trust estate, at any time during the year of income.
Unless otherwise specified, the terms used in items 14 to 19 have the same meaning as set out in Divisions 6 and 6AAA of the Income Tax Assessment Act 1936.
This item asks whether the entity had an interest in a non-resident trust estate, or was entitled to acquire an interest in a non-resident trust estate, at any time during the income year. ?Entitled to acquire? has the same meaning as set out in section 322 of Part X of the ITAA 1936.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3379" xlink:label="loc_DE3379"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3379" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous International Dealing  Main Business Activity Carried Out With International Related Party Excluding Loan Amount</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3379" xlink:to="lbl_DE3379"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3379" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">International transactions, agreements or arrangements between related parties, between a permanent establishment and its head office or between two permanent establishments of the same entity. It includes all transactions between an Australian resident and its international related parties.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3399" xlink:label="loc_DE3399"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3399" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Non Resident Participation In Capital Management Or Control Of Reporting Party Indicator</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3399" xlink:to="lbl_DE3399"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3399" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicator to determine whether a non-resident party directly or indirectly participated in the reporting party's capital, management or control. To participate in the reporting party's capital, a non-resident party must have an equity interest of 10% or greater in that reporting party.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3399" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the appropriate code to answer the question.
Advise whether any non-resident has participated in the capital, management or control of the company in this year. ?Participating in the capital? means having an equity interest of 10% or greater in the company. You are required to respond with yes or no.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3400" xlink:label="loc_DE3400"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3400" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Number of Related Parties Count</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3400" xlink:to="lbl_DE3400"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3400" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The number of international related parties where the dealings were international transactions, agreements or arrangements between related parties, between a permanent establishment and its head office or between two permanent establishments of the same reporting party.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3400" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the number of international related parties with which you had dealings during the year. ?International related parties? are parties (including subsidiaries and permanent establishments) whose international dealings can be subject to Division 13 of the Income Tax Assessment Act 1936.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3414" xlink:label="loc_DE3414"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3414" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Other Assets And Reserves Transferred From Controlled Foreign Company Or Controlled Foreign Trust Of Unlisted Country To Related Entity In Listed Country Indicator</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3414" xlink:to="lbl_DE3414"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3414" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicator to determine whether transfers of other assets or reserves were made from any unlisted country Controlled Foreign Company or Controlled Foreign Trust to a related entity in a listed country.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3414" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field whether or not transfers of other assets or reserves were made from any unlisted countries Controlled Foreign Company or Controlled Foreign Trust to a related entity in a listed country during the year of income? 
Transfer includes sale, acquisition, gift, deed of assignment, declaration or trust or otherwise, with or without consideration ? monetary or non-monetary.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3413" xlink:label="loc_DE3413"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3413" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Paid Up Capital Transferred From Controlled Foreign Company Or Controlled Foreign Trust Of Unlisted Country To Related Entity In Listed Country Indicator</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3413" xlink:to="lbl_DE3413"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3413" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicator to determine whether transfers of paid up capital were made from any unlisted country Controlled Foreign Company or Controlled Foreign Trust to a related entity in a listed country.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3413" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field whether or not transfers of accumulated losses were made from any unlisted countries Controlled Foreign Company or Controlled Foreign Trust to a related entity in a listed country during the year of income? 
Transfer includes sale, acquisition, gift, deed of assignment, declaration or trust or otherwise, with or without consideration ? monetary or non-monetary.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3391" xlink:label="loc_DE3391"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3391" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Provided Services Property Processes Rights Or Obligations For NonMonetary Consideration Indicator</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3391" xlink:to="lbl_DE3391"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3391" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicator to determine whether the reporting party has made any provision of services, transfer of assets (both tangible and intangible) or any similar dealings for which they received no consideration.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3391" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the appropriate code to answer the question.
A 'Y' answer would also be required where an Australian company owned a trademark that it allowed an international related party to use without payment.
A permanent establishment should be regarded as a separate, but related, party to that of the head office for the purposes of this item. Where there is no charge or adjustment allocating income or expenditure between the parties for a provision of services, transfer of property, or other transactions listed on Schedule 25A by:
- the head office to the permanent establishment, or
- the permanent establishment to the head office or another related international party,
this will be regarded as being for nil consideration. 
Where you have disclosed an outbound interest-free loan at amounts loaned on Schedule 25A, the answer 'Y' is not required.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3390" xlink:label="loc_DE3390"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3390" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Received Or Provided Services Property Processes Rights Or Obligations For NonMonetary Consideration Indicator</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3390" xlink:to="lbl_DE3390"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3390" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicator to determine whether any non-monetary consideration has been given or received in any dealings.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3390" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the appropriate code(Yes/ No, True/False) to answer the question.
These dealings may include the performance of services, transferring property (tangible or intangible), processes, rights or obligations during the income year. The nature of the dealing in which the non-monetary consideration is provided may be a barter, swap, bonus or discount, or any type of similar agreement. Non-monetary consideration will generally include any consideration other than:
- monetary payment
- payment by cheque
- telegraphic and bank-to-bank transfer of funds
- inter-company loan account charges.
In particular, debt-for-equity swaps and non-monetary settlements of inter-company loan accounts will be taken to be non-monetary consideration.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3395" xlink:label="loc_DE3395"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3395" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Revenue And Expenses Percentage Bracket Dollar Value Code</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3395" xlink:to="lbl_DE3395"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3395" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The percentage of the revenue derived and expenses incurred that the arm's length pricing method relates to.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3395" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the appropriate code.
1 = 0% , 2 = 1% to less than 25%, 3 = 25% to less than 50%, 4 = 50% to less than 75%, 5 = 75% to less than 100%, 6 = 100%
Indicate, against each method identified, the total dollar value of related-party dealings to which you applied that method. Express them as a percentage of the sum of all the related-party dealings for which you used methods to establish arm?s length pricing - see the ATO website. The total dollar value of related-party dealings is the sum total of such dealings, both income derived and expenses incurred. Do not offset these amounts against each other. The percentage required is an approximate percentage, and an estimate is acceptable provided it is based on objective premises. A statistical sampling is an acceptable method, provided the method follows accepted statistical practice. Keep any working papers relating to this process.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3418" xlink:label="loc_DE3418"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3418" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Transfer Beneficiary Or Interest In Discretionary Non Resident Trust Estate Indicator</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3418" xlink:to="lbl_DE3418"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3418" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicator to determine whether: 
* a transfer of property or services has ever been made or caused to be made to a non-resident trust estate; or
* the reporting party was a beneficiary of a non-resident trust estate; or
* the reporting party had an interest in a non-resident trust estate, or was entitled to acquire an interest in a non-resident trust estate
is a discretionary trust estate.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3418" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field whether any of the non-resident trust estates for which a yes answer was given at items 14,15 or 16 is a discretionary trust estate.
Unless otherwise specified, the terms used in items 14 to 19 have the same meaning as set out in Divisions 6 and 6AAA of Income Tax Assessment Act 1936.
A discretionary trust estate is defined in section 102AAB of the Income Tax Assessment Act 1936. If you answered yes at any of the above listed questions , respond as applicable, in this element . If you answered no at all of the above listed questions, leave this element blank.</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafot.02.02.data.xsd#DE3415" xlink:label="loc_DE3415"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3415" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Miscellaneous Transfer Of Property Or Services To Non Resident Trust Estate Indicator</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3415" xlink:to="lbl_DE3415"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3415" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Indicator to determine whether a transfer of property or services has ever been made or caused to be made to a non-resident trust estate.</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3415" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field whether or not a transfer of property or services has ever been made or caused to be made to a non-resident trust estate. The item is not restricted to the income year of this tax return. ?Transfer?, ?property? and ?services? are defined in section 102AAB of the Income Tax Assessment Act 1936. Sections 102AAJ and 102AAK of the Income Tax Assessment Act 1936 provide guidance in relation to whether there was a transfer or a deemed transfer of property or services to a non-resident trust estate. Please see the ATO website for detail.</link:label>
    </link:labelLink>
</link:linkbase>
