<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Disclaimer: http://www.sbr.gov.au/content/taxonomy_introduction_3_0.htm#Disclaimer -->
<link:linkbase xmlns:link="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xbrli="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink">
  <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#businessDefinition"/>
  <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#dataElementGuidance"/>
  <link:labelLink xlink:type="extended" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/link">
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#bafpr3.02.02_bafpr3Abstract" xlink:label="loc_bafpr3.02.02_bafpr3Abstract"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_bafpr3Abstract" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Financial Performance 3</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_bafpr3.02.02_bafpr3Abstract" xlink:to="lbl_bafpr3Abstract"/>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3211" xlink:label="loc_DE3211"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3211" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Depreciating Assets Deductible From Balancing Adjustment Events Total Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3211" xlink:to="lbl_DE3211"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3211" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total deductible amount a taxpayer has from balancing adjustment events occurring for their depreciating assets.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3211" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the total deductible amount from balancing adjustment events occurring for depreciating assets (this type of deduction may arise if, for example,  a depreciating asset was disposed of for less than its adjustable value). Do not include information about assets allocated to a low-value pool or assets that are deductible under the specific primary production provisions of the Uniform Capital Allowances regime. If there are no deductible balancing adjustment amounts this income  year, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3213" xlink:label="loc_DE3213"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3213" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Depreciating Assets Deduction For Decline In Value Diminishing Value Method Total Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3213" xlink:to="lbl_DE3213"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3213" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total amount of a taxpayer's deductions for decline in value calculated using the diminishing value method, not including amounts from a low-value pool.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3213" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the total amount of deductions for decline in value calculated using the diminishing value method.  Do not include information about the decline in value of assets allocated to a low-value pool or assets that are deductible under the specific primary production provisions of the Uniform Capital Allowances regime. If there are no deductions for decline in value calculated using the diminishing value method, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3212" xlink:label="loc_DE3212"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3212" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Depreciating Assets Deduction For Decline In Value Prime Cost Method Total Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3212" xlink:to="lbl_DE3212"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3212" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total amount of a taxpayer's deductions for decline in value calculated using the prime cost method.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3212" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the total amount of deductions for decline in value calculated using the prime cost method. Do not include information about the decline in value of assets allocated to a low-value pool or assets that are deductible under the specific primary production provisions of the Uniform Capital Allowances regime. If there are no deductions for decline in value calculated using the prime cost method, leave the field blank.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3228" xlink:label="loc_DE3228"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3228" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Depreciating Assets Intangible Assets Decline In Value Of Exploration Or Prospecting Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3228" xlink:to="lbl_DE3228"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3228" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total of a taxpayer's deductions for the decline in value of intangible depreciating assets used in exploration or prospecting.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3228" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the total deductions for decline in value of intangible depreciating assets used in exploration or prospecting. If there were no deductions for depreciating assets used in exploration or prospecting, leave this field blank.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3497" xlink:label="loc_DE3497"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3497" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Depreciating Assets Intangible First Deducted Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3497" xlink:to="lbl_DE3497"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3497" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The cost of all intangible depreciating assets for which the Company is claiming a deduction for decline in value for the first time.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3497" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of intangible depreciating assets first deducted.
If the Company is using the small business entity simplified depreciation rules, do not include an amount at this label. Otherwise, this is the cost of all intangible depreciating assets for which the Company is claiming a deduction for decline in value for the first time. If the Company has allocated any intangible depreciating assets with a cost of less than $1,000 to a low-value pool for the income year, also include the cost of those assets at this label. Do not include expenditure on in-house software which has been allocated to a software development pool at this label. For further information on completing this label where the Company is the head company of an income tax consolidated group or MEC group, or is a company that was a subsidiary member of a consolidated or MEC group for part of the income year and is completing a tax return because of any non-membership periods, see the Tax Office publication Company tax return instructions.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3229" xlink:label="loc_DE3229"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3229" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Depreciating Assets Other Assets Decline In Value Of Exploration Or Prospecting Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3229" xlink:to="lbl_DE3229"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3229" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total of a taxpayer's deductions for the decline in value of other depreciating assets used in exploration or prospecting.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3229" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the total deductions for decline in value of depreciating assets used in exploration or prospecting, excluding intangible depreciating assets.  If there were no deductions for such depreciating assets used in exploration or prospecting, leave this field blank.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3498" xlink:label="loc_DE3498"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3498" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Depreciating Assets Other First Deducted Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3498" xlink:to="lbl_DE3498"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3498" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total cost of all depreciating assets, other than intangible depreciating assets, for which the Company is claiming a deduction for the decline in value for the first time.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3498" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of other depreciating assets first deducted.
If the Company is using the small business entity simplified depreciation rules, do not include an amount at this label. Otherwise, this is the cost of all depreciating assets (other than intangible depreciating assets) for which the Company is claiming a deduction for the decline in value for the first time. If the Company has allocated any assets (other than intangible depreciating assets) with a cost of less than $1,000 to a low-value pool for the income year, also include the cost of those assets at this label. For further information on completing this label where the Company is the head company of an income tax consolidated group or MEC group, or is a company that was a subsidiary member of a consolidated or MEC group for part of the income year and is completing a tax return because of any non-membership periods, see the Tax Office publication Company tax return instructions.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3225" xlink:label="loc_DE3225"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3225" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Depreciating Assets Project Pool Allocations For Environmental Assessments Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3225" xlink:to="lbl_DE3225"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3225" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total of any amounts the taxpayer  has allocated to a project pool this income year which were incurred for environmental assessments for the project.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3225" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the total of any amounts allocated to a project pool this income year which were incurred for environmental assessments for the project. If no such amounts have been allocated to a project pool, leave this field blank.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3226" xlink:label="loc_DE3226"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3226" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Depreciating Assets Project Pool Allocations For Mining And Transport Capital Expenditure Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3226" xlink:to="lbl_DE3226"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3226" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total of any amounts the taxpayer has allocated to a project pool for mining capital expenditure or transport capital expenditure in the income year.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3226" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the total of any amounts allocated to a project pool for mining capital expenditure or transport capital expenditure incurred this income year. If no such amounts have been allocated to a project pool, leave this field blank.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3227" xlink:label="loc_DE3227"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3227" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Depreciating Assets Project Pool Allocations Other Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3227" xlink:to="lbl_DE3227"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3227" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total of all other project amounts the taxpayer has allocated to a project pool in the income year.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3227" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the  total of all other project amounts allocated to a project pool this income year. If there were no other project amounts allocated, leave this field blank.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3509" xlink:label="loc_DE3509"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3509" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Depreciating Assets Small Business Entity General Pool Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3509" xlink:to="lbl_DE3509"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3509" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">A deduction amount for general pool assets (2008: effective life less than 25 years) that the entity can claim because it is eligible to use the simplified depreciation rules and has chosen to do so.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3509" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of small business entity depreciating assets - deduction for long-life pool assets (25 years or more).
Only complete this item if the company is a small business entity using the simplified depreciation rules.
Do not show at this label the balance of any small business pool or the cost of assets transferred to a pool.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3510" xlink:label="loc_DE3510"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3510" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Depreciating Assets Small Business Entity Long Life Pool Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3510" xlink:to="lbl_DE3510"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3510" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">A deduction amount for long-life pool assets (2008: effective life of 25 years or more) that the entity can claim because it is eligible to use the simplified depreciation rules and has chosen to do so.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3510" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of small business entity depreciating assets - deduction for long-life pool assets (25 years or more).
Only complete this item if the company is a small business entity using the simplified depreciation rules.
Do not show at this label the balance of any small business pool or the cost of assets transferred to a pool.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3508" xlink:label="loc_DE3508"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3508" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Depreciating Assets Small Business Entity Low Cost Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3508" xlink:to="lbl_DE3508"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3508" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">A deduction amount for low-cost assets (cost less than a specified amount - $1,000 each in 2008) that the entity can claim because it is eligible to use the simplified depreciation rules and has chosen to do so.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3508" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of small business entity  depreciating assets - deduction for low cost assets (less than $,1000)
Do not show at this label the balance of any small business pool or the cost of assets transferred to a pool.
Only complete this item if the company is a small business entity using the simplified depreciation rules. 
To complete this item use the amounts calculated for SBE depreciation deductions at label "X" "Depreciation expenses" item</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3319" xlink:label="loc_DE3319"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3319" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Allowable Deductions Total Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3319" xlink:to="lbl_DE3319"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3319" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The specified total amount of deduction allowed.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3339" xlink:label="loc_DE3339"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3339" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Personal Services Income Other Deductions Total Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3339" xlink:to="lbl_DE3339"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3339" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total amount of other deductions that offset PSI in calculating attributed income.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3338" xlink:label="loc_DE3338"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3338" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Personal Services Income Principal Work Payments To Associates Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3338" xlink:to="lbl_DE3338"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3338" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total amount being claimed as deductions that were paid to  associates from which PSI was gained or produced.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3378" xlink:label="loc_DE3378"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3378" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Adjusted Change In Expenditure Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3378" xlink:to="lbl_DE3378"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3378" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the change in expenditure on an Australian owned Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure to the group total.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3378" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Because of the nature of the calculation, the complexity or  the number of steps involved,  refer to the ATO website at www.ato.gov.au for guidance on how to calculate this amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3377" xlink:label="loc_DE3377"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3377" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Adjusted Increase In Expenditure By The Group Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3377" xlink:to="lbl_DE3377"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3377" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the calculation of the company's share of the Australian owned part of the adjusted increase in expenditure on Research and Development (R&amp;D) by the Group.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3377" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Because of the nature of the calculation, the complexity or  the number of steps involved,  refer to the ATO website at www.ato.gov.au for guidance on how to calculate this amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3376" xlink:label="loc_DE3376"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3376" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Adjustment Balance Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3376" xlink:to="lbl_DE3376"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3376" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the balance of the adjustment amounts.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3376" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Because of the nature of the calculation, the complexity or  the number of steps involved,  refer to the ATO website at www.ato.gov.au for guidance on how to calculate this amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3374" xlink:label="loc_DE3374"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3374" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Adjustment Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3374" xlink:to="lbl_DE3374"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3374" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the term used to denote a group?s adjustment amount for the current year of income, that is, Year 0.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3374" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Because of the nature of the calculation, the complexity or  the number of steps involved,  refer to the ATO website at www.ato.gov.au for guidance on how to calculate this amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3359" xlink:label="loc_DE3359"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3359" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Aggregate Adjustments Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3359" xlink:to="lbl_DE3359"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3359" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Adjustments required to the company's aggregate R&amp;D amount, for example, building expenditure, consolidated group adjustments, expenditure on foreign owned R&amp;D</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3359" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of expenditure on the following items- Building expenditure and other adjustments required to the company?s aggregate Research and Development (R&amp;D) amount, other amounts that are not included in the fields informing the Calculation of R&amp;D in the Research and Development Tax Concession Schedule that are needed to calculate the company?s aggregate R&amp;D amount. These amounts form part of the aggregate research and development amount even though they are not deductible.  These include the total amount of any capital expenditure on buildings used for the purpose of carrying on R&amp;D activities, for companies that are lodging a return regarding income and deductions for a period before or after they joined a consolidated group, the additional aggregate research and development amount.   NOTE The items referred to above are not eligible for deduction under the R&amp;D tax concession but are part of the aggregate R&amp;D amount.  (Only complete this item if the company chooses to take the R&amp;D tax offset. Include also at Amount of expenditure on the following items- Building expenditure and other adjustments required to the company?s aggregate R&amp;D amount any positive or negative adjustments that may need to be made where a company has a transitional substituted account period in the year of income, and where the amounts reported in the fields informing the Calculation of R&amp;D in the Research and Development Tax Concession Schedule that relate to a period that is less or greater than 12 months. The aggregate R&amp;D amount is calculated using the 12 month period that is the tax offset year.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3356" xlink:label="loc_DE3356"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3356" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Allocated Total Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3356" xlink:to="lbl_DE3356"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3356" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total base amount of all deductions claimed for Australian owned research and development activities in the research and development (R&amp;D) schedule. This amount may be positive or negative.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3356" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">As a total,  this field may not be required in Standard Business Reporting.  It should be noted that some of the amounts listed under base amount could be negative.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3351" xlink:label="loc_DE3351"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3351" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Balancing Losses Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3351" xlink:to="lbl_DE3351"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3351" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Balancing adjustment (loss) for a depreciating asset that was acquired under a contract entered into, or that commenced construction, after midday Australian Eastern Standard Time on 29 January 2001 that relates to the use of the asset for the purpose of carrying on Australian owned R&amp;D activities</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3351" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">If the company is entitled to deduct an amount following a balancing adjustment event (such as disposal), inform the relevant field with the amount of any part of the balancing adjustment that the company is entitled to increase by 25%, in the calculation of the base amount.   The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3372" xlink:label="loc_DE3372"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3372" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Change in Expenditure Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3372" xlink:to="lbl_DE3372"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3372" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the change in expenditure on foreign owned Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure to the group total.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3372" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Because of the nature of the calculation, the complexity or  the number of steps involved,  refer to the ATO website at www.ato.gov.au for guidance on how to calculate this amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3345" xlink:label="loc_DE3345"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3345" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Contract Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3345" xlink:to="lbl_DE3345"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3345" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Eligible expenditure incurred under a contract to another party (other than an RRA) that is directly in respect of R&amp;D activities carried on, by or on behalf of the company, or wholly or primarily on behalf of a grouped foreign company.

Contract - Other R&amp;D Expenditure. Base Amount</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3345" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with any expenditure incurred under a contract to another party, other than a Registered Research Agency (RRA), that is directly for Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities carried on by or on behalf of the company. This item excludes contracted expenditure carried out by an RRA and  expenditure under a contract that is, in substance, for the acquisition of plant. The amounts claimed at the fields -Claimable at 100%-  Claimable at 125%- and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3353" xlink:label="loc_DE3353"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3353" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Core Technology Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3353" xlink:to="lbl_DE3353"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3353" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Deduction for expenditure incurred in acquiring, or in acquiring the right to use core technology for Australian owned R&amp;D activities that are carried on by the eligible company or on its behalf</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3353" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the deductible amount of Core technology expenditure.  Include deductions for core technology expenditure. Core technology expenditure includes expenditure incurred in acquiring, or in acquiring the right to use, core technology for Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities that are carried on by the company or on its behalf. A maximum of one-third of R&amp;D expenditure incurred during the year on R&amp;D activities related to the core technology can be deducted. Any undeducted core technology expenditure amounts can be carried forward to future years when the company undertakes R&amp;D activities related to the core technology. Adjust the amount of core technology expenditure claimed in accordance with prepayment provisions.  An adjustment may need to be made if core technology is disposed of.  If core technology expenditure is deductible, as a result  of the company joining a consolidated group, the tax cost of the core technology asset is ?set?. An adjustment may need to be made to any deductions allowable for the decline in value of that asset. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3350" xlink:label="loc_DE3350"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3350" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Decline In Value Plant And Depreciating Assets Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3350" xlink:to="lbl_DE3350"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3350" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Notional Division 40 deduction for depreciating assets, including certain capital works, used in carrying on Australian owned R&amp;D activities, that were acquired under a contract entered into, or that commenced construction, after midday Australian Eastern Standard Time on  29 January 2001</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3350" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the notional amount as determined under at the base amount. Deductions for depreciating assets including certain capital works, used in carrying on Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities must have begun to be constructed, or have been acquired under contracts entered into, after midday Australian Eastern Standard Time on 29 January 2001. The amount allowable is determined through a notional application of the provisions of the  ITAA 1997, subject to certain assumptions. Calculation of research and development deduction asset applied to non-R&amp;D purposes as well as R&amp;D use in a year,  the R&amp;D portion  of the decline in value can be claimed.  If an STS taxpayer, or a taxpayer who could otherwise allocate an asset to a low-value pool, uses that asset for R&amp;D activities as its first use, the taxpayer must claim deductions for it under these provisions, not the STS  or low-value pool provisions. If the asset is used for non-R&amp;D purposes for part of the year or in a subsequent year, deductions for that part of the year or the subsequent year will be considered.  If an asset was not used for R&amp;D in an earlier income year and the company was entitled to a deduction for the asset(s) under a low-value pool or a Simplified Tax Systems (STS) pool in that year, continue to calculate deductions under the relevant pooling provisions, even if the asset is subsequently used for R&amp;D. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3347" xlink:label="loc_DE3347"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3347" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Feedstock Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3347" xlink:to="lbl_DE3347"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3347" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Excess of an eligible company?s feedstock input over feedstock output in relation to Australian owned R&amp;D activities in respect of a year of income claimable at 100%</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3347" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of eligible feedstock expenditure claimable at 100%.  It is the excess of the feedstock input over the feedstock output for the related activities, in the year of income. The eligible feedstock expenditure will attract the additional 25% concession component.  If the company has eligible feedstock expenditure, include this amount.  Inform the remainder of feedstock input at Residual feedstock expenditure as residual feedstock expenditure. Adjust the amount of eligible feedstock expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions.  The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% ,  Claimable at 125% and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3354" xlink:label="loc_DE3354"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3354" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Interest Or Amounts In The Nature Of Interest Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3354" xlink:to="lbl_DE3354"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3354" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Deduction for interest, or an amount in the nature of interest, incurred by an eligible company during the year of income in the financing of Australian owned R&amp;D activities.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3354" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of interest expenditure.
This item includes interest, or an amount in the nature of interest, incurred during the year of income in the financing of Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities. NOTE: You may need to adjust the amount of interest expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3344" xlink:label="loc_DE3344"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3344" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Other Expenditure Registered Research Agency Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3344" xlink:to="lbl_DE3344"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3344" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">All Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure incurred directly in respect of R&amp;D activities carried on by or on behalf of the company not covered by contracted or salary expenditure.

Other R&amp;D Expenditure. Claimable at 100%</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3344" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with other Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure incurred directly in respect of R&amp;D activities carried on by or on behalf of the company. Do not include amounts to be shown at Contract other or  Plant leasing. Taxation Ruling states that overhead and administrative expenditure is directly in respect of R&amp;D where the eligible R&amp;D activities contributed to all or an identifiable part of the expenditure being incurred, or the conduct of eligible R&amp;D activities by the company would be materially impaired if the expenditure was not incurred. Adjust the amount of other R&amp;D expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions ?Other R&amp;D expenditure? does NOT include:  core technology expenditure;  interest expenditure;  feedstock expenditure (show eligible feedstock expenditure and residual feedstock expenditure at separate items);   expenditure incurred acquiring or constructing plant, pilot plant or a building, or extending, altering or making improvements to a building expenditure incurred acquiring or constructing a depreciating asset. The amounts claimed at the fields -Claimable at 100%- - Claimable at 125%- and foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3346" xlink:label="loc_DE3346"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3346" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Plant Leasing Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3346" xlink:to="lbl_DE3346"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3346" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Eligible expenditure incurred in hiring or leasing an item of plant that is directly in respect of Australian owned R&amp;D activities.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3346" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with any expenditure incurred in the hire or leasing of an item of plant that is directly in respect of Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities carried on by or on behalf of the company. Adjust the amount of plant leasing expenditure claimed in accordance with the prepayment provisions. The amounts at the fields  - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3348" xlink:label="loc_DE3348"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3348" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Plant Pilot Deductions Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3348" xlink:to="lbl_DE3348"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3348" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Plant and pilot plant deductions pre 29 Jan 2001 (including disposal losses) Base amount</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3348" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with any deduction that is claimed  for expenditure in acquiring or constructing such an item of pilot plant only if the unit of pilot plant is used exclusively for carrying on R&amp;D activities during the year of income. The base amount at this item is the annual deduction percentage of the qualifying pilot plant expenditure for such items. Balancing adjustments may be needed if items of plant and pilot plant for which expenditure has been deducted  are disposed of, lost or destroyed after being used exclusively for carrying on R&amp;D activities, provided no deduction is allowable to the company for depreciation.  Such balancing adjustments are covered under the  ITAA 1936. The consideration received for the plant at the time of disposal may vary from the written-down value. If this balancing adjustment is a loss, record it at this item. If the consideration receivable for the disposal, loss or destruction of the unit of R&amp;D plant is less than the written-down value, the amount of this difference can be claimed if a deduction for that expenditure is allowable under the  ITAA 1936. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% (Claimable at 150% pre 8/96) must equal the Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3342" xlink:label="loc_DE3342"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3342" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Registered Research Agency Contracted Expenditure Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3342" xlink:to="lbl_DE3342"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3342" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Expenditure incurred by an eligible company under contract with an RRA for R&amp;D activities undertaken by the RRA on behalf of the company, or wholly or primarily on behalf of a grouped foreign company.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3342" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the total amount of contracted expenditure that is Register Research Agency incurred.  The base amount must equal the sum of the other amounts claimed at the fields Claimable at 100%, Claimable at 125% and Foreign owned R&amp;D expenditure.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3341" xlink:label="loc_DE3341"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3341" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Research And Development Accounting Expenditure Add Back Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3341" xlink:to="lbl_DE3341"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3341" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Accounting expenses incurred on R&amp;D Activities. Those expense amounts included at the expenditure labels at Calculation of total profit or loss on the company tax return, which relate to amounts that are subject to the R&amp;D tax concession (Australian owned R&amp;D tax concession and foreign owned R&amp;D tax concession). Generally, these amounts include expense amounts for accounting purposes, related to R&amp;D activities, for which different amounts will be claimed for income tax purposes</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3341" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">On the Research and Development (R&amp;D) Schedule at Preliminary Calculation inform the write-back of R&amp;D accounting expenditure for the amounts included at the appropriate expenditure labels at Information statement- Calculation of total profit or loss on the Company tax return field.  The amount shown at Preliminary Calculation on the R&amp;D Schedule must be the same as the amount shown at Information statement- Reconciliation to taxable income or loss- Accounting expenditure in item 6 subject to R&amp;D tax concession on the company tax return.  If expense amounts for R&amp;D deductions at Information statement- Calculation of total profit or loss on the company tax return have not been included (for example, those amounts are capitalised) write zero 0 at Preliminary Calculation on the R&amp;D tax concession schedule and Information statement- Reconciliation to taxable income or loss- Accounting expenditure in item 6 subject to R&amp;D tax concession on the company tax return. For consolidated groups -  If aggregated expenditure has been used for accounting R&amp;D expenditure under Information statement- Calculation of total profit or loss on the company tax return, add back the full amount of this aggregated expenditure at the fields Information statement- Reconciliation to taxable income or loss- Accounting expenditure in item 6 subject to R&amp;D tax concession on the company tax return.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3355" xlink:label="loc_DE3355"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3355" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Residual Feedstock Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3355" xlink:to="lbl_DE3355"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3355" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Residual feedstock expenditure deduction for the lesser amount of the eligible company?s feedstock input and feedstock output for Australian owned R&amp;D activities in the year of income</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3355" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of residual feedstock expenditure. Residual feedstock expenditure is the lesser amount of the company?s feedstock input and feedstock output for Research and Development (R&amp;D) activities in the year of income. If feedstock inputs are greater than feedstock outputs, inform the relevant field with  the outputs amount; if it is less than feedstock outputs, inform the relevant field with the inputs amount  Residual feedstock expenditure. This is the residual feedstock expenditure.  The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3375" xlink:label="loc_DE3375"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3375" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Running Average Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3375" xlink:to="lbl_DE3375"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3375" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The average Australian owned Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure over  three income years for each company.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3375" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Because of the nature of the calculation, the complexity or  the number of steps involved,  refer to the ATO website at www.ato.gov.au for guidance on how to calculate this amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3373" xlink:label="loc_DE3373"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3373" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Research And Development Total Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3373" xlink:to="lbl_DE3373"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3373" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the total Research and Development (R&amp;D) expenditure for the current year for which the company return is being completed.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3373" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">The amount of Total R&amp;D Expenditure OF Current Year (Year0) (RDS130) = Australian owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year 0 (RDS73) + Foreign owned R&amp;D incremental tax concession - Group Totals Year 0 (RDS95).</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3318" xlink:label="loc_DE3318"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3318" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Assessable Income Including Transfers To Virtual Pooled Superannuation Trust Total Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3318" xlink:to="lbl_DE3318"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3318" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Total assessable income that is allocated to a complying superannuation/FHSA class. This includes both income according to ordinary concepts and statutory income.  This also includes transfer to the complying superannuation/FHSA asset pool.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3318" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">The total assessable income of the complying superannuation/FHSA class includes both income according to ordinary concepts and statutory income.  Inform the relevant field with the assessable income that is allocated to the complying superannuation/FHSA class under the Income Tax Assessment Act 1997.  The Act covers assessable income of a life insurance company that is assessable income derived by the company from the investment of its complying superannuation/FHSA assets in relation to the period during which those assets were complying superannuation asset, so much of the amount that is included in the company's assessable income; as is equal to the total transfer value of assets transferred in the income year by the company to a complying superannuation/FHSA; if an asset (other than money) is transferred by the company from a complying superannuation/FHSA - amounts that are included in the company's assessable income; amounts that are included in the company's assessable income; or amounts that are included in the company's assessable income; so much of the company's assessable income for the income year as is the total amount credited during that year to the RSAs provided by the company; less the total amount debited during that year from the RSAs.  Please refer to the legal reference for guidance.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3317" xlink:label="loc_DE3317"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3317" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Assessable Income Total Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3317" xlink:to="lbl_DE3317"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3317" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The assessable income that is income according to ordinary concepts for all members of the consolidated group, except for the ordinary income of the complying superannuation class of any life insurance company which is a member of the consolidated group.  Any assessable income includes income according to ordinary concepts, which is called ordinary income.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3512" xlink:label="loc_DE3512"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3512" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Fees And Charges Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3512" xlink:to="lbl_DE3512"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3512" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The amount of all fees and charges included in assessable income.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3512" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with fees and charges  from assessable income for life insurance companies and friendly societies.
This includes premium-based fees, establishment fees, time-based account fees, asset fees, switching fees, surrender penalties, buy?sell margins, exit fees and interest on overdue premiums.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3325" xlink:label="loc_DE3325"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3325" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Head Company Taxable Income Less Complying Superannuation Class Or FHSA Class Taxable Income Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3325" xlink:to="lbl_DE3325"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3325" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Amount of Life Insurance Companies Head Company Taxable Income Less Complying Superannuation Class Or FHSA Class Taxable Income.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3325" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of taxable income of the head company less the taxable income of the complying superannuation/FHSA class.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3312" xlink:label="loc_DE3312"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3312" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Investment Income Segregated Exempt Assets Net Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3312" xlink:to="lbl_DE3312"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3312" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">All investment income from Segregated Exempt Assets (SEA) less losses made from the disposal of SEA assets. Investment income includes gains made on the disposal of investments, interest income, dividend income, trust distributions, partnership distributions, net rental income and all other investment income, calculation on Taxation basis.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3312" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">If a life company reconciles accounting income to taxable income, it must inform the relevant field with the total accounting net investment income for segregated exempt assets (SEA).  If a life company uses a taxation basis to determine income derived from SEA, inform the details of ordinary and statutory income derived from SEA: all investment income from SEA less losses made from the disposal of SEA assets. Investment income includes gains made on the disposal of investments, interest income, dividend income, trust distributions, partnership distributions, net rental income and all other investment income. Inform whether the company used an accounting basis or a taxation basis to determine net investment income derived from SEA with the appropriate symbol in the relevant field. These amounts derived by a life insurance company are not assessable income and are not exempt income, that is, amounts of ordinary income and statutory income derived from segregated exempt assets, being income that relates to the period during which the assets were segregated exempt assets.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3315" xlink:label="loc_DE3315"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3315" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Premium Policies Accident Disability And Term Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3315" xlink:to="lbl_DE3315"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3315" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total amount of gross premiums received from accident, disability and term policies.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3315" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the total amount of gross premiums received from accident and disability and term policies. Term policies include assets (including money) having a total transfer value equal to ?risk riders? that are transferred from the Virtual Pooled Superannuation Trust (VPST) under the Income Tax Assessment Act 1997. Disability policies include continuous disability policies.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3316" xlink:label="loc_DE3316"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3316" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Premium Policy Other Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3316" xlink:to="lbl_DE3316"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3316" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total gross amount of  other premiums received from all life insurance policies excepting exempt life insurance policies, term policies (including riders), accident and disability policies.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3314" xlink:label="loc_DE3314"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3314" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Premiums Policies Exempt Life Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3314" xlink:to="lbl_DE3314"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3314" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The total amount of gross premiums received from exempt life insurance policies.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3314" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of income received from exempt life insurance policies.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3320" xlink:label="loc_DE3320"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3320" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Taxable Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3320" xlink:to="lbl_DE3320"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3320" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Taxable income that is income according to ordinary concepts, the total ordinary income less total allowable deductions.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3313" xlink:label="loc_DE3313"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3313" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Taxation Basis Or Accounting Basis Code</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3313" xlink:to="lbl_DE3313"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3313" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The method by which net investment income of the Segregated Exempt Assets (SEA) is determined.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3313" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">T = Taxation Basis, A = Accounting Basis</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3505" xlink:label="loc_DE3505"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3505" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income International Dealings Attributed Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3505" xlink:to="lbl_DE3505"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3505" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The amount of attributed foreign income from controlled foreign entities.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3503" xlink:label="loc_DE3503"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3503" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income International Dealings Net Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3503" xlink:to="lbl_DE3503"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3503" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The amount of the assessable income derived by the business entity from foreign sources grossed up by the amount of the foreign tax, but net of expenses. This amount includes:
- foreign source capital gains after offsetting any unapplied capital losses
- assessable dividends paid by a New Zealand company
- income attributable to a dividend from a New Zealand company received from a partnership or trust.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3503" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of net foreign income.
Do not include the following amounts in this label:
- attributed foreign income (such as attributed income from a CFC or foreign investment fund (FIF))
- any amount of Australian franking credits attached to franked distributions received from a New Zealand company. Include these amounts at  Australian franking credits from a New Zealand company. 
Do not show negative amount. Foreign source tax losses may be used to offset against foreign source income only. Any excess of foreign source tax losses over foreign source income may be carried forward to be used to offset against future foreign source income of the same class ? see Foreign income return form guide, available on the ATO website.
Tax Laws Amendment (2007 Measures No. 4) Act 2007 removes the quarantining of foreign losses, from the first income year starting on or after 1 July 2008. Existing foreign losses will be subject to transitional rules. These changes will not affect the completion of the Losses schedule 2008.
Foreign source capital gains are made by an Australian resident company if a CGT event happens to any of its worldwide CGT assets.
Include any capital gain made from CGT assets in the company?s net capital gain for the income year and include it at  Net capital gain. For more information about CGT, see Guide to capital gains tax 2008.
Do not apply debt deductions other than those attributable to an overseas PE of the taxpayer against foreign source income for the purpose of calculating net foreign income or identifying a foreign loss.

Complete a Losses schedule if the company has:
- claimed a deduction for foreign source losses greater than $100,000
- current year foreign source losses greater than $100,000
- foreign source losses carried forward to later income years greater than $100,000
- claimed a deduction for prior year CFC losses greater than $100,000
- current year CFC losses greater than $100,000
- CFC losses carried forward to later income years greater than $100,000.
For more information, see Losses schedule instructions on the ATO website.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3524" xlink:label="loc_DE3524"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3524" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income International Dealings Tax Offset Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3524" xlink:to="lbl_DE3524"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3524" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">A credit available to a taxpayer who received foreign income that is taxable in Australia and for which they paid (or are taken to have paid) foreign tax. This amount includes credits for foreign source capital gains.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3524" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">The amount of a corporate tax entity is entitled to a tax offset for an income year for which it satisfies the residency requirement and at least one of the following applies:
-  the entity has incurred a liability to pay FDT in that year 
-  the entity has carried forward an amount of excess FDT offset that was unable to be applied against an income tax liability in a previous income year, or 
-  the entity incurred a liability to pay FDT in a previous income year when it did not meet the residency requirement, and was therefore not entitled to an FDT offset for that income year.
At the end of an income year, a corporate tax entity that has a deficit balance in their franking account is liable to pay franking deficit tax (FDT).</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3340" xlink:label="loc_DE3340"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3340" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Personal Services Income Net Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3340" xlink:to="lbl_DE3340"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3340" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The net Personal Services Income (PSI) is the total of the personal services income to be attributed to individuals.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3337" xlink:label="loc_DE3337"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3337" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Personal Services Income Total Derived During The Year Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3337" xlink:to="lbl_DE3337"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3337" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Total amount of PSI attributed to individuals.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3352" xlink:label="loc_DE3352"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3352" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Research And Development Balancing Profits Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3352" xlink:to="lbl_DE3352"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3352" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">Balancing  adjustment (profit) for a depreciating asset that was acquired under a contract entered into, or that commenced construction, after midday Australian Eastern Standard Time on 29 January 2001 that relates to the use of the asset for the purpose of carrying on Australian owned R&amp;D activities</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3352" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">If the company is entitled to deduct an amount following a balancing adjustment event (such as disposal), inform the relevant field with the amount of any part of the balancing adjustment that the company is entitled to increase by 25%, in the calculation of the base amount.   The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% and  Claimable at 125% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.02.data.xsd#DE3349" xlink:label="loc_DE3349"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3349" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Research And Development Disposal Profits Amount</link:label>
    <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE3349" xlink:to="lbl_DE3349"/>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3349" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">The amount by which the consideration exceeds the written-down value, up to the limit of the difference between the cost of the plant and its written-down value.</link:label>
    <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE3349" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Inform the relevant field with the amount of Pre 29 Jan 2001 disposal profits. Include the amount by which the consideration exceeds the written-down value, up to the limit of the difference between the cost of the plant and its written-down value.   NOTE: If the company chooses to take the Research and Development (R&amp;D) tax offset,  use this amount in calculating the size of the offset. Include the amount of any balancing adjustment (assessable income). Balancing adjustments sale of pilot plant (profits). If the consideration receivable is greater than the written-down value of the unit of pilot plant, include the amount by which the consideration exceeds the written-down value, up to a limit of the difference between the cost of the plant and its written-down value. The amounts at the fields - Claimable at 100% must equal the amount shown at Base amount.</link:label>
  </link:labelLink>
</link:linkbase>
