<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Disclaimer: http://www.sbr.gov.au/content/taxonomy_introduction_3_0.htm#Disclaimer -->
<link:linkbase xmlns:link="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xbrli="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance">
    <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#businessDefinition"/>
    <link:labelLink xlink:type="extended" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/link">
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#bafpr3.02.05_bafpr3Abstract" xlink:label="loc_bafpr3.02.05_bafpr3Abstract"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_bafpr3Abstract" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Financial Performance 3</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_bafpr3.02.05_bafpr3Abstract" xlink:to="lbl_bafpr3Abstract"/>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8507" xlink:label="loc_DE8507"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8507" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of all acquisition costs recognised as expenses. This is determined in accordance with the relevant Accounting Standards.

For the purposes of this item exclude the results of the liability adequacy test (LAT). Commission or brokerage paid to agents or brokers for obtaining business for the insurer is included.

Acquisition costs are incurred in obtaining and recording insurance contracts. They include commission or brokerage paid to agent or brokers for obtaining business for the insurer, selling and underwriting costs such as advertising and risk assessment, the administrative costs of recording policy information and premium collection costs.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8507" xlink:to="lbl_DE8507"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8507" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Acquisition Excluding Liability Adequacy Test Results Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8486" xlink:label="loc_DE8486"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8486" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of all acquisition costs recognised as expenses. This is determined in accordance with the relevant Accounting Standards.

For the purposes of this item exclude:
- commission or brokerage paid to agents or brokers for obtaining business for the insurer; and
- results of the liability adequacy test (LAT).

Acquisition costs are incurred in obtaining and recording insurance contracts. They include commission or brokerage paid to agent or brokers for obtaining business for the insurer, selling and underwriting costs such as advertising and risk assessment, the administrative costs of recording policy information and premium collection costs.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8486" xlink:to="lbl_DE8486"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8486" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Acquisition Excluding Liability Adequacy Test Results And Commissions Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8481" xlink:label="loc_DE8481"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8481" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of insurance claims expense recognised during the relevant period, gross of any associated insurance recoveries. This item is to be determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.

This item is calculated as the sum of paid claims and the movement in outstanding claims liabilities over the relevant period.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8481" xlink:to="lbl_DE8481"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8481" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Claims Gross Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8502" xlink:label="loc_DE8502"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8502" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of insurance claims expense which is due to prior period reserve releases or strengthening. This item refers to movements in outstanding claims due to changes in the assumptions used to calculate outstanding claims in prior periods. It includes changes due to the impacts of movements in discount rates and changes in the probability of sufficiency.

This item is determined in accordance with the relevant Accounting Standards.

Insurance claims expense is calculated as the sum of paid claims and the movement in outstanding claims liability for the relevant period.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8502" xlink:to="lbl_DE8502"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8502" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Claims Gross Due To Reserve Changes Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8572" xlink:label="loc_DE8572"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8572" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of the rise in claims expense recognised for the relevant period which is due to prior period reserve strengthening. This item refers to movements in outstanding claims provisions due to changes in the assumptions used to calculate outstanding claims in prior periods that result in increases in the provision. It includes the impact of changes in the probability of sufficiency.

This item is determined in accordance with the relevant accounting standards, except that it is not discounted as required by those accounting standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8572" xlink:to="lbl_DE8572"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8572" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Claims Gross Reserve Strengthening Not Discounted Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8956" xlink:label="loc_DE8956"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8956" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of relevant period, claims paid on a cash flow basis in the current financial year, regardless of the financial year in which the reinsurance recovery may have been recognised as revenue.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8956" xlink:to="lbl_DE8956"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8956" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Claims Paid Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8479" xlink:label="loc_DE8479"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8479" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of insurance claim payment expenses recognised during the relevant period, gross of any associated insurance recoveries. This item is to be determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8479" xlink:to="lbl_DE8479"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8479" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Claims Payments Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8554" xlink:label="loc_DE8554"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8554" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of insurance claims payments, as at the relevant date. This item is to be reported gross of any associated reinsurance recoveries, but net of any associated non-reinsurance recoveries.

This includes non-reinsurance recoveries that have been received or are expected to be received only in relation to claims already paid.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8554" xlink:to="lbl_DE8554"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8554" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Claims Payments Gross Reinsurance Recoveries Net Non Reinsurance Recoveries Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8555" xlink:label="loc_DE8555"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8555" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of insurance claims payments, as at the relevant date. This item is to be reported net of any associated reinsurance and non-reinsurance recoveries.

This includes reinsurance and non-reinsurance recoveries that have been received or are expected to be received only in relation to claims already paid.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8555" xlink:to="lbl_DE8555"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8555" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Claims Payments Net Reinsurance And Non Reinsurance Recoveries Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8493" xlink:label="loc_DE8493"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8493" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of commission or brokerage paid for obtaining business for the insurer. This item is determined in accordance with the relevant Accounting Standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8493" xlink:to="lbl_DE8493"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8493" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Commission Or Brokerage Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8484" xlink:label="loc_DE8484"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8484" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of net insurance claims expense recognised during the relevant period, but only of which relate to the current period.

Current period net claim represents:
- current period claims payments;
- current period reported outstanding case estimates (that is, case estimates created in the current period); and 
- current period incurred but not reported (and incurred but not enough reported) claims expenses. 

Current period net claims expense should be defined and reported according to the following:
- net of all recoverables (including input tax credits reinsurance, salvage, subrogation and other recovery types); 
- inclusive of claims handling expense, assuming that industry generally includes claims handling costs with the claim paid component of the incurred claims expense; 
- the outstanding claims component be inflated only i.e. undiscounted; and 
- the outstanding claims component be on a central estimate basis i.e. without risk margins.

'Current period' should only include claims incurred in the current accident year. For this purpose the current accident year should be aligned to the insurer's current financial year.

This item will include both net payments made in the financial year to date on claims arising from accidents in the current financial year, and net outstanding estimates (undiscounted and without risk margins) at the end of the financial year to date on claims arising from accidents in the current financial year.

Movements in claims costs for claims incurred in accident years before the current year, as well as the impact of discounting and risk margins, should be reported as 'nonrecurring'. This means that the 'current' claims expense is on an undiscounted central estimate basis and the `non-recurring' claims expense is the balancing item.

Insurers issuing 'claims made' policies should classify as 'current' any claims reported in the financial year to date.

Reinsurers that manage their business on an underwriting period basis (and so are unable to assess current accident period outcomes) should use a proxy approach to estimating current year incurred claims. Claims expense in the current financial year to date attributable to each of the current and immediately prior underwriting years should be adopted as the 'Current period net claims expense'. As with direct insurers, the 'Current period net claims expense' for reinsurers should be reported on an undiscounted basis with no risk margins, net of all recoverables and including claims handling expense. The 'Non-recurring items that are part of total net claims expense' is a balancing item such that in total they equal to the 'Net claims expense'.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8484" xlink:to="lbl_DE8484"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8484" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Current Claims Net Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8489" xlink:label="loc_DE8489"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8489" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of any adjustments to deferred acquisition costs or the unexpired risk liability as a result of performing the Liability Adequacy Tests (LAT). This item is determined in accordance with the relevant Accounting Standards.

Report at this item only the results of the LAT performed in the current relevant period.

Liability adequacy test means an assessment of whether the carrying amount of an insurance liability needs to be increased (or the carrying amount of the related deferred acquisition costs or related intangible assets decreased) based on a review of future cash flows.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8489" xlink:to="lbl_DE8489"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8489" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Current Liability Adequacy Test Result Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8504" xlink:label="loc_DE8504"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8504" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of the full cost of reinsurance entered into during the relevant period.
 
The full cost of reinsurance entered into during the relevant period includes both reinsurance costs recognised as an expense in the relevant period and reinsurance costs deferred for recognition in future periods.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8504" xlink:to="lbl_DE8504"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8504" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Full Cost Of Reinsurance Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8531" xlink:label="loc_DE8531"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8531" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of any adjustments to deferred acquisition costs or the unexpired risk liability as a result of performing the Liability Adequacy Tests (LAT). This item is determined in accordance with the relevant Accounting Standards.

Report at this item the results of the LAT performed in the relevant period and the results of the LAT performed in prior years which have profit and loss impact in the relevant  period.

Liability adequacy test means an assessment of whether the carrying amount of an insurance liability needs to be increased (or the carrying amount of the related deferred acquisition costs or related intangible assets decreased) based on a review of future cash flows.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8531" xlink:to="lbl_DE8531"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8531" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Liability Adequacy Test Result Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8503" xlink:label="loc_DE8503"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8503" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of net claims incurred which are due to prior period reserve releases or strengthening. This item refers to movements in outstanding claims due to changes in the assumptions used to calculate outstanding claims in prior periods. It includes changes due to the impacts of movements in discount rates and changes in the probability of sufficiency.

This item is determined in accordance with the relevant Accounting Standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8503" xlink:to="lbl_DE8503"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8503" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Net Claims Due to Reserve Changes Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8485" xlink:label="loc_DE8485"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8485" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of net insurance claims expense recognised during the relevant period, but only of which relate to non-recurring items.

Non-recurring net claims expense represents those net claims expenses that are not classified as current period, and is a balancing item such that current period net claims expense and non-recurring claims expense are equal to net claims expense.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8485" xlink:to="lbl_DE8485"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8485" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Non Recurring Claims Net Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8480" xlink:label="loc_DE8480"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8480" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This item represents the movement in the outstanding claims liability for the relevant period and is to be determined in accordance with the relevant Accounting Standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8480" xlink:to="lbl_DE8480"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8480" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Outstanding Claims Movement Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE7557" xlink:label="loc_DE7557"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE7557" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of insurance premiums. other than those for workers' compensation, that have been expensed in the relevant period in accordance with accounting standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE7557" xlink:to="lbl_DE7557"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE7557" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Premiums Not Workers Compensation Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8490" xlink:label="loc_DE8490"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8490" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of any adjustments to deferred acquisition costs or the unexpired risk liability as a result of performing the Liability Adequacy Tests (LAT). This item is determined in accordance with the relevant Accounting Standards.

Report at this item only the results of the LAT performed in prior relevant periods which have a profit or loss impact in the current relevant period.

Liability adequacy test means an assessment of whether the carrying amount of an insurance liability needs to be increased (or the carrying amount of the related deferred acquisition costs or related intangible assets decreased) based on a review of future cash flows.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8490" xlink:to="lbl_DE8490"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8490" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Prior Liability Adequacy Test Result Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8499" xlink:label="loc_DE8499"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8499" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of reinsurance expense recognised during the relevant period, as determined in accordance with the relevant prudential standards.
 
Reinsurance expense represents the full costs of reinsurance entered into during the relevant period plus deferred reinsurance expense (DRE) at the beginning of the period, less deferred reinsurance expense (DRE) at the end of the relevant period.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8499" xlink:to="lbl_DE8499"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8499" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Reinsurance Prudential Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8560" xlink:label="loc_DE8560"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8560" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of the total gross ultimate cost (inflated &amp; undiscounted) of claims, as at the relevant date.

This item represents the sum of:
     - gross claims payment expenses incurred, as at the relevant date;
     - gross case estimates as at the relevant date; and
     - gross claims incurred but not reported (IBNR)/incurred but not enough reported (IBNER) as at the relevant date;</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8560" xlink:to="lbl_DE8560"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8560" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Total Ultimate Cost Gross Reinsurance Recoveries And Net Non Reinsurance Recoveries Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8561" xlink:label="loc_DE8561"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8561" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of the total net ultimate cost (inflated &amp; undiscounted) of claims, as at the relevant date.

This item represents the sum of:
     - net claims payment expenses incurred, as at the relevant date;
     - net case estimates, as at the relevant date; and
     - net claims incurred but not reported (IBNR)/incurred but not enough reported (IBNER), as at the relevant date;</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8561" xlink:to="lbl_DE8561"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8561" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Total Ultimate Cost Net Reinsurance And Non Reinsurance Recoveries Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8669" xlink:label="loc_DE8669"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8669" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of acquisition costs and other underwriting expenses recognised during the relevant period, as determined in accordance with relevant Accounting Standards.

This item should be an aggregate of all expenses incurred in writing insurance business gross of any commission revenue.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8669" xlink:to="lbl_DE8669"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8669" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Underwriting Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8574" xlink:label="loc_DE8574"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8574" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of acquisition costs and other underwriting expenses recognised during the relevant period, as determined in accordance with relevant Accounting Standards.

This item should be an aggregate of all expenses incurred in writing insurance business. However, for the purposes of this item exclude:
- commission or brokerage paid to agents or brokers for obtaining business for the insurer; and
- results of the liability adequacy test (LAT).

Acquisition costs are incurred in obtaining and recording insurance contracts. They include commission or brokerage paid to agent or brokers for obtaining business for the insurer, selling and underwriting costs such as advertising and risk assessment, the administrative costs of recording policy information and premium collection costs.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8574" xlink:to="lbl_DE8574"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8574" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Underwriting Excluding Liability Adequacy Test Results And Commission Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE457" xlink:label="loc_DE457"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE457" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of underwriting expenses incurred during the relevant period. This item is to be determined in accordance with the relevant accounting standards.

Underwriting expenses represents the sum of acquisition costs (including the results of the liability adequacy tests), levies and charges, commission expense (net of commission revenue) and any other expenses attributable to providing underwriting operations</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE457" xlink:to="lbl_DE457"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE457" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Underwriting Expenses Total Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8491" xlink:label="loc_DE8491"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8491" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is a balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of any other underwriting expenses, as required on APRA form GRF 310 0. This item is determined in accordance with the relevant Accounting Standards.

Other underwriting expenses excludes:
- acquisition costs and the results of liability adequacy tests;
- levies and charges; and
- commission expense.

Acquisition costs are incurred in obtaining and recording insurance contracts. They include commission or brokerage paid to agent or brokers for obtaining business for the insurer, selling and underwriting costs such as advertising and risk assessment, the administrative costs of recording policy information and premium collection costs.

Liability adequacy test means an assessment of whether the carrying amount of an insurance liability needs to be increased (or the carrying amount of the related deferred acquisition costs or related intangible assets decreased) based on a review of future cash flows.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8491" xlink:to="lbl_DE8491"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8491" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Insurance Underwriting Other GRF 310 0 Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8952" xlink:label="loc_DE8952"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8952" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, during the relevant period, of outwards reinsurance expense as determined in accordance with relevant prudential standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8952" xlink:to="lbl_DE8952"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8952" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Expense Prospective Outwards Reinsurance Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8573" xlink:label="loc_DE8573"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8573" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of the reduction in claims expense recognised for the relevant period which is due to prior period reserve releases. This item refers to movements in outstanding claims provisions due to changes in the assumptions used to calculate outstanding claims in prior periods that result in decreases in the provision. It includes the impact of changes in the probability of sufficiency, and the release of risk margin as claims are paid.

This item is determined in accordance with the relevant accounting standards, except that it is not discounted as required by those accounting standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8573" xlink:to="lbl_DE8573"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8573" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Claims Gross Reserve Releases Not Discounted Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8492" xlink:label="loc_DE8492"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8492" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of commission revenue earned in relation to the insurance business. This item is determined in accordance with the relevant Accounting Standards.

This item excludes premium rebates received from reinsurers.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8492" xlink:to="lbl_DE8492"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8492" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Commission Excluding Reinsurer Premium Rebates Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8527" xlink:label="loc_DE8527"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8527" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the description of the detailed line item comprising the other distributions balancing item, as required to be reported on APRA Insurance forms 310.3.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8527" xlink:to="lbl_DE8527"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8527" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Distributions Other APRA 310 3 Description</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8526" xlink:label="loc_DE8526"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8526" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is a balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

This is the value of all other distributions received during the relevant period, as required on APRA forms. This item excludes dividend income, rental income, interest income and distributions received from trusts.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8526" xlink:to="lbl_DE8526"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8526" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Distributions Other Excluding Dividend Rental Interest And Trust Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8488" xlink:label="loc_DE8488"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8488" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of premium revenue earned during the relevant period. This item is to be determined in accordance with the relevant accounting standards.

This item includes any fire service levy and other levies imposed by state and territory governments and is gross of any associated outwards reinsurance expense.

Premium is earned by recognising deferred revenue as a liability in accordance with the pattern of the incidence of risk expected under the policy.

Premium revenue must be recognised in line with the following:

Premium recognition for direct business: Premium revenue must be recognised fully upfront on the date the policy is accepted (bound) by insurers writing direct business. 

Premium recognition for inwards reinsurance business: Premium revenue for inwards reinsurance business is to be recognised from the date of acceptance of the reinsurance risk by the reinsurer. Reinsurers are required to recognise the premium based on the Gross Premium Income to be written by the direct insurer under the contract for proportional reinsurance. For excess of loss reinsurance contracts, the premium revenue is to be recognised on the basis of the agreed minimum/deposit premium, which will be subject to a final adjustment factor applied to the final declared values of the premium determinant. 

Premium revenue must be discounted where it is to be received beyond the current year of cover under an insurance/reinsurance contract. In these cases, use the discount rate as required in calculating insurance liabilities in accordance with GPS 310 Audit and Actuarial Reporting and Valuation. 

Premium revenue excludes amounts collected on behalf of third parties i.e. government stamp duty and taxes.

Levies charged to insured, such as fire service levies, are to be included as premium revenue.

Premium refunds and rebates are to be deducted from premium revenue. 

For instalment premium policies, the amount of the annualised premium is to be used. Where premium is calculated on an adjustment basis, the estimated annual premium is to be brought to account, with the estimated premium being replaced by the actual amount as it becomes known. 

Where premium is accepted on a deposit basis, the full annual premium is to be brought into account. 

Premium revenue must be gross of reinsurance expense. 

Premium revenue includes premium receivable on unclosed business. This includes the business which has been accepted by the insurer/reinsurer prior to the balance date but there is insufficient information to fully identify the business.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8488" xlink:to="lbl_DE8488"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8488" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Earned Premium Revenue Gross Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8487" xlink:label="loc_DE8487"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8487" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of premium revenue earned during the relevant period.  This item is to be determined in accordance with the relevant accounting standards.

This item excludes any fire service levy or other levies imposed by state and territory governments and is gross of any associated outwards reinsurance expense.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8487" xlink:to="lbl_DE8487"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8487" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Earned Premium Revenue Gross Excluding Fire Service Or Other Government Levy Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8586" xlink:label="loc_DE8586"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8586" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of any fee income or commission associated with underwriting for the relevant period.

Do not include commission revenue that is associated with underwriting activities and is disclosed as commission revenue in the calculation of underwriting expenses in accordance with relevant Accounting Standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8586" xlink:to="lbl_DE8586"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8586" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Fees And Commissions Underwriting Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8585" xlink:label="loc_DE8585"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8585" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is a balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

This is the value of other fee and commission income, as required on APRA Insurance form 310_3.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8585" xlink:to="lbl_DE8585"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8585" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Fees Commissions Other 310 3 Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8478" xlink:label="loc_DE8478"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8478" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of insurance premium revenue derived from fire service and other state and territory government levies (FSL) that was earned during the relevant period.  This item is to be determined in accordance with the relevant accounting standards.

FSL is earned in accordance with the pattern of the incidence of risk expected under the policy.

This item is gross of any associated outwards reinsurance expense.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8478" xlink:to="lbl_DE8478"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8478" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Fire Service And Other Government Levies Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8023" xlink:label="loc_DE8023"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8023" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of income received in relation to general insurance business. This income includes fee and commission income derived from selling General Insurance products, as determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8023" xlink:to="lbl_DE8023"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8023" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance General Business Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8024" xlink:label="loc_DE8024"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8024" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of income received in relation to life insurance business. This income includes fee and commission income derived from selling Life Insurance products, as determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8024" xlink:to="lbl_DE8024"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8024" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Life Business Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE7527" xlink:label="loc_DE7527"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE7527" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the change in the excess of the market value over the net assets of life insurance subsidiaries in which the reporting party has invested, that has been recognised as income in the relevant period, as determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE7527" xlink:to="lbl_DE7527"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE7527" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Life Movement Excess NMV Over Net Assets Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8482" xlink:label="loc_DE8482"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8482" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of revenue from recoveries other than those from reinsurance in respect of insurance claims. This item is determined in accordance with the Accounting Standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8482" xlink:to="lbl_DE8482"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8482" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Non Reinsurance Recoveries Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8583" xlink:label="loc_DE8583"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8583" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of operating income for the relevant period, as required to be reported on GRF_310_3.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8583" xlink:to="lbl_DE8583"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8583" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Operating GRF 310 3 Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8498" xlink:label="loc_DE8498"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8498" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of other operating income. This item represents all income which is not considered part of the insurance result or investment income on shareholders' funds.

The insurance result represents the sum of the underwriting result and any investment income on assets backing insurance liabilities net of investment expenses on assets backing insurance liabilities. Underwriting result represents net premium revenue less net claims expense and total underwriting expenses.

Investment income on shareholders' funds represents investment income that is associated or attributable to the investment of shareholders' funds only. In cases where the insurer has an existing internal split of the assets between shareholders and insurance liabilities then this should be used to determine the investment income attributable to shareholder funds. Otherwise insurers must assume that the insurance liabilities are backed by investment assets and proportionally allocate the investment income to the insurance liabilities and the balance to shareholders fund.

These items are determined in accordance with the relevant Accounting Standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8498" xlink:to="lbl_DE8498"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8498" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Operating Other Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8548" xlink:label="loc_DE8548"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8548" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the description of the detailed line item comprising the other income balancing item, as required to be reported on APRA Insurance forms 310_3.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8548" xlink:to="lbl_DE8548"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8548" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Other Description</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8547" xlink:label="loc_DE8547"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8547" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is a balancing item in the list in which it is being used.

This is the value of other income for the duration of the relevant period, as required on APRA Insurance forms 310_3.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8547" xlink:to="lbl_DE8547"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8547" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Other APRA 310 3 Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8509" xlink:label="loc_DE8509"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8509" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of net premium revenue recognised during the relevant period. This represents premium revenue determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards, less reinsurance expense determined in accordance with relevant prudential standards.

This item includes any fire service levy and other levies imposed by state and territory governments and is net of any associated outwards reinsurance expense.

Premium is earned by recognising deferred revenue as a liability in accordance with the pattern of the incidence of risk expected under the policy.

Premium revenue must be recognised in line with the following:

Premium recognition for direct business: Premium revenue must be recognised fully upfront on the date the policy is accepted (bound) by insurers writing direct business. 

Premium recognition for inwards reinsurance business: Premium revenue for inwards reinsurance business is to be recognised from the date of acceptance of the reinsurance risk by the reinsurer. Reinsurers are required to recognise the premium based on the Gross Net Premium Income to be written by the direct insurer under the contract for proportional reinsurance. For excess of loss reinsurance contracts, the premium revenue is to be recognised on the basis of the agreed minimum/deposit premium, which will be subject to a final adjustment factor applied to the final declared values of the premium determinant. 

Premium revenue must be discounted where it is to be received beyond the current year of cover under an insurance/reinsurance contract. In these cases, use the discount rate as required in calculating insurance liabilities in accordance with GPS 310 Audit and Actuarial Reporting and Valuation. 

Premium revenue excludes amounts collected on behalf of third parties i.e. government stamp duty and taxes.

Premium refunds and rebates are to be deducted from premium revenue. 

For instalment premium policies, the amount of the annualised premium is to be used. Where premium is calculated on an adjustment basis, the estimated annual premium is to be brought to account, with the estimated premium being replaced by the actual amount as it becomes known. 

Where premium is accepted on a deposit basis, the full annual premium is to be brought into account. 

Premium revenue must be gross of reinsurance expense. 

Premium revenue includes premium receivable on unclosed business. This includes the business which has been accepted by the insurer/reinsurer prior to the balance date but there is insufficient information to fully identify the business. 

Reinsurance expense is to be recognised in accordance with the pattern of reinsurance service received as required by relevant Accounting Standards. Reinsurance expense will be recognised from the attachment date over the period of indemnity of the reinsurance contract in accordance with the expected pattern of the incident of risk. This may vary according to the type of reinsurance contract as outlined below.

For reinsurance written on risks attaching or, equivalently, an underwriting period basis, current reinsurance contracts are fully matched to the underlying insurance portfolios. Reinsurance coverage for the underlying portfolio is recognised as the underlying policies are written.

For reinsurance written on a losses occurring basis, current reinsurance contracts provide coverage for any risks exposed during the reinsurance period irrespective of when the underlying business was written. Such reinsurance covers both the unexpired portion of policies in force at the contract commencement date and that portion of new business and renewals written during the year that is earned up to the contract expiry date. This latter portion relates to business which has not yet been written at the contract commencement date.

It is expected that initially the full minimum and deposit premium would be recognised as an expense, with any necessary adjustments due to experience at subsequent relevant dates.

Where payments under a reinsurance contract extend beyond the current year of cover, reinsurance expense is to be discounted using similar discount rates as required in measuring insurance liabilities in accordance with AASB 1023.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8509" xlink:to="lbl_DE8509"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8509" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Premium Revenue Net Prudential Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8955" xlink:label="loc_DE8955"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8955" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of relevant period, reinsurance recoveries received on a cash flow basis in the current financial year, regardless of the financial year in which the reinsurance recovery may have been recognised as revenue.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8955" xlink:to="lbl_DE8955"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8955" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Recoveries Reinsurance Received Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8483" xlink:label="loc_DE8483"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8483" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of revenue from reinsurance recoveries in respect of insurance claims. This item is to be determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8483" xlink:to="lbl_DE8483"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8483" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Reinsurance Recoveries Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8953" xlink:label="loc_DE8953"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8953" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of subscription and membership income.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8953" xlink:to="lbl_DE8953"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8953" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Subscription Membership Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8562" xlink:label="loc_DE8562"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8562" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of gross written insurance premium revenue recognised during the relevant period, as determined in accordance with relevant Accounting Standards.

This item includes any fire service levy or other levies imposed by state and territory governments and is gross of any associated outwards reinsurance expense.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8562" xlink:to="lbl_DE8562"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8562" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Written Premium Revenue Gross Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8505" xlink:label="loc_DE8505"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8505" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of gross written insurance premium revenue recognised during the relevant period, as determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.

This item excludes any fire service levy or other levies imposed by state and territory governments and is gross of any associated outwards reinsurance expense.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8505" xlink:to="lbl_DE8505"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8505" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Written Premium Revenue Gross Excluding Fire Service Or Other Government Levy Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8568" xlink:label="loc_DE8568"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8568" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of gross written insurance premium revenue recognised during the relevant period, and which is related to unclosed business.

Unclosed business is that which has been accepted by the insurer/reinsurer prior to the balance date but there is insufficient information to fully identify the business.

This item excludes any fire service levy or other levies imposed by state and territory governments and is gross of any associated outwards reinsurance expense.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8568" xlink:to="lbl_DE8568"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8568" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Written Premium Revenue Gross Excluding Fire Service Or Other Government Levy Unclosed Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8563" xlink:label="loc_DE8563"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8563" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of net written insurance premium revenue recognised during the relevant period, determined in accordance with relevant accounting standards.

This item includes any fire service levy or other levies imposed by state and territory governments and is net of any associated outwards reinsurance expense.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8563" xlink:to="lbl_DE8563"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8563" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Insurance Written Premium Revenue Net Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8974" xlink:label="loc_DE8974"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8974" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of a credit available to a taxpayer who received foreign income that is taxable in Australia and for which they paid (or are taken to have paid) foreign tax. This amount includes credits for foreign source capital gains.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8974" xlink:to="lbl_DE8974"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8974" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income.International Dealings Foreign Tax Offset Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE7466" xlink:label="loc_DE7466"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE7466" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is proceeds received/receivable from the insurer and/or accrued in relation to the death or disability of policyholders, including amounts for total and permanent disability and temporary disability/income protection.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE7466" xlink:to="lbl_DE7466"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE7466" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Insurance Proceeds Death Disability Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8546" xlink:label="loc_DE8546"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8546" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the profit (loss) after tax or the relevant period. This item is calculated in accordance with the relevant Prudential Standards and represents profit (loss) after tax of both continuing and discontinued operations.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8546" xlink:to="lbl_DE8546"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8546" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Insurance After Tax Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8598" xlink:label="loc_DE8598"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8598" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the profit (loss) after tax for the relevant period attributable to members of the reporting party. This item is calculated in accordance with the relevant Prudential Standards and represents the proportion of profit (loss) after tax of both continuing and discontinued operations  attributable directly, or indirectly to the members of the reporting party.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8598" xlink:to="lbl_DE8598"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8598" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Insurance After Tax Attributable To Members Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8597" xlink:label="loc_DE8597"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8597" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the profit (loss) after tax for the relevant period attributable to non-controlling interests. This item is calculated in accordance with the relevant Prudential Standards and represents the proportion of profit (loss) after tax of both continuing and discontinued operations not attributable directly, or indirectly to the parent of the reporting party.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8597" xlink:to="lbl_DE8597"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8597" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Insurance After Tax Attributable To Non Controlling Interests Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8542" xlink:label="loc_DE8542"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8542" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the profit (loss) before tax for the relevant period. This item is calculated in accordance with the relevant Prudential Standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8542" xlink:to="lbl_DE8542"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8542" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Insurance Continuing Before Tax Prudential Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8544" xlink:label="loc_DE8544"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8544" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the profit (loss) after tax for the relevant period. This item is calculated in accordance with the relevant Prudential Standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8544" xlink:to="lbl_DE8544"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8544" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Insurance Continuing Operations After Tax Prudential Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8545" xlink:label="loc_DE8545"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8545" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the profit (loss) after tax from discontinued operations for the relevant period. This item is calculated in accordance with the relevant Prudential Standards. It represents the operating results of discontinued operations and the gain or loss on sale of the discontinued operations. Remeasurement gains or losses of non-current assets or disposal groups classified as held for sale which meet the definition of a discontinued operation are excluded from this value.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8545" xlink:to="lbl_DE8545"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8545" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Insurance Discontinued Operations After Tax Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8497" xlink:label="loc_DE8497"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8497" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the duration of the relevant period, of the insurance result. 

This item represents the sum of the underwriting result and any investment income on assets backing insurance liabilities net of investment expenses on assets backing insurance liabilities.

Underwriting result represents net premium revenue, in accordance with the Prudential Standards, less net claims expense and total underwriting expenses as determined by the relevant Accounting Standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8497" xlink:to="lbl_DE8497"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8497" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Insurance Result Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8541" xlink:label="loc_DE8541"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8541" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value of the underwriting result for the relevant period. This represents net premium revenue as determined by the relevant Prudential Standards, less net incurred claims and underwriting expenses in accordance with the relevant Accounting Standards. 

For this item net premium revenue represents premium revenue (including any fire service levy and other levies imposed by state and territory governments) determined in accordance with relevant Accounting Standards, less reinsurance expense determined in accordance with relevant Prudential Standards.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8541" xlink:to="lbl_DE8541"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8541" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Insurance Underwriting Result Prudential Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE2318" xlink:label="loc_DE2318"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2318" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the value, for the relevant period, of net profit or loss after tax, calculated in accordance with prospective accounting principles</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE2318" xlink:to="lbl_DE2318"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE2318" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Prospective After Income Tax Attributable To Company Members Net Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE7680" xlink:label="loc_DE7680"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE7680" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the net value, as at the relevant date, of any unrealised fair value gains and (losses) arising from changes in the reporting party's creditworthiness. A gain may arise, for example, from a reduction in fair value of the reporting party's outstanding debt due to a change in credit rating.

A net gain must be reported as a positive figure and a net loss as a negative figure.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE7680" xlink:to="lbl_DE7680"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE7680" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Unrealised Change In Creditworthiness Fair Value Gains Net Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE7464" xlink:label="loc_DE7464"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE7464" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is, for the duration of the relevant period, unrealised gains or (losses) recognised on equity securities.

Unrealised gains/losses
The change in the net market value is the increase or decrease in the market value of each asset compared to the value of that asset at the beginning of the relevant period. These assets are still owned by the entity at the end of the period, they have not been disposed of, and as a result, the gains or losses on the assets are unrealised. If the assets are disposed of during the period, then the gains or losses are realised.
Only include the movement in the net market value of the asset. Do not include the movement in the value of the currency relative to the local currency if the asset is denominated in a currency other than the local currency.

Equity investments or securities are, as defined by the Australian Accounting Standards, contracts that evidence a residual interest in the assets of an entity after deducting all its liabilities.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE7464" xlink:to="lbl_DE7464"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE7464" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Unrealised Equity Securities Amount</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8431" xlink:label="loc_DE8431"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8431" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the description of the detailed line item comprising the balancing item for other realised or unrealised gains/losses brought to account, as required to be reported on APRA form SRF_100_0.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8431" xlink:to="lbl_DE8431"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8431" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Unrealised Other SRF 100 0 Description</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8433" xlink:label="loc_DE8433"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8433" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the description of the detailed line item comprising the balancing item for other realised or unrealised gains/losses brought to account, as required to be reported on APRA form SRF_200_0.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8433" xlink:to="lbl_DE8433"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8433" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Unrealised Other SRF 200 0 Description</link:label>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="bafpr3.02.05.data.xsd#DE8432" xlink:label="loc_DE8432"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8432" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">This is the description of the detailed line item comprising the balancing item for other realised or unrealised gains/losses brought to account, as required to be reported on APRA form SRF_300_0.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE8432" xlink:to="lbl_DE8432"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE8432" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Profit Or Loss Unrealised Other SRF 300 0 Description</link:label>
    </link:labelLink>
</link:linkbase>
