<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Disclaimer: http://www.sbr.gov.au/content/taxonomy_introduction_3_0.htm#Disclaimer -->
<link:linkbase xmlns:link="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xbrli="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance">
    <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#businessDefinition"/>
    <link:roleRef roleURI="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xlink:type="simple" xlink:href="../../../fdtn/tech.sbr.01.02.xsd#dataElementGuidance"/>
    <link:labelLink xlink:type="extended" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/link">
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rvctc1.02.06.data.xsd#rvctc1.02.06_rvctc1Abstract" xlink:label="loc_rvctc1.02.06_rvctc1Abstract"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_rvctc1Abstract" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Tax Collection 1</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_rvctc1.02.06_rvctc1Abstract" xlink:to="lbl_rvctc1Abstract"/>
        <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="rvctc1.02.06.data.xsd#DE1670" xlink:label="loc_DE1670"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1670" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/businessDefinition" xml:lang="en">A code that is given to each beneficiary, where the beneficiary is presently entitled to a share of the income of a trust and also against income to which no beneficiary is presently entitled and in which no beneficiary has an indefeasible vested interest.</link:label>
        <link:labelArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-label" xlink:from="loc_DE1670" xlink:to="lbl_DE1670"/>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1670" xlink:role="http://sbr.gov.au/fdtn/sbr.01.02.tech/dataElementGuidance" xml:lang="en">Valid values are:

11 = Deceased Estate - Resident beneficiary under a legal disability
12 = Deceased Estate - Resident beneficiary not under a legal disability
13 = Deceased Estate - Resident company 
14 = Deceased Estate - Resident trustee
15 = Deceased Estate - No beneficiary entitled and deceased person died =&lt; 3 years 
16 = Deceased Estate - No beneficiary entitled and deceased person died &gt; 3 years 
17 = Deceased Estate - Non resident trust 
25 = Inter Vivos - Resident beneficiary - Over 18 years and under legal disability
26 = Inter Vivos - Resident beneficiary - Receiving excepted income only
27 = Inter Vivos - Resident beneficiary - Receiving eligible income only
28 = Inter Vivos - Resident beneficiary - Receiving excepted and eligible income 
29 = Inter Vivos - Resident beneficiary - Receiving income from multiple trusts
30 = Inter Vivos - Resident beneficiary - Not under legal disability
34 = Inter Vivos - Resident beneficiary - A company
35 = Inter Vivos - Resident beneficiary - A trustee
36 = Inter Vivos Trusts - Resident beneficiary - No Beneficiary entitled to income.
37 = Inter Vivos Trusts - Resident beneficiary - A bankrupt estate or no beneficiary entitled.
45 = Inter Vivos Trusts - Resident beneficiary - A special disability trust.
111 = Deceased Estate - Non Resident beneficiary under a legal disability
118 = Deceased Estate - Non Resident beneficiary not under a legal disability
119 = Deceased Est - Non Resident beneficiary company 
120 = Deceased Est - Non Resident beneficiary trustee
125 = Inter Vivos - Non Resident beneficiary - Over 18 years and under legal disability
126 = Inter Vivos - Non Resident beneficiary - Receiving excepted income only
127 = Inter Vivos - Non Resident beneficiary - Receiving eligible income only
128 = Inter Vivos - Non Resident beneficiary - Receiving excepted and eligible income 
129 = Inter Vivos - Non Resident beneficiary -  Receiving income from multiple trusts
138 = Inter Vivos - Non Resident beneficiary - Not under legal disability
139 = Inter Vivos - Non Resident beneficiary - A company
140 = Inter Vivos - Non Resident beneficiary - A trustee
145 = Inter Vivos - Non Resident beneficiary - A special disability trust</link:label>
        <link:label xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="lbl_DE1670" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/label" xml:lang="en">Income Tax Assessment Calculation Code</link:label>
    </link:labelLink>
</link:linkbase>
